Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Friend Is a Young Kabuki Actor
Takumi-kun!
That's safe even when used while diving, right?
Yeah! The modern people cherish time.
My papa said that one mustn't forget about valuable time even during leisure...
Is that really so...
That toy still suits you, Kouta-kun.
This isn't a toy!
What are you doi-...!
K-Kosuke-kun...
Takumi, you've got a nice watch, huh?
No... Um... It's nothing worthy for Kosuke-kun to look at... It's just a cheap product.
I see! So I can have it, right?
Stop it, Kosuke-kun!
What?
You can't do that!
Hey! Your clock has the mark of Exkaiser!
T-That's right...
I'll take it!
No! You can't take it!
Can you call Exkaiser with this or something?
Is it this button?
Don't push it!
Uh oh...
How interesting! Exkaiser!
Who's this?
It's not Kouta's voice...
What? It's just a toy...
That's right! So give it back...
But I'll still borrow it!
No way! Kosuke-kun!
I'm in trouble without it!
But this one's more expensive...
I'm sure Kosuke's house was
somewhere around here...
Kosuke!
How many times do I have to tell you?
Huh?
Mr. Tokuda!
Kouta-kun!
Did something happen?
Yeah, the kabuki actor Mr. Ichimura Chiyonosuke was selected as a Living National Treasure,
so I'm here to interview him.
Living National Treasure?
Yeah! It means that he's become a treasure of our country.
Kosuke! Practicing is the soul of an actor!
Kosuke?
He's having me wait until he's done with his son's practicing.
It's rather tough to be the son of a
distinguished family in the kabuki world.
Kosuke is that?
Don't you still understand?
I'm so sorry, father!
Tomorrow is finally the opening day.
You do understand that, Kosuke?
Yes, father!
You'll be practicing tomorrow
from morning till the play.
But I have school...
I have asked permission from
the teacher, so don't worry.
Think only about the stage now.
Are you Kosuke's friend?
Y-Yes!
He's my classmate Hoshikawa Kouta-kun, father.
Kosuke, did you make plans even though you know you have to practice?
N-No... Um...
U-Um... It's fine! I was just in the neighborhood, so...
Excuse me!
Wait a minute, Kouta-kun!
Hey, what's the matter?
And so...
It became harder to get it back... This sucks...
But to take things from others...
So there's someone like the Geisters at Kouta's elementary school, huh?
He's even worse than the Geisters!
What? Worse than Geisters?
Unforgivable! I'll definitely get it back!
It's not like that! He's just a mischievous kid!
Mischievous kid?
What's that?
Ah, it's fine! I'll get it back surely.
It really is alright, okay?
If Exkaiser would really go, it'd be a big commotion!
He sure doesn't get jokes...
Everyone, today I'm visiting the home of the person who has been selected as a Living National Treasure.
It's the kabuki actor Ichimura Chiyonosuke.
Ah! It's Kosuke!
Do you know him, Kouta?
Yeah, he's my classmate...
What did you say?
Hey! Why haven't you told me that such a famous person is in your class?
I didn't know!
I bet a kabuki actor's child is so
polite even at school...
Um...
Well, yeah...
Hey, does he happen to have a big brother?
If he has, introduce us! Okay? Okay?
Oh, you like kabuki too, Fuuko?
I like all celebrities whether they're in kabuki or comedy shows!
Celebrity?
They said it's a human treasure.
Are there treasures and non-treasures even among humans?
Well, there are idiots and a genius among us, too!
Who did you call an idiot?
Armor and Horn equal two idiots!
What did you say?
Shut up!
By the way, what is a treasure
for you, Mr. Chiyonosuke?
Of course the audience is one... and this child who'll follow in my footsteps.
Treasure of father and son, huh? Interesting!
Wake up...
Are you Kosuke?
I know you did bad things at school today.
If you only do bad things,
horrifying things will happen to you.
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
Repent for your sins!
I won't do it again!
Understood?
I won't do it ever again! I'm sorry!
I'm going!
Good morning! You sure are early.
I'll drop by Kosuke's house first and get back the Kaiser bracelet!
It's alright, I'm sure he'll give it back.
I can guarantee it!
Did you do something?
No, it's just... Come on, go ahead!
Kosuke! Kosuke!
Kosuke!
Kouta, run!
Ah, wait! Kosuke!
Weren't you off from school today?
I don't care about that!
Hey! Give back the bracelet!
No way!
Damn... This is completely different from what Exkaiser said.
Pass! Pass!
Pass here!
Kouta! If you can steal this ball,
I'll give back the bracelet!
Alright!
This is my victory! Shot!
Kosuke-kun!
It's mine now!
Oh my... Are you alright, Kosuke-kun?
What is it, teacher?
Your father called that you must go to the theater immediately.
See? They've come to pick you up.
We all got invitations, so we'll come watch it later! Do your best!
Yes...
Let's settle the score later.
I'll borrow this a little while more!
Kosuke...
Everyone, watch today's play politely.
We can see the admired Mr. Ichimura Chiyonosuke in person, after all!
Teacher seems to be a fan of Kosuke's father!
Huh? Kouta-kun?
My only chance to retrieve the Kaiser
bracelet is when Kosuke is on stage...
But...
Where is Kosuke's room?
Hi!
Mr. Tokuda!
Are you going to check on Kosuke-kun
in his dressing room?
Don't scare me like that!
This is a good timing! I'm about to go interview Mr. Chiyonosuke, so let's go togeth-...
You're in the way! Please move away.
Oh my, what a handsome man...
Excuse us!
Who are you?
Um... W-We're sorry!
It's like we've come to a whole different world...
It's not something you want to see up close...
Say that once more!
W-We're sorry!
Where is your makeup?
Do you intend to get on stage with that face?
And I definitely told you to get rid of things that aren't used on stage.
Take off that toy-like watch!
No!
Are you still talking back?
It's the Kaiser bracelet!
No! I won't take it off!
Kosuke!
Stage this and stage that! Father doesn't think about anything else than the stage!
I even had to stop playing soccer halfway through!
Kosuke!
I'm quitting acting!
Kosuke! Wait!
Kosuke!
Ouch!
Kouta!
Is it fine to skip the play?
It's fine.
But doesn't this trouble your father?
I don't care!
I hate my father!
It can't be helped. Let's do it without Kosuke.
Open the curtain.
But then...
The audience is waiting for us!
I wonder where Kouta-kun went...
What's this?
I-Is this perhaps a new idea?
It's not! It's Geisters!
Which ones are the treasure called father and son?
Is it these?
Those are not father and son!
It's Geisters!
Who is the Living National Treasure?
Come out!
Could it be that Geisters are
targeting Kosuke's father?
Seems like it.
Father!
Kosuke! While I'm distracting them, you must lead the audience to a safe place!
Come on! I'm counting on you!
Father!
You monsters!
I am Ichimura Chiyonosuke!
It's the father.
Treasure!
We'll be taking you!
Father!
Kosuke, what are you doing?
You must protect the audience!
Y-Yes!
Stop running around!
Takumi-kun, we must escape quickly!
Kotomi-chan!
Kouta-kun!
Let's go to the backdoor quickly!
Come on! Over here!
Bastard!
How irritating!
Let's take the whole house!
Teacher! Please hold on!
The theater is...!
That's...
Father!
Kosuke!
Don't come here! Escape!
But...!
Don't worry about me! Just hurry!
Give back my father!
Kosuke!
I got the treasure!
Look out!
I did it!
It disappeared...
Kosuke! Give me the bracelet!
What are you saying at a time like this!
This is exactly the right time!
K-Kosuke!
Kosuke! Press quickly the bracelet's switch!
But...
You have to call for Exkaiser!
But this is...
You want to save your father, right?
It's alright! Exkaiser will definitely come!
Kosuke, hurry!
Exkaiser, help! Help my father! Please!
Oh no! Kouta is in danger!
We got the treasure!
Exkaiser!
Damn Geisters!
Are you increasing your crimes by trampling over the love of father and son?
Exkaiser!
He really came...
We're different from ordinary today!
Let's go, Thunder!
Yeah!
Double Fusion, Pteder!
Whoa! Geisters combined!
Take the treasure with you and go quickly!
Wait!
We are your opponents!
Dragon Jet!
What!
Let go of him!
Exkaiser!
Father!
Kosuke!
Damn you!
Do it!
Dragon Jet!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, Dragon Kaiser!
Geisters!
Stop the futile resistance!
Let's go!
Dragon Kaiser is...!
Die!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Super Giant Fusion, Great Exkaiser!
Kaiser Sword!
Thunder Crash!
This is bad! Let's retreat!
Thank you so very much!
Think nothing of it... The caring feelings
Kosuke-kun had for his father called me.
But...
You didn't come the first time I called...
Even if I'm not called,
I'll come rushing to any place
where Geisters appear.
I see! So this is really a toy...
Kouta! I'll give it back!
Catch it!
It'll break!
Don't do that, Kosuke.
Here goes!
Got it!
There goes!
Kosuke-kun!
Kosuke!
Just like there's sand on a beach,
there's bound to be mischievous kids in the world!
Yo! You're the best in Japan!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Has your school already had a sports day?
I got the first place prize, you know!
And so I was chosen as the torch runner for the next Olympic!
Isn't it amazing?
I can run together with all the star athletes from around the world!
But Geisters strike again!
Whoa! They'll take the arena!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Our Olympic
Is there an alien in your home, too?