Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Decisive Battle at the Snow Country
Let me out of here!
Your crimes will only get more
severe by doing this!
Shut up already!
... Is what Lord Dino Geist said!
What?
My comrades will come soon! Surely!
That's what you get! Serves you right!
Lord Dino Geist, please look at this.
These guys make use of the
vehicles that humans use.
They call them Shinkansen trains.
You can just be quiet!
We're going to reveal the true
identity of Exkaiser too.
Once we know it, we can get him with that shield!
Is that true, papa?
Yeah, it's a ski trip.
We can see the Snow Festival also.
This is the best!
A love (koi) might be born at
the white snowy slopes...
Oh, a carp (koi)? Did a carp born
in the neighborhood?
That's not it...
How come you look like that?
Starting now, I'll fire up the mood
for the Snow Festival like this!
A ski suit would be cooler...
Oh, is that so?
Mama, you look wonderful in both...
Kouta, could you say someth-...
What's the matter?
You've been looking down lately.
Aren't you happy about the ski trip?
I am...
If you're happy, then look more like it!
Mario, let's go...
Hey, Kouta...
I wonder what's wrong with Kouta...
I'm sure he got rejected by Kotomi-chan!
Snow Festival, huh...
Kouta, didn't you look forward to it?
You said that you wanted to ski, right?
It's not the time for that!
Aren't you worried about God Max?
Don't worry about God Max.
Raker Brothers are investigating currently.
But...!
I appreciate your feelings, but this is our problem.
Don't say that!
I'm also...
I know.
But we can only wait now.
So, Kouta... Please be your usual energetic self.
Yeah...
So wonderful!
So once we've passed the tunnel,
the Snow Country is revealed!
This is what they call a winter wonderland!
This is the Snow Country, huh?
Kouta-kun!
Kotomi-chan!
Hi! What a coincidence, Kouta.
You're sighing at the snow scenery?
You're so childish...
But it's so beautiful!
The Snow Country is like a backyard to me.
I see this every year, so I'm not
much impressed by it...
Well, I'm here now in order to
improve my skiing skills.
This year I'm escorting Kotomi-chan!
I got invited to Takumi-kun's villa.
Are you all going to ski, too?
Yeah...
We might meet over there...
So don't get weak at the knees
at my amazing sliding!
See you!
Kouta-kun, let's definitely meet later!
Kotomi-chan...
I knew you had troubles in love.
An earthquake!
It's a big one! I'll put on the brakes!
What?
Was it an earthquake?
Looks like this isn't it.
I'm fast!
It's not it...
Why does the traffic light stop me here...
Just what has happened?
Shinkansen trains are attacked by
dinosaur robots at various places!
We'll do repair work, so please
return to the earlier station!
Roger!
Geisters, huh?
What did you say?
Shinkansen trains are...
Geisters are attacking only Shinkansen trains.
And they're doing it at random.
So in other words, big brother...
Are they targeting us?
That's most likely so.
But we can't let innocent people
be involved because of us!
I'm currently returning there.
Be on the alert!
I got it!
That's...!
What's wrong, Green Raker?
How about that one?
Come out! You Raker bastards!
What on earth is that?
Big brother!
Geister is here!
What did you say?
Ptera Geist is destroying the garage!
I can't stand just watching here!
Wait!
If you move now, you'll reveal yourself!
But, big brother...!
I can't let that Geister do what he wants!
That's their trap! Just wait!
Might as well destroy these too!
Unforgivable! I can't take this anymore!
Wait!
Change!
Stop it, Ptera Geist!
I won't allow you to destroy any more!
The Shinkansen train turned into a robot!
So you finally showed yourself, Green Raker.
Wait! Where are you going?
Bye then!
Damn you! I won't let you escape!
T-This time the Shinkansen train flew!
He sure follows me...
Snow Festival
Hey, papa! Let's go sliding already!
Sure thing...
Papa, it's scary when we slide so
could you hold my hand?
It's alright, mama...
Oh? Where's Kouta?
So this is snow.
They're wonderful moldings.
I haven't seen such on any other planets!
So these crystallizations form this
beautiful pure white landscape.
Earth's mysticality keeps on surprising me.
Exkaiser!
It's my first time also to see this much snow!
I'd love to show this scenery to God Max too...
Kouta...
Kouta-kun!
Kotomi-chan!
What do you think about this style, Kouta?
It's fine... But the ski resort is over there.
Are you going to carry the skis from here?
You're so naive!
They're normally carried from here!
Hey, Kouta-kun! Would you come
slide together with us?
Don't try to act all cool just because
you're in front of Kotomi-chan!
T-That's not it!
Alright!
Me too!
You sure did it...
I'm glad.
Seems like Kouta is energetic again.
Alright! Me too!
O-Oh no!
Now you've done it!
Mr. Tokuda!
Here's my payback! Let's go!
Tokuda!
Chief editor!
You were here too?
Do you have a holiday too, Mr. Tokuda?
No such thing!
I'm going to cover this Snow Festival.
I came here in order to write an
article about these snow arts!
A snow robot won't run away, after all!
Oh come on now...
Exkaiser!
I'm currently following Ptera Geist and we're passing Oouba mountain!
Oouba mountain? It's right near here!
Geisters have finally come after us!
We were waiting for you!
Green Raker!
What's wrong? Please respond!
You fell for it, Green Raker!
Geisters!
As long as we bring you along,
we don't need this thing!
Change!
Don't try to act cool!
Serves you right!
Suffer even more!
Suffer and call for your big brother!
Big brother...
Wait!
Stop right there!
Big brother!
You finally came!
We've been waiting for you!
Big brother!
Are you alright, little brother?
I'm sorry that I acted on my own...
Now you're both here, Raker Brothers!
This place will become your graveyard!
Dino Geist!
Let's go, little brother!
Got it, big brother!
Form Up!
Left&Right Fusion, Ultra Raker!
Ultra Shoulder Crash!
That was great! Amazing!
What a big snowball!
I wonder if that was planned...
It moved!
My eyes are spinning...
Geisters!
Where are we?
Change!
Geisters!
Where is God Max?
Give him back!
Shut up!
This is terrible!
Dino Blade!
Let's go!
Black Thunder Storm!
God Max!
Oh no! Ultra Raker, you must escape!
It's too late now!
Dammit!
Ultra Raker!
Damn you, Dino Geist!
Dragon Jet!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, Dragon Kaiser!
Stop right there, Dragon Kaiser!
What?
Dino Geist!
Just look!
Dragon Kaiser!
God Max! Ultra Raker!
Damn you Geisters!
I'll capture you alive too!
Look out, Dragon Kaiser!
How impudent...
Dragon Corkscrew Kick!
I'll be taking the shield!
I won't let you!
The shield!
Kouta-kun!
Prepare yourself!
Here goes!
I can't shoot! Why?
Wait a minute...
This reminds me of that time...
That shield can't be used when it's soiled!
Really?
Then, Mr. Tokuda, let's use that!
This sword will be your end!
Damn...
Alright! How about now?
Mr. Tokuda!
Let's go!
We did it!
Let's return to where everyone is!
Yeah!
That kid is...!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Super Giant Fusion, Great Exkaiser!
Dino Geist!
I won't be showing you any mercy!
That damn kid!
Kouta-kun!
Look out, Kouta-kun!
Kouta!
We'll be taking this guy!
Wait, Dino Geist!
Now's the chance...
There we go!
Exkaiser!
That guy will fight against you!
Kaiser Sword!
Thunder Crash!
Kouta!
Kouta...
Kouta-kun...
Kouta!
Exkaiser...
Kouta, you were safe!
Thank goodness!
Kouta-kun!
Huh? Where's Mr. Tokuda?
This is Mr. Tokuda's!
Could Tokuda have been...
Taken away by the Geisters...
No way!
It's my fault...
Because he tried to save me...
Mr. Tokuda got...!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
It's too bad but Exkaiser will finally end next week.
Friends who watched every week...
And friends who only watched once in a while, thank you so much!
Well then, Exkaiser and Dino Geist's final battle will determine which will win!
It's super cool so don't forget
and definitely watch it!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
The last episode!
True Treasure
Is there an alien in your home, too?