Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Fuuko's Tanabata Story
Hikoboshi and Orihime got too well along, right?
They loved each other so much they weren't doing their important work.
And so they got torn apart by the angered God...
But they're allowed to meet once a year...
I know that. It's the 7th of July.
Tomorrow is the only day they can meet, right?
That's right.
I hope tomorrow will be sunny.
It'd be a shame to rain on their only date of the year, after all.
Yup!
"Please make me into a pilot."
"If a pilot is off the limits, even a racer would be fine."
What's up with you!
Sheesh, how can you write such childish things?
Can you talk about others?
I bet sister's wish is to have a boyfriend!
T-Too bad!
I want a boyfriend.
I don't even write wishes on a tanzaku!
Oh, don't say such things and try writing one?
I've no need for that! If I say I won't, then I won't!
Mario! Let's go for a walk!
Sheesh, she's not honest at all!
Sigh, why do I try to act more than I am...
That must be why I can't get a boyfriend...
I'd love to have a boyfriend...
Seems like you're not hurt.
Um, wait!
What a...
What a lovely voice...
You're not hurt, right?
Little miss.
To think that we met on the day before Tanabata...
What a destiny this is!
This must be a once in a lifetime, now or never love!
T-Those are the entrance tickets to Nanpu department store's observatory!
I heard that the latest telescope has just been added there.
Unlike normal telescopes, you can still see
the stars no matter how bright the surroundings are.
Is that so?
They're special tickets that let you look
through that latest telescope!
Since tomorrow is Tanabata, they'll let you look at Orihime and Hikoboshi.
Yahoo!
There's only two tickets, so Kouta
take your friend with-...
Thank you, papa!
It's the appropriate place for my love of the century!
Ah! My entrance tickets!
Mr. Hikoboshi will be glad too.
M-Mr. Hikoboshi?
The person of my destiny!
Our meeting was like destiny as it was with Orihime and Hikoboshi.
I've fallen in love!
Oh my! How wonderful!
Well then, everyone.
I shall go take a rest before you.
Ah! My entrance tickets!
Summon everyone!
If only I had those tickets, I could've seen the latest telescope with Kotomi-chan...
I wonder who's the person that sister loves...
Dash Max! What's wrong?
There's been a warning.
These past few days, something suspicious has been flying above the Kantou district.
Something suspicious... Geisters?
I thought that might be the case,
so I'm patrolling around.
See you!
Kouta!
Are you acquaintances with Mr. Hikoboshi?
S-Sister! That's painful!
Kouta-kun, you know Mr. Hikoboshi, right?
What's this talk about Hikoboshi?
The person who was driving that car... He's my love of the century!
That car?
Dash M-...!
So you really know him, Kouta!
I don't know him! He only asked for directions.
It's not for your own good to lie!
It's true!
Yeah, there's no way...
So the person my sister loves is Dash Max!
What should I do?
Isn't it a good thing to fall in love?
My sister thinks there's some wonderful person driving Dash Max.
If she finds out that nobody is driving...
How awful!
Why does such a thing have to happen on Tanabata!
Tanabata?
It's one of the summer's festivals.
When you write your wish on a tanzaku and tie
it on a bamboo, that wish becomes true.
It's a romantic day when torn away lovers meet for the only time in the year.
A romantic day?
So there's a lot of variations of romantic...
Kouta, where are you?
Kotomi-chan is here.
Exkaiser, please tell Dash Max that he
wouldn't come around here.
Absolutely!
It's the observatory's entrance tickets!
Would you like to go with me?
Eh, can I?
Yeah, I only have two so I was thinking of inviting Kouta-kun...
Alright!
I'll go! I'll absolutely go!
Uh oh...
I wasn't supposed to come around here...
I thought it was the love of the century, but I can't even meet him again...
Maybe it wasn't so after all...
This is bad...
You're Mr. Hikoboshi, right?
U-Um, you saved me the other day...
He's not there...
And here I thought it'd be our dramatic reunion...
Where did Mr. Hikoboshi go...
Car with MAX tag! Car with MAX tag!
You're illegally parked!
Please move out quickly!
But if I wait here, I'll eventually meet him!
What should I do!
This is Asahidai's 2-1-1!
Please send a tow truck immediately!
A tow truck?
Don't joke around!
If that happens, we can't have our dramatic reunion!
Who might you be?
"I'm the one you saved yesterday.
I'd like to meet you again and give you my thanks.
I'll be waiting at the Nanpu department store's event plaza."
Excuse me!
Wait a minute!
Hey, you!
What is it?
What is going on here?
What is your relation to that car?
Relation, you say! Oh sheesh!
Is it a car of someone you know?
Well... Yeah...
No, it isn't!
Which one is it?
Tow truck
Where is the car that needs to be moved?
Where are you looking at?
It's over there!
It's gone...
How amazing!
I can really see well!
That's Altair of Aquila!
It's Hikoboshi...
That's Vega of Lyra!
It's Orihime.
It was really pretty, right?
Yeah!
Ah, sister!
What's your horoscope?
Sister!
Ugh! This is the worst...
Sister, what are you doing over here?
Ah, I know!
Your date is not coming!
Am I right?
There's no way I'll get dumped!
I'm Orihime, you know!
Oh no!
I didn't write my name!
What should I do?
W-What the heck...
It can't be helped! I should just wait here.
If he reads that letter, Mr. Hikoboshi
will definitely come!
That's right, I just need to wait...
A-An earthquake?
Mr. Hikoboshi!
Ah! It's Geisters!
Treasure!
Idiot! That's not it!
Idiot?
I'm not an idiot!
Treasure... Treasure...
Ah, is that it?
Is that the treasure?
Jeez, can we even sell such thing?
Lord Dino Geist's whims are troublesome sometimes...
This is awful! It's going towards the observatory!
Run away!
W-What should I do...
I can't meet Mr. Hikoboshi at this rate!
Exkaiser! Exkaiser!
It's awful!
What? Geisters have appeared?
I got it, Kouta! I'll come immediately!
Dash Max! Dash Max!
I was listening, Exkaiser! I'm hurrying there!
Kouta-kun, hurry!
Ah, Kotomi-chan!
Sister, let's escape quickly!
You should escape quickly!
I'm going to wait for Mr. Hikoboshi here!
What are you saying at a time like this!
Kotomi-chan!!
That Ptera, I hope he isn't planning on getting the glory all by himself...
Hurry up!
Sister, we must escape quickly!
Let go! I'm not going to move from here until Mr. Hikoboshi comes!
It's not the time to be saying that!
We got found!
What should I do...
What's up with you!
This is the meeting place of my
important date, so go away already!
You idiot!
I-I'm not an idiot!
Sister! We must escape quickly!
No way! I'm absolutely not going
to leave from here!
I'm not an idiot!
Idiot is fair enough for you!
I'm angry!
Sister!
Mr. Hikoboshi!
Something went past...
That color!
I won't let you do as you wish!
This color... This voice...
It's the same as Mr. Hikoboshi's car!
H-He'll be revealed!
I see...
I'm sure God send him as the
replacement of Mr. Hikoboshi!
Right, Kouta?
T-That's right, sister!
He's the replacement of Mr. Hikoboshi!
What do you think? This'll be a piece of cake!
Is that really so?
Those who ruin the romantic festival that only happens once in a year...
I, Exkaiser, won't forgive them!
Don't talk nonsense!
Kill him!
I cannot destroy the telescope!
At this rate, the telescope will be stolen!
What should I do...
I-I'll fall!
Do your best!
The replacement of Mr. Hikoboshi!
Sister, hide quickly!
Why you!
This is bad!
If I fight here, Kouta-kun and his
sister will get involved!
Ah, he'll get done in!
Hurry up and hide!
H-He's falling!
Thanks, Sky Max!
No big deal!
Thank goodness...
This is your fault!
What the heck are you saying!
This time it's a black Hikoboshi!
I'm falling!
I can't get it off!
That's good!
Crush him into pieces!
Kill him!
He'll get done in!
What about Hikoboshi? Where is Hikoboshi?
Exkaiser!
They're getting away!
What are you doing?
W-Who is it?
Give up, Geisters!
We, Kaisers, won't overlook your evil deeds!
That's right! Yellow is truly the
best color for Hikoboshi!
This is bad! It's coming this way!
Run away!
W-We survived...
I'm having a bad feeling...
Kouta... You're heavy...
Sister!
Don't let go! I'll do whatever you want!
Oh no! Kouta is in danger!
Kouta!
I-I can't do it anymore... My legs are getting numb...
Please, sister!
I'll give you my TV games and my stuffed koala toy, so please don't let go!
N-No good!
My hands hurt so much, that...
I'm... I'm going to faint!
Sister, no! You can't faint!
Mr. Hikoboshi...
Stay here, Kouta!
Thank you, Dash Max!
Alright, let's combine!
Max Team, Form Up!
Triple Fusion, God Max!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
God Sonic Buster!
Kaiser Sword!
They got the telescope!
This is it for today!
Let's escape!
Thunder Flash!
He did it! As expected of Exkaiser!
Is this Heaven?
I'll fall!
Look over there!
It's Mr. Hikoboshi's car, Kouta!
He... He really came for me...
My... My Mr. Hikoboshi!
Alright!
I'll definitely become a fine woman
by this time next year,
and find Mr. Hikoboshi!
You haven't given up?
Let's go, Kouta!
I'm... I'm falling!
Wait for me, Mr. Hikoboshi!
S-Sister! Help me!
Exkaiser! Dash Max!
Someone help me!
Have you all gone home?
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
My sister will be on TV soon!
She said she's going to become an idol!
I think it's impossible for her.
But I'm so excited that I can go to the TV station together with her!
But then Geisters appeared once again!
Exkaiser!
Our idols are going to get captured!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Find the Idols!
Is there an alien in your home, too?