Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He's the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Buddha Rampage at the Hanamiyama
He's angry...
That's cause you stole unimportant things!
Don't blame me, I only did as Ptera told...
What was that? You fool, I only said the koinobori would make a good landmark.
How arrogant, you sure are one to talk as you ran away first!
What did you say?
You jerks!
So noisy!
... Is what lord Dino Geist said.
Please stop...
One day I'll make barbecue out of you...
What!
This is your fault for blabbering!
You idiot! Fool!
Why is it my fault?
Goddamn, everyone's looking down on me.
When things need to get done, I get them done properly!
Ah! What is that?
Everyone who's watching TV right now,
I'm currently in the full-bloomed
Buddha Park in the God Mountain.
Please look at this.
These perfectly blooming cherry blossoms are a beauty you can only witness rarely.
And in the middle of the God Mountain lies the nation's largest Buddha statue that guards the cherry blossoms.
This Buddha has been certified as an Important Cultural Property,
but furthermore, this colorful scenery of cherry blossoms can also be called our country's treasure.
A treasure?
Sheesh.
This planet sure loves the festival hype.
That's true, brother.
My capacity is over 120% today.
The other guys are so lucky.
Since they have nothing to do with this cherry blossom viewing thing.
Are you okay?
Somehow.
But why's there so much luggage,
if we're only looking at flowers?
Mama, we're not going to the beach so we don't need the parasol.
Oh, is that so?
Don't worry.
Although this car isn't that fast, it's sturdy.
Kouta-kun!
Sorry, I'm late!
It's alright, we just finished packing our things.
I, papa, mama, Kouta, Kotomi-chan and Mario...
Hard work for you, huh? Not only are you overweight, but also overloaded!
Yeah.
Did you say something?
Yeah, there's no way...
Spring breeze, swaying the cherry blossoms, as they dilute...
Everyone is so late! Alright, I'll do some exercises!
One and two, three and four, five and six, seven and eight...
Don't ruin the elegance!
Eh, the dinosaur? (kyouryuu)
I said elegance! (fuuryuu)
Mr. Tokuda! Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Oh, chief editor!
Huh, teacher?
Teacher has come to watch the cherry blossoms, too?
Eh? Teacher?
There's no mistake this time, since all those people have got together enthusiastically and are making a fuss.
That has to be the greatest treasure.
Well? It's as I said, right?
Seems so.
Let's go a bit closer.
♪ Even if money makes the world go round ♫
♪ There's something you can't buy with money ♫
♪ Even though I can't tell other people ♫
♪ You are my treasure ♫
Hey, you two are great!
Delicious!
It's like we're in a dream world.
A dream... world.
Kotomi-chan, let's eat our lunch boxes soon.
Thanks for inviting.
But I want to look at the falling cherry
blossoms a little longer.
I see.
Alright!
So beautiful!
It truly is wonderful.
Hoshikawa-kun!
Teacher.
If you do that, it'll be a pity for the finally blossomed cherry blossoms.
Yes...
If you want to see the cherry blossoms falling like snow, try going to the top of God Mountain.
And moreover, the Buddha statue is wonderful.
The Buddha statue was made in the Tenpyo era
in order to pray for everyone's happiness.
Mario, shall we go take a look too?
In other words, it was built in the same era as that Horyu-ji...
Huh?
Ah, a lift!
Let's take a ride on it, right?
But it doesn't seem to be for sightseeing...
Do you have business with our private lift?
Takumi-kun!
Private?
Yes, my father had it made, so we could use it during the yearly cherry blossom viewings.
Kotomi-chan, if you ride this, you can get to the Buddha easily.
Let me ride it, please!
Of course! I wouldn't refuse the request from a beauty.
If you please.
Takumi, w-what about me? Hey...
Well sorry, as you can see this is only for two people.
We'll send the lift back once we're at the top.
But in order to be healthy, I advise you to climb up.
Kouta-kun, we'll be waiting at the top.
Okay then, no way I'll lose to a lift.
I've seen many planets,
but it's my first time to be in such a beautiful place.
This planet is great, right Mario?
We're at the top, Kotomi-chan.
Let's hurry and go see the Buddha statue.
Wait a minute, Kouta-kun isn't here yet.
You should just ignore that guy!
Kouta-kun, come quickly!
Don't rush me...
How shameful to get tired from only that much steps.
Keep on going!
Things are getting fired up!
Fired up-...!
I-It turned into a monster robot...
This is it.
Huh?
Hey you, what are you doing? I'll arrest you...
Huh? Why do they fall out?
Dammit!
How about this one?
This too!
What the hell's up with this treasure?
Hey, don't daze around! Come and help.
That's it.
Hey, where are you going?
I'm going to take that!
Let's go then.
W-Wait... Let me rest a bit first...
Fine, rest all you want by yourself.
Kotomi-chan, let's get going.
W-What?!
It's the Geisters!
Kotomi-chan, hurry up!
Kotomi-chan!
Help me!
Exkaiser, Geisters appeared!
Kotomi-chan is in danger, come quickly!
I'll come immediately! Calm down, Kouta.
It looks a bit too heavy.
Guess I'll have this guy help us.
Kotomi-chan, run away quickly!
Exkaiser!
Change Exkaiser!
Are you okay, Kouta?
Yup! Thank you, Exkaiser, but...
Hurry up and carry that thing!
I won't let you do it!
Damn you Exkaiser...
I won't let you stand in our way!
There's enemies over there too!
Kill him! If we take this back, boss will be happy.
Flaming Nova!
Impact Flash!
Not good!
Your sin of destroying this planet's resting place is very heavy!
You'll be atoning for this greatly!
Darn...
Resign yourselves!
No way we'll be caught that easily.
And now, let's hear where your comrades are!
You think it'll go that smoothly?
What?
The Buddha statue stood up!
Papa...
This is a dream, right?
Seeing a standing and walking Buddha statue is really rare!
The wrath of Buddha! The wrath of Buddha has struck us humans!
Takumi-kun!
Someone help me!
Hey! Take these ropes off first.
Please do it gently.
I'll be paying you back greatly!
Help me!
Please help me!
Takumi-kun!
Takumi, hold on!
It's all over...
Hold on a little longer, I'm going to save you.
Finish him!
I-I'm saved...
I'm leaving him to you!
Exkaiser, behind you!
King Loader!
Form up!
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
Come on!
Just like that, squash him good!
Oh no!
Hey, what're you doing? It's your turn now!
Kaiser Sword!
Look out!
Not good, let's run away!
Void Cherry Blossom Blizzard!
Thunder Flash!
He did it!
So beautiful!
Calming down Buddha's anger,
it's the cherry blossom blizzard...
You're really good!
Sorry, we failed to bring back the big one.
But please take this bonus one...
This must be a warning to humanity!
Chief editor, we must repent for our sins!
And how will we repent them?
For starters, we'll make the park nice and clean!
But really, what a peaceful expression.
He must've been very tired, let's let him rest peacefully.
We must make the park clean, everyone together now!
Here we go! Clean up, clean up...
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
It's time for this year's baseball league season!
We've come to the baseball stadium to see the starting match.
But there's a difference in mine and Kotomi-chan's sense of cheering. It's kinda complicated!
Huh? It's shaking! It's the Geisters again!
I don't want the match to be cancelled now that we're here!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Great Shaking! At the Baseball Dome
Is there an alien in your home, too?