Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Papa Is a Non-Smoker
Tokuda!
Isn't the manuscript ready yet?
Yes, yes!
There's 10 mistakes in kanji!
Go back to elementary school and study again!
W-What the heck are you doing?
Chief editor, could you do something about this tobacco smoke?
Look! Our newspaper has written about it too!
"1 Cigarette Bothers 10 People"
"Mother who married a heavy smoker has a shorter lifespan."
Mama...
These are so heavy!
What does mama take her actual children for?
The 100 yen reward isn't nearly
enough for this! Sheesh!
Mario!
What's wrong, Mario?
Mario, stop that!
It's a cigarette!
Poor you! It was hot, right?
How long are you staring?
"The charming flavor.
The treasure of adults."
How is this a treasure!
It stings a little, but hang in there!
Don't wiggle so much!
You were in such a bad situation, Mario.
I don't understand adults!
What's so interesting about smoking?
I definitely won't smoke even when I become an adult!
Alright, Mario! It's all done!
Maybe I'll quit smoking too...?
Eh? Really?
Great idea!
H-Hey, I didn't decide yet...
As expected from our papa!
So great! Papa, you're great!
That's why I love you!
Is that so?
Well then, let's buy something with the money that we'll save!
Yay!
I'd like an one piece! There's one I really want...
I want a game software!
Then I'll buy a new pot.
This sure turned into a hassle...
Is this what they call a treasure of adults?
This is tobacco, there's no doubt about it!
They're leaves!
Alright, let's get to work right away.
Yeah!
"The tobacco field was completely ruined overnight."
Do you think this could be Geisters' doing?
Judging by the exit, it could be Geisters' doing...
Kouta, isn't tobacco those white sticks that are packed in a box?
The tobacco that's sold is made by drying leaves from the fields and then manufactured in a factory.
And what use do they have?
Nothing!
They're smoky, smelly and the fire is dangerous.
It's only bad for the health!
But isn't papa constantly having that white stick in his mouth and blowing smoke?
I don't really get it, but papa can't seem to relax if he hasn't got those.
Doesn't that mean, that people on Earth inhale
unhealthy smoke even though there's no need to?
That's right!
I can't understand...
People on Earth have such strange customs...
What do we do with this?
Don't ask me!
Maybe it's food?
I like vegetables!
Hey, don't eat by yourself!
I'll eat too!
So it's something different?
You idiots!
There's no use in stealing that stuff!
... Is what Lord Dino Geist said.
What does that mean?
That's just raw material.
This is what tobacco is!
»The charming flavor.«
»The treasure of adults.«
The treasure of adults, huh?
No smoking!
Chief chief chief editor!
What?
Well, there sure is work piled up!
Say your business! Your business!
Please look at this!
This article!
"The Educated People of the 21st Century Don't Rely on Cigarettes"?
Right? I'm an educated person and chief editor
is an educated person of the past!
If you have time to say stupid things to me,
go double-check an article or something!
Yes, yes...
Oh? Chief editor, you have a kanji wrong there!
What's the matter, Exkaiser?
Kouta, wasn't papa going to quit smoking?
That's right...
Please overlook this!
Have some compassion!
I'll buy you some meat chops, okay?
Do we have an understanding?
Then it's time for the desired cigarette...
Papa!
Um... Well...
Papa, come over here!
Ow ow ow... Don't pull! Just let me explain!
Maybe I did something unnecessary?
Papa, weren't you going to quit smoking?
So what's up with this? Well?
I'm so ashamed...
Sheesh!
I didn't think my papa would be this weak-willed!
I agree!
And it's not manly at all to do it secretly!
But you know... Cigarettes are absolutely necessary to me!
I don't care! It was you who suggested this!
But in reality my work isn't going well,
I make kanji mistakes,
and even Tokuda is making fun of me...
Don't sound like an elementary school kid!
It's an adult's job to put up with that, right?
How scary...
I bet you're thirsty after all that shouting.
Let's drink coffee.
Yes!
Thank you!
Oh? It's empty.
Didn't you two buy coffee?
Huh? We don't know about that...
We bought a lot of various things, so maybe we forgot that one.
Well, this is troublesome...
We're running out of both black and green tea, too...
See, see? You guys also feel unhappy when such things are missing, right?
Maybe it is similar to papa's cigarettes...
That's right! That's it!
Even if it's a bit bad for your health,
it's necessary for adults to have that something that will ease their fatigue!
"Adults, adults", that's your excuse...
Hello, this is at Hoshikawa's.
Ah, Mr. Tokuda!
Papa...
Hello, it's me.
What? Geisters appeared at the cigarette factory?
Be energetic today!
Cigarettes are tasty!
I found them! There's a lot of small boxes!
Over here they're in a way that's easy to carry!
Then it's this guy's turn. Go!
Alright, do it!
We'll take all of the treasures!
Exkaiser, it's terrible!
What's wrong, Kouta?
Geisters appeared at the cigarette factory!
What did you say?
I'm going to cover the event!
Papa, don't hurry so much! Here's your necktie!
Well then, I'm going.
Be careful!
The cigarettes... I won't let the cigarettes be taken!
Today's papa is kind of scary...
Alright, that warehouse is next!
What?
Damn Geisters!
We, Raker Brothers, are your opponents!
Raker Brothers are nothing!
So cheeky! Kill them!
Raker Hurricane!
Well, what's the matter?
Big brother!
You're doomed now!
Green Raker and Blue Raker are...!
Chief editor!
You're late, Tokuda! Take a photo quickly!
Whoa, this is amazing!
Papa!
I must get info! Let me through!
You can't go past here!
Change, Exkaiser!
Exkaiser!
Evil Geisters who disrupt the peace on Earth!
We, Kaisers, won't forgive any of your evil doings!
It's Exkaiser!
Show 'em!
Take it! Take a photo quickly!
Um... Where was the film again...
How dare you bother us!
Now's the only time you can talk big! Do it!
Form Up!
Left&Right Fusion, Ultra Raker!
Dragon Jet!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, Dragon Kaiser!
That's...
It's the stolen cigarettes!
Idiot, can't you find it?
Ultra Cannon Beam!
The cigarettes...!
Ultra Raker!
Cigarettes! Cigarettes!
How strange...
Um...
I found it!
I found it, chief editor!
Huh?
Ultra Chain Crusher!
We'll take back the cigarettes now!
D-Damn!
Should we escape?
What are you doing!
Dino Geist!
So you appeared, Dino Geist!
Lord Dino Geist...
We'll get the treasure back immediately!
I can't stand watching you!
Change, Dino Geist!
Dino Geist! We won't let you have these cigarettes!
I wonder about that...
Ah! They'll get defeated!
This Lord Dino Geist will be taking the treasure!
I won't let you!
Just stay down!
Cigarettes... Cigarettes... Cigarettes...
T-The cigarettes will be taken! Wait!
Papa!
As expected from the boss!
Alright, we should leave too!
This is bad!
We won't let you take them!
This is what they call a "shutter chance"!
I can't do it...
I can't put such a pitiful looking chief editor in the newspaper...
But I'll still take a photo of it!
Papa!
Change!
Wait!
Such persistent guys!
Then how about this?
Farewell!
Look out!
Papa!
Dragon Kaiser!
Ultra Raker!
Dragon Anchor!
I'm alright!
Dragon Archery!
Thunder Arrow!
Chief editor!
Papa!
Kouta, you were here too?
Papa, are you alright?
Yeah...
Chief editor! I succeeded today for sure!
Dragon Kaiser...
I'm so sorry...
The cigarettes got stolen by them...
Ah, well... I was quitting smoking anyway.
It's obviously better to not have such things that are bad for your health.
Disgusting!
People who smoke these must be out of their minds!
We can't even sell these to the space merchant.
Don't tell that to me!
They're worthless, huh...
Lord Dino Geist! Congratulations!
You finally managed to get one
of humans' treasures!
Papa, are you alright?
Today was a really tiresome day...
I'd love to smoke one at times like these...
Here you go, papa!
Welcome back home, papa!
You're tired, right?
Mama!
No... I'll just appreciate the thought!
Now I'll truly promise it!
Mama, for your sake I'll quit
smoking for sure this time!
Papa...
I love the way you are!
Sheesh...
I wonder how long it'll last this time...
Eh? This time?
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Do you know the Nazca Lines?
They're mysterious pictures that might have been drawn by aliens!
They're so big that they can only
be seen from the sky!
Perhaps Exkaiser's ancestors drew them...
Huh? A giant is walking!
How horrible! Is that legend going to become true?
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Secret of the Geoglyphs
Is there an alien in your home, too?