Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
The Oil Platform Trap
Hey, what's going on with this?
How can we make it usable?
If I knew that, I wouldn't have this much trouble...
Sheesh! The treasure is as good as nothing!
Show me it!
It's so hard...
Idiot! What's the use in chewing it!
I'm not an idiot!
Lend me that for a little!
H-Help me!
Where are you?
I'm here! Let me out quickly!
What are you doing?
Well, can't you tell by looking?
I can't get out!
You idiots!
How dare you play with the important treasure!
What did you say?
... Is what Lord Dino Geist said!
We're terribly sorry...
This idiot did such an unnecessary thing...
What did you say?
I'm saved...
Listen up!
This shield will become the proof of our powers.
The time has come to test our powers!
It's Lord Dino Geist's will...
We'll be taking this whole thing.
It's so warm!
But it's such an old model...
I'd like for you to call it antique.
It's still fully usable, right?
Can I really take this?
You're not one to be reserved.
Well then, can I have some oil for it too?
And also some mochi and mandarins...
Come on now, Tokuda...
But Mr. Tokuda, you sure were clumsy!
You dropped your newly bought
stove in the stairs!
I'm so ashamed...
But this sure is shiny although it's old.
It's because we bought it during our
honeymoon and didn't use it even once.
Weren't you cold?
Not at all!
I was together with the world's
warmest papa, after all!
It somehow got really hot in here...
I'll be watching TV!
Here's some good news.
At the Igsaret oil field, a new
reservoir has been found.
It's now very likely that there's more oil buried
than what had been estimated before.
You can get oil even in Japan?
Kouta, you didn't even know that?
They've been able to get a little since long ago.
But no matter how much there's oil,
it's still an important natural resource.
We'll be in trouble if it's used wastefully.
Trouble?
Oil isn't only used as a material
for gasoline or kerosene.
The synthetic fibres of Kouta's shirt
are also made out of oil.
I was wearing oil?
That's right!
And also plastic, vinyl..
And my most important camera's
film is also made from oil.
When you think about it, oil is
pretty involved in our lives.
Yeah! That's why it has to be treated valuably.
Yeah!
We just received these news.
An oil tanker has been attacked by Geisters at the Izu peninsula.
And then they stole it.
What did he say?
But don't worry!
Luckily the oil had just been unloaded and
all the passengers escaped safely.
I don't think that Geisters will withdraw so easily!
Well, it is them.
They'll surely target something even bigger next.
Kouta!
Do you have any idea?
Let's see...
If I think of a big place, then it
could be the oil factory...
Oh yeah!
Then there's the Igsaret oil field!
Oil factory and oil field, huh...
I got it!
I'll be on alert in any case.
I'm counting on you, Exkaiser!
Oil is an important natural resource for us!
This is Exkaiser!
Geisters are targeting oil!
Raker Brothers, go to the oil factory!
Sky Max,
Dash Max,
and Drill Max!
Please keep an eye on the Igsaret oil field!
Roger!
Damn Geisters!
I'm sure they'll attack the oil
platform after the tanker!
My genius-like deduction can't be mistaken!
A strong smell of oil...
It totally smells like a scoop, too!
Everything's still alright...
Um... What are you doing?
Well, it just smells like a scoop...
Scoop? Who are you?
Oh! Excuse me!
I'm Tokuda from Touto Newspaper!
Oh... You came to get information?
Yes! I came for the scoop and
some other business...
It's just like Lord Dino Geist said.
Stupid Kaisers! They came all carelessly...
What do you do with this?
It's fuel for my stove!
This sure helps!
This will last for some time.
This is crude oil, you know.
It can't be used in a stove unless it's refined.
You didn't even know that?
Now that you mention it, I did think that
it was unusually dark and thick!
Oh well!
I'll take it with me as a memory.
Did you really come here to get information?
It's not a lie!
The truth is...
Geisters are targeting this place.
Hey! Don't shout!
This is my exclusive scoop!
What are you saying!
If that's true, then we need to inform everyone!
You can't!
It's my exclusive scoop!
They appeared!
Geisters!
This base is ours now!
That won't happen!
Max Team has arrived!
So you've come!
It wasn't the time to escape!
Gotta get the scoop!
We, Max Team, won't forgive you for
trying to take over the oil platform!
Say what you want!
We were actually waiting for you!
What?
You bunch!
Take this!
Max Team, Form Up!
Triple Fusion, God Max!
Dino Geist!
We won't let you do as you wish!
We were waiting for that!
We did it!
God Max was...
It was a great success just like
Lord Dino Geist planned it.
That goes without saying!
Y-You bastards! Just what are you...
To think that a cosmic police got
captured... What a clumsy guy!
I'll do this!
Such cowardice!
Let me out of here!
Shut up!
If you want to get out, then do it yourself!
Looks like Trader has come!
Change, Trader at your service!
Well then, Sir Dino Geist.
Where are the goods?
It's this whole oil platform with the oil field!
5 billion!
5 billion?! That's too high!
Well, I shall check it first.
Hurry up!
If you're too slow, Exkaiser will come!
You mean that sharp-looking policeman?
Then I need to hurry.
I'm so busy... Really busy...
I see!
Well, this is a quite fine piece!
Alright! Then I'll be so generous and
give ya a nice 2 billion for it!
2 billion, you say?
Don't kid us!
Well, fine... Let's seal the deal with 3 billion!
Are you looking down on us!
Alright! I know!
I'm a striving space merchant, after all!
I'll go through fire and water for
this deal... Click and click...
3.25 billion! How about it?
5 billion!
You're so hard to do business with!
Where's that Trader going?
Change, Blue Raker!
Change, Green Raker!
Form Up!
Left&Right Fusion, Ultra Raker!
Trader has been arrested!
Arrested?! But I haven't done anything bad!
Forgive me! Forgive me please!
Damn you! You dare be so impudent!
Dino Geist!
Oil is mankind's important treasure!
I won't ever let villains like you have it!
We've been waiting for you, Exkaiser!
So you've appeared, Exkaiser.
Look at this!
Exkaiser!
God Max!
I'll make you have the same fate!
Take this!
Ultra Raker, you take this too!
We must save God Max somehow!
But at this rate, we can't do much...
Hey! Are you trying to kill me too?
Do a hostage exchange with me and that guy!
Could ya use your heads a little!
That's it! That's a good idea!
But that's...
What are you blabbering about!
Sir Dino Geist!
How about you exchange me and that God Max?
No way!
I won't allow that to happen!
Exkaiser! Don't care about me
and capture these guys!
God Max!
Sir Dino Geist!
Please save me quickly!
I don't care what happens to
a space merchant or two.
T-That's too ruthless!
Aren't we close friends here?
I beg you!
Save me in the name of our
negotiations, Sir Dino Geist!
Is that so?
If ya have that attitude,
then let me say a few words!
I won't do deals with you ever again!
Even if you get stuff around the space, I'm the only
one who puts up with an awful brat like you!
No matter what you say later, I won't listen to you!
Cry alone with your gaudy deals, you big idiot!
Shut up!
You're in the way!
Forgive me!
Ultra Raker!
It's no use hiding!
At this rate, Exkaiser will be defeated...
Something must be done...
What happened?
I see!
As long as that light doesn't show...
Alright!
Here it goes!
What are you doing!
I did it!
Damn you!
Now's the chance!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Super Giant Fusion, Great Exkaiser!
Dino Geist!
You'd better give back God Max!
Shut up!
Great Flasher!
Kaiser Sword!
Dino Blade!
Let's go!
Do your best, Exkaiser!
God Max!
Ultra Raker!
Things don't look too good now!
Leave it to me!
Hello, this is at Hoshikawa's...
What?
Alright, I got it!
Papa, has something happened?
Seems like Geisters are rampaging at the oil platform.
Although it seems like Exkaiser and his
comrades are fighting them...
I see...
Exkaiser has already gone there...
But...
What's wrong?
It'd be an awful thing if the base gets
destroyed and the crude oil flows out...
An awful thing?
Exkaiser, there's trouble!
What's wrong, Kouta?
I heard that the sea will die if the oil
platform is destroyed and the oil flows out!
The sea will die?
That's right!
It will become a sea of death,
that living things can't inhabit!
I got it, Kouta!
I won't let the sea be polluted!
I'm counting on you, Exkaiser!
Damn you!
Oh no!
It's dangerous! Hurry!
This is amazing!
Alright! Time for the last one!
Ah! Wait!
Alright!
H-H-Help me!
Grab onto me!
Damn you!
Great Bomber!
Thunder Crash!
Let's retreat!
We'll take God Max with us!
Wait!
Ultra Raker!
Our current priority is to turn
this base back to normal!
But God Max is...
I know...
But at this rate, this beautiful sea
will turn into a sea of death!
Got it...
Exkaiser, thank you!
I got my real scoop for the first time after
being a reporter for 7 patient years...
It sure was a long way...
Tokuda Osamu, 29 years old...
How could I be this stupid...
Hey, mister!
W-What?
Could ya take this off?
If ya help me, I'll give you
plenty in return...
Okay?
W-What's this guy?
Go away!
What did ya do that for!
Why must I go through all this!
Exkaiser...
For sure...
We'll save you for sure!
Just wait, God Max!
God Max was...?
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
God Max got captured...
Exkaiser is telling me to not worry
and go to my ski trip, but...
Shinkansen trains are getting attacked by Geisters one after another?
Ultra Raker! Be careful!
Dino Geist appeared at the Snow Festival's venue!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Decisive Battle at the Snow Country
2 episodes left until Geisters get arrested!