Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
The Targeted Bride
Lord Dino Geist is...
Angry...
How many times do you have to fail
till you've had enough?
... Is what Lord Dino Geist said.
Well, that's...
There's too much treasures on this planet
that we don't understand!
We, you say?
Don't label me together with you brainless!
What was that?
We will now start the press interview of the engagement of the third princess of Mim country, her Highness Miang
and the second prince of Goam country, his Highness Yahman.
What are they making a fuss about?
Maybe it's an amazing treasure...
That can't be counted on.
Nothing good has ever happened when those humans fuss.
Then don't watch!
What?
I can't see!
We're very honored to be able to hold our wedding ceremony in this beautiful country where we met.
Princess Miang, how are you feeling?
Are you feeling like you've received an irreplaceable treasure?
Yes...
An irreplaceable treasure?
I've heard that you first met in front of the church?
Yes!
In the Saint Picaresque church that was next to the university where we were studying abroad.
Princess, is his Highness your first love?
Yes...
So nice!
I wonder if anyone as wonderful as prince Yahman would ever appear before me?
I-It's alright!
If it's for Kotomi-chan, then surely!
Really?
It'll be me for sure...
Oh my, so it's alright then?
Y-Yes...
Thank goodness!
Then I'll contact her immediately and decide a day for the matchmaking!
Now I can wear the evening dress
I made the other day...
Dress?
Let's organize a grand wedding ceremony, okay?
Would you like to go on a gondola? Or would a helicopter be better?
U-Um...
Leave it to me! I want Mr. Tokuda to be happy.
W-Wedding...
Um... Well...
Well then, chief editor!
My humble self, Tokuda Osamu, shall accept your kind words and have a free afternoon!
Well, just go do your best...
Yes! If we're going to establish an engagement, please act as a matchmaker by all means!
A matchmaker, huh?
Maybe I'll have him come earlier in the mornings.
Here are the news.
I'm currently in front of the hotel where princess Miang is waiting for her escort car to come.
The princess will go from here to the Saint Picaresque church where prince Yahman is waiting.
The escort car has now arrived.
Treasure...
She sure is late.
Did I get the time wrong?
N-No way...
I'll go phone her.
I'm sure she'll come looking pretty.
Huh? They haven't even started yet.
I can't agree on your peeping!
Shh! Be quiet!
What's going on today?
Looks like mama is enjoying herself.
They're matchmaking!
Matchmaking?
It means that people who are hoping to get married
meet for the first time, talk about things and such.
Wedding?
Wedding means that a man and a woman live together and make babies...
Babies?
Mama and Mr. Tokuda will?
You're wrong! Mr. Tokuda's partner is elsewhere!
W-What?
Don't move from here!
Yeah...
There's an incident... I want to go...
Madam, I'm borrowing your car!
Huh, it's gone...
Kouta-kun!
Mr. Tokuda, what about the matchmaking?
A reporter will throw everything else away and run when there's an incident!
It'll be a good experience for my girlfriend if she wants to marry a reporter!
Well then, I'm going!
Girlfriend, huh? He hasn't even met her yet.
Mr. Tokuda!
He said there's a scoop.
How troublesome... Even though we should have an important talk.
I'll go call for him!
It's awful! Just now, princess Miang who was on her way to the wedding ceremony
got attacked by mysterious dinosaur robots!
The princess was?
Princess, look out!
She's not here.
Look better! She should be there!
What are you doing?
Sky Max!
Don't bother us!
What are you planning this time?
We have no time to be playing with you!
Wait!
Sky Max, wait!
Exkaiser, what are they targeting?
Seems like it's the princess.
Princess?
Amazing! This is a scoop!
Alright!
Ah! M-My camera...
A bride?
A-Are you alright?
Mr. Tokuda!
Huh? You're holding a wedding already?
Well, there's no way that's true.
Huh? This person...
It's the princess!
Princess?
Are you hurt?
H-Have no worries.
I'm a newspaper reporter called Tokuda.
There was a dinosaur! Help me! Please help me!
Y-Yes!
That woman!
Give her to me!
What did you say?
Give her to me!!
Change!
Stand up, Geister!
I'm your opponent!
Exkaiser!
That hurt, you know!
Drill Max!
Leave him to me!
Take the princess to a safe place!
Alright, I got it!
Mr. Tokuda! Help the princess in the car quickly!
W-Why is chief editor's car here?
Just do it quickly!
Okay! Come on then...
I won't let you escape!
Wait!
Let go!
I'm your opponent!
Come on then!
I have no business with you!
Now that we're this far...
Yeah! Princess, there's no need to worry anymore.
Yes...
But why did that dinosaur robot target the princess?
I don't know.
Anyway, we must return to the hotel
and show that she's safe.
Please wait!
There's no doubt that if we go back now, those dinosaurs will attack again!
Then, what should we do?
Please take me to the church
where Yahman is waiting.
No matter what the situation is,
if it's the two us, we can get married!
Please...
I understand!
Ow... It's alright! Leave it to me!
I, Tokuda Osamu, shall put my life on the line and deliver the princess to the church!
I'm so grateful!
And now finally, the luxurious bridal performance is starting!
Everyone, it's the arrival of the bride and groom!
Please welcome them with applauds!
Thank you! Thank you!
This wedding ceremony sure has exquisite production!
We're going to get eaten!
I'm not tasty at all!
Please pass over me!
This is not it...
W-We're saved...
What's up with you?!
We're soon there.
Yes...
Mr. Tokuda, can't you drive a bit more carefully?
Kouta-kun! The princess' love is more intense than my driving, you know!
How do they relate?
It smells!
What is it this time?
Don't you think it's strange?
Shouldn't there be more of a commotion since the princess was attacked?
But there's no one here...
It couldn't be...!
Yahman!
Oh no, you mustn't do that!
Princess Miang, you mustn't act so hastily!
It appeared again!
I have business with you!
Princess!
Wait!
What?
Change!
I have no business with you!
Mr. Tokuda, hurry!
Kouta-kun! An elementary school student shouldn't drive the car-...
It's not the time to be saying that!
You're so persistent...
Turbo Tornado!
Yahman!
Princess!
There's one here too!
Yahman...
I've been waiting for you!
If you don't want him to be killed, you'd better give me the irreplaceable treasure.
What did he say?
What's the irreplaceable treasure...?
I don't know...
Don't you care what happens to him?
Let go of Yahman! I'll take his place instead.
Princess Miang!
I can't let you be involved in such
a dangerous situation.
I shall be the hostage!
Mr. Tokuda!
What an idiot!
How's that! You'd better give me the treasure quickly!
Yahman!
What's that?
Exkaiser!
Geisters!
The treasure you're looking for is
something you'll never get!
What was that?
You'll have plenty of time to think
about what it is in jail!
Shut up!
Spike Cutter!
Yahman!
Is he alright?
Damn!
Look out!
Exkaiser!
Take the prince with you and get out of here quickly!
Let's go, Geisters!
Take this!
I won't let you escape!
Flaming Nova!
Give up!
It won't go that easy... Look!
What?
Princess!
I will pay you back plenty!
Do it!
Jet Boomerang!
Alright, finish him!
That's how far you go!
What?
Sky Max! Drill Max!
I'd prefer you wouldn't forget me!
Change, Dash Max!
Change, Drill Max!
Change, Sky Max!
Max Team has arrived!
Have you come to?
Where's the princess? Where's Miang?
She got captured by a monster...
Miang!
Don't do it! It's dangerous if you go out there now!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
Max Team, Form Up!
Triple Fusion, God Max!
Kaiser Blaster!
God Slugger!
Miang!
Yahman...
Alright, let's do a consecutive attack!
God Sonic Buster!
Do it now, King Exkaiser!
Not good! I guess this is it for today...
Kaiser Sword!
Thunder Flash!
I don't know what to say...
The best day... turned into this...
They can't hold the wedding ceremony anymore, huh...
Thank you, you two! But don't worry, even if there's no church
as long as there's the two us,
then we can hold the wedding.
That's right, I don't need anything else.
As long as I have Miang...
That's right! That's what weddings are!
It's a treasure, huh...
It really is the best treasure...
Next up is Mr. Tokuda, right?
Mama!
Mr. Tokuda, thank goodness I met you!
I'm sorry for leaving in the middle of the matchmaking. I'll come back immediately!
Well, the truth is...
She already has someone she loves,
so she'd like to decline without even meeting you...
Is that so?
It's alright!
I'll search for a new person quickly! Leave it to me!
Well, don't be so worried!
I'm satisfied with being a single who risks his life for his job!
Tokuda Osamu, 28 years and 11 months old...
For now on... I'll search for love and fight on!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Yay! It's a movie, a movie!
I'm performing in a super epic historical play together with Kotomi-chan!
They're not important parts though...
We'll put on kimonos and wigs, and then ready, start!
Huh? Director! Why do the Geisters appear?
This isn't a monster movie, right?!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Burning Movie Town
Is there an alien in your home, too?