Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Halloween Monster
Alright, all is in order.
What's that sound?
Hey! What are you doing, you sneaky thief?
Y-You're wearing such a strange costume...
What are you up to?
Hey!
What's the matter?
Huh?
T-This can't be!
The cargo has disappeared!
W-What's going on here?
Perhaps it's due to Halloween being close, but strange incidents are continuing.
Halloween related things such as pumpkins,
the tastes of autumn like chestnuts, persimmons, grapes and matsutake mushrooms
have disappeared from warehouses and markets.
The Tastes of Autumn Exhibition was planned to hold at the Makuma Fair,
but it's now unsure whether it'll be held.
Makuma Fair, huh...
Sister! Sister!
Everyone's outside already! Hurry up!
Sheesh, I'm telling you to hurry!
Sister!
I'm a witch who serves the boogeyman!
If you have business with me, call me by that!
It's done!
Sheesh, I was just getting in character...
What do you think? I did a good job on Mario's mask, right?
M-Mama, is that supposed to be a pumpkin man...?
I didn't find pumpkins anywhere, so I tried making it with a Sakurajima radish.
It has to be a pumpkin for Halloween...
Oh, is that so?
I think it suits him well, though.
Hello!
Huh? Kouta-kun's at it, too?
Hey, is there a costume party or something at the city today?
Don't be silly, it's Halloween! Halloween!
"H-Hello darling"?
Mr. Tokuda, don't you know Halloween?
You go from house to house while saying "Trick or treat!" and get sweets...
I see! That sounds nice!
Let me join y-...
You can't!
You can't do it unless you disguise yourself into something like a witch, an elf or a monster!
Why?
Eh? I-I wonder why...
Sheesh, you don't even know that much?
It was believed that witches and goblins
possess humans on the day of Halloween!
And so, humans dressed up as witches and goblins so they wouldn't be found.
Did you get it?
I see! So that's why you've dressed as a witch.
That's right!
This day is also the day when the demons of darkness have the most powers!
So that's what it is! Alright, I'll go put on a costume!
W-Wait!
Sheesh, you gotta listen till the end...
It's only children who get the sweets...
We're going!
Takumi, what's up with that outfit?
Can't you tell by looking?
It's Exkaiser! Don't I look cool?
But Exkaiser is an ally of justice!
All that matters is that the costume looks cool!
Don't make Exkaiser be one of the monsters!
I can't let an ally of justice be included
in the Halloween's holy ceremony!
Leave at once!
But that's not happening, so...
Now you don't look like Exkaiser.
Children!
In order to not disgrace the
name of boogeyman...
Let's do our best and go get sweets!
Yeah!
Help me!
T-Trick or treat!
Hey, Tarou! Stop that!
Trick or treat!
Yes, yes... Everyone in turn!
Well then, I'd like to start the party that celebrates the end of Halloween...
Not yet! Kotomi-chan hasn't arrived yet!
Sorry...
I got so excited by the tastes of autumn...
Well, I understand how you feel!
Since you people don't usually eat plenty of matsutake mushrooms...
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry that I'm late.
It took some time to prepare the costume...
Wow! Kotomi-chan, you look so cute!
You really do!
B-Beautiful...
I actually mimicked this doll.
Let's see...
It's a souvenir that my papa brought from Germany.
It's my greatest treasure!
Can I take a look at it?
Okay!
It's a really pretty doll...
It's an earthquake!
Trick or treat!
T-Treat!
T-The treats!
T-That was the true boogeyman!
He only took the treats and didn't break anything...
I-I'm sorry, Kotomi-chan!
Y-You're so cruel...
My treasure...!
Kotomi-chan!
What should I do?
You should pray for boogeyman.
I'm sure that boogeyman will appear
instantly and repair that doll!
Stop with the boogeyman nonsense!
It's all because that monster appeared-...
That's it!
If I ask Exkaiser, he might fix it...
I think he mentioned about going
to the Makuma Fair...
Alright!
Go!
And pray for boogeyman!
My party... My party is ruined!
Even my favorite matsutake mushrooms got stolen...!
That really was an awful thing to do...
Ms. Fuuko, where's Kouta-kun?
Kouta went to the Makuma Fair in order to get the doll fixed...
Makuma Fair?
This should be the place that
might get attacked next...
Kouta!
I think Kotomi-chan wouldn't be happy even
if the doll got fixed by my powers.
Wouldn't she just think it's strange?
That's...
Instead of doing that,
don't you think that Kotomi-chan would be happy
if you gave your best at something else?
You're right!
I'm sorry, Exkaiser!
I'm just glad you understand.
Kouta-kun!
Kotomi-chan!
Why...?
My doll doesn't matter anymore!
I'm sorry for earlier...
Rather than the doll, Kouta-kun...
Kouta-kun is more important...
Kotomi-chan!
I-I'm sorry, Kotomi-chan! I made you worried...
I was in the fault.
It's because I said such things to you...
It's not Kotomi-chan's fault!
Anyone would be angry if their treasure got broken...
No! I'm in the fault here!
Don't mind it anymore, Kouta-kun!
Oh yeah! Now that we're here, why don't we go take a look?
Tastes of Autumn Exhibition!
But they're doing it from tomorrow on...
It's the Halloween night, so I think they'll forgive us even if we go take a peek!
Let's go!
K-Kotomi-chan!
Sheesh...
There's so much delicious looking things!
That's true!
Huh? I have a feeling like I've
seen this somewhere...
It's that monster we saw at Takumi's house!
Kotomi-chan!
Kouta-kun!
I'm scared!
I don't know who you are,
but stealing the season's food that people look forward to...
It's unforgivable!
Exkaiser has arrived!
Exkaiser!
Spike Cutter!
What?
Kouta! Kouta!
Kotomi-chan, are you alright?
I'm alright!
I'm such a genius.
Since I thought of such a good idea.
Those stupid humans think that it's all done by a Halloween monster!
I-It's Geisters!
Looks like it wasn't the boogeyman!
Exkaiser! Exkaiser!
Kouta! I was worried!
It's terrible!
That monster was Geisters' sidekick!
What?
I got it!
I'll come there immediately!
Dragon Jet!
Wouldn't it be better to call for
the space merchant soon?
That's true... This place is so full already.
Let's do that.
Damn Geisters!
T-There's humans!
They're mixed in the treasure!
They found us!
Don't be bothered by a human or two!
No! If we leave them be,
the treasures might get broken!
That's not good!
Wait!
Stop that!
Are you trying to crush the treasures?
Ouch!
Go away!
Kouta-kun!
Kotomi-chan, escape quickly!
What an impolite guys to throw food at others!
Damn you!
T-The pumpkins are...!
Kotomi-chan, over here!
We must escape there!
Hey! Wait!
It's useless to hide there!
W-What should we do?
I-I'm scared!
Just a little more to go!
I-It's alright!
Exkaiser will... Exkaiser will surely come to help us!
Exkaiser?
Hey! Did you hear that?
He said that Exkaiser is coming to help them!
Don't be worried!
There's no way that he can find this place.
T-That's right...
Looks like I'm way too cautious!
He's here!
What's going on?
I won't forgive you for exploiting Halloween!
Ah! Exkaiser!
He really came!
You're such a persistent bastard!
Go!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, Dragon Kaiser!
Do it! Smash him good!
Kotomi-chan, hurry! We must escape now!
Yes...
It disappeared...
Where did it go?
Dragon Archery!
Thunder Arrow!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Super Giant Fusion, Great Exkaiser!
That's good!
Kill him!
Go!
Great Exkaiser will get defeated!
Alright, keep on going!
Finish him at once!
Hang in there!
Ms. Fuuko said that today's the day when the demons of darkness have the most powers!
If there's demons of darkness, then
there's surely a God of justice also!
God of justice, I beg you!
Please lend Exkaiser...
Please lend Exkaiser your powers!
Kaiser Sword!
This is bad!
Escape!
Thunder Crash!
He did it!
As expected from Great Exkaiser!
So we're saved now!
Yeah!
Kotomi-chan, this is embarrassing...
Oh, why?
Kotomi-chan, would you like to go
to school in my limousine?
I bet you don't want to walk with
Kouta-kun who broke your doll!
Your hands!
No way...
Thanks! But I want to walk with Kouta-kun today.
Well then! Let's go!
K-Kotomi-chan...
Great success!
Mr. Tokuda! Why are you dressed up like that?
It's obviously my Halloween costume!
It's rather nice, right?
Halloween was yesterday! Today is not Halloween.
No way!
It took me a whole day to finally
get this costume...
This is just my luck...
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Picture books, illustrations and how to cook food...
There's a huge variety of books, but I love comics the most!
When I'm reading a book with
only letters, I get so tired...
But since we got a homework to write a report,
I'll challenge myself to read a proper book!
Eh? Books disappeared from all around the city?
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Monster Library
Is there an alien in your home, too?