Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Great Discovery at the Ancient Ruins
Miss Himiko!
The country of Matsuro has come to attack us.
What did you say?
They've come in huge numbers.
At this rate, our military force can't hold them back.
No! No! No!
There's no way that the ancient people would say "our military force".
That part goes "our righteous army", okay?
Could you please act by the script?
And just as our class got invited to the memorial event of discovering the Kusunoki village ruins...
It won't be much of a play if our lead actor is so incapable!
S-Sorry...
But it's our first time to do a play...
It can't be helped if it doesn't go well.
That's true.
Don't aim for the perfect,
just do as much as you're capable of.
Teacher, what are you saying?
The Kusunoki village ruins are currently the hot topic in Japan as a great historic discovery!
TV stations, newspapers, and magazines!
They're all coming to cover the event!
Well, that could be so...
Our play will also be seen by people all around the country!
That's exactly why I put a lot of money into preparing the costumes and the set.
But if the most important actor is like this...
It'll all be in vain!
Kouta-kun!
W-What?
I absolutely won't forgive failure!
My future is depending on this play, so please do well.
Your future?
If this play is successful, I'm going to become a theatre director!
And I'll be a celebrity as fast as overnight!
Kouta-kun!
Yes!
You're the lead actor!
Please act elegantly, exotically and energetically
just like I've visioned!
I got it... I got it all right!
Well then, once again from the beginning!
If I'd known being an actor is this tough, I would've refused.
In the renowned Kusunoki village ruins,
there's been a new discovery of a golden coffin.
This coffin has tremendous value in both academic sense and industrial art.
It can most likely be counted as one of the greatest academic discoveries of this century.
It's the greatest treasure for mankind.
A treasure! A treasure!
... This coffin has tremendous value in both academic sense...
A golden coffin, huh? I've seen a similar thing on another program.
You mean those inside that strange triangle structure?
A strange triangle?
Time for new orders!
Go steal that golden coffin! is what lord Dino Geist said.
Good that we know it already.
All right, I'll go steal it in a flash!
Huh?
According to that program, this was surely the place...
W-What's this big hole?
Did they escape from the hole?
Nothing seems to be stolen.
Good thing that we had transported the coffin to the museum already.
Yeah...
A play using the ruins, huh?
Isn't that amazing!
Papa, let's make lunch boxes and go see it!
Sounds good.
No, it's okay if you don't come.
Oh? Why?
It's your debut stage, after all.
It's obvious I'll fail...
It's all good even if you fail.
Me and mama are happy with just
seeing you do your best.
Ancient ruins, huh?
It's kinda romantic.
Tsk, you only care about yourself...
Blossoming love and adventures with an ancient kingdom as the stage...
And the prince charming...
But when the crucial prince is you, well then...
I was saving that so I could eat it as last!
Thanks for the meal!
You knew well enough I like that one!
I won't forgive you!
Stop it, you two.
Fuuko, that's bad manners!
Wait!
No way!
Miss Himiko!
The country of Matsuro has come to attack us.
They've come in huge numbers.
At this rate, our righteous army can't hold them back.
I can't remember it at all!
Crisis of
Yamatai Kingdom
Grade 3 Class B
Exkaiser...
What's the matter, let alone in the middle of the night?
My class is doing a play at the Kusunoki village ruins, but...
Ah! Do you know the Kusunoki village ruins?
Yes, I've heard the news on the radio.
We're doing a play in those ruins, but it's just not going well...
When I try to say the lines, I get nervous!
If you're confident, it'll be all right.
Kids in the past probably didn't have these sort of troubles...
Instead of that, they most likely had other troubles.
I wonder if that's true...
Regardless from what era the people are, there's no difference in the fact that they lived to their best.
Those ruins are the proof of that.
Everyone's lived to their best, huh...
It's been over a billion years since the birth of universe.
Various planet civilizations have been born and perished.
But regardless of what planet the various living things are from, they've all lived to their best.
Kouta.
You're also one of their comrades.
Me too?
That's right.
You, your sister, papa, mama and Mario.
Kotomi-chan, Mr. Tokuda and Takumi-kun...
You all live in the history of the same universe,
you're comrades.
Comrades of universe...
If you do that play, then you'll surely feel like the people from that time are like friends right next to you.
And someday, I hope that you'll have big heart that'll help you become friends
with people from other eras, countries and planets.
Exkaiser!
I'll work my hardest!
Where the hell is your brain?
... Is what lord Dino Geist said.
You were way too clumsy to attack a wrong place!
Since it can't be helped, I'll go next.
You may explore the ruins freely until the time of the play.
Go on then!
Hey, Kouta-kun!
Did you learn all your lines?
Yup!
I think I'm getting kinda nervous...
Let's not take it too seriously!
I've decided to give it my all, even if I fail.
It's like you're a completely different person from yesterday.
No! No!
I'll never forgive you if you fail!
Kouta-kun!
My future is depending on this play!
Okay. I got it!
Hey! Kouta-kun!
You're here too, Mr. Tokuda?
Don't sound like it's surprising.
I'm going to be covering your play.
Eh, covering?
Just kidding!
I've actually come to cover the discovered golden coffin.
Thus, your play is only secondary.
It's fine being secondary,
but you must write an amazing article!
Leave it to me!
Ow...
Hey, could you let me in for just a little while?
No means no!
Inside the excavation site
Apart from workers
NO ENTRY
Please, just taking one picture is enough!
The coffin isn't open for public yet!
You should make an exception for me!
Don't cause trouble, sheesh!
Let's go check it out a little.
But if we're found out, we'll get scolded.
It'll be okay!
So that's the entrance, huh?
Which means that the treasure is in there.
We haven't proceeded at all for a while now...
Now, now...
The main thing is to be in time
for Kouta's play, right?
Papa, let's stop somewhere and take a little break.
Yes. Let's do that, mama.
Sigh, I bet there were no traffic jams like this in the ancient times...
This is kinda creepy...
The ancient people didn't seem to have a good taste.
So this is the golden coffin!
I-It's a monster!
Change, Ptera Geist!
Change, Armor Geist!
Now, let's get started!
Alright!
Dig up the treasure!
What's that?
It's the Geisters!
This is amazing! It's a scoop!
No film, install film.
Film! Where is film...
There's some!
It'll collapse!
Let's hide inside this!
Come over, Kotomi-chan!
Save us, Exkaiser!
Don't rush, it'll continue eventually.
Wasn't that our car that just left?
What on earth are you saying?
How could that happen if we're here?
You're right!
Blue Raker! Green Raker!
It's an emergency!
This is Blue Raker. Roger!
This is Green Raker. I'll rush to the scene immediately!
We're going to get buried alive in here!
If you cry, we'll lose air.
Hold your breath and wait.
I'm sure we'll be saved!
But there's such a monster rampaging outside!
That's...
Kouta-kun?
Don't worry. The monster will surely be defeated!
Look!
That's good! Get that golden coffin out just like that!
Hold it!
Change, Exkaiser!
Damn, he showed up again.
Geisters!
I won't forgive you for your selfish actions!
Shut up!
We won't let you bother us today!
Crush that guy to pieces!
Let's go steal the golden coffin now!
Alright!
Damn you!
They're here!
Change! Blue Raker!
Change! Green Raker!
Raker Brothers!
Blue Raker, Green Raker, take care of that guy!
I'll chase the Geisters!
Understood!
Form Up!
Left&Right Fusion, Ultra Raker!
Kouta-kun, it's painful...
Just hold on, rescue will come for sure!
We've finally got the treasure!
Lord Dino Geist will be so delighted about this.
Wait, Geisters!
Exkaiser!
You bastard!
You better remember this, Exkaiser!
It's here!
Exkaiser, you really came to help us!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
Kaiser Sword!
What!
Ultra Spider Net!
Thunder Flash!
Kusunoki Ruins Play
So the enemies are finally defeated?
Yes, Yamatai Kingdom has been protected.
And now the last lines!
Let us praise the blessings of God!
And let us pray that peace will continue forever!
Let us praise the Braves!
So that their names will go down in history!
There wasn't lines like that...
Thank you Braves, who have protected peace and the people's lives!
Kusunoki Ruins Play
Well what the heck! That kid was cool!
Thank you, Exkaiser!
I'm happy for you, Kouta.
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
I've decided to give a handmade cake as a birthday present to Kotomi-chan!
Isn't it a great idea?
But flour, which is the origin of cake, has disappeared!
We can't eat bread, udon, tempura and such anymore!
Exkaiser!
Take the flour back from Geisters!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
The Origin of Cake Is Gone!
Is there an alien in your home, too?