Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Great Adventure at the Pyramids
Lord Dino Geist!
Wasn't there supposed to be no treasure here...
No... There is something here...
It's not like I've forgotten that
mysterious incident on that day...
T-This is...
I'm sure that Kaisers' secret is hidden in here!
Lord Dino Gest!
T-That's...!
This is a map!
Let's go!
♪ How many nights to sleep before it's New Year's... ♫
♪ At New Year's we eat mochi... ♫
G-Geisters!
Lord Dino Geist.
Open that stone coffin.
Yes...
There's nothing here...
Where are you looking, Ptera?
T-This is...
Looks like they're ancient letters.
"We'll leave behind the power of justice
for the one who comes later."
What does that mean?
Looks like the cosmic policemen that once visited this planet left here an Life Energy Capture Device.
That's...
T-This is...
Put that in there.
Yes!
Life Energy Capture Device!
So if we have this, we can seal
away those Kaisers, right?
But this alone isn't enough.
We need an Emerald Stone!
Where is that?
Unbelievable that she won the first prize trip
to Egypt in a lottery...
Your family's mama is way too lucky!
Yes...
Yes, yes, yes...
Hello! This is at Hoshikawa's!
Chief editor!
Tokuda-kun, thanks for looking after the house.
Mama has something to talk to you about.
Madam has?
Mr. Tokuda, have you given Mario food properly?
Yes, please have no worries about that.
I've done a perfect job on it!
Hey! Mario!
Stop it!
That's my New Year's meal!
Oh! That's Mario's New Year's meal!
Let's stop here, Kotomi-chan.
I can't climb anymore...
Such an amazing place!
Yeah!
It's so high!
To think that humans built these
over 4000 years ago...
It's unbelievable!
Maybe aliens actually built them!
You're as unscientific as usual...
Takumi!
These pyramids were built by numerous slaves,
and it took over 20 years to complete them.
If Kouta had lived during that time, you would've
most likely been put to work as a slave.
Why are you even here?
I just thought I'd watch the first sunrise
of New Year from the pyramid.
Young sir!
There's a phone call from boss.
Papa, when will you come here?
Y-Yeah...
That's enough...
I don't even want to see you, papa!
Did something happen?
Young sir had made promises
to meet his father here...
But he suddenly had to go to Europe...
It's none of their business!
I don't even care about my papa!
Young sir!
The boss gave me this.
It's the New Year's gift from boss to you.
He told me to give it on New Year's Day, but...
New Year's gift?
I don't need such thing!
The top-notch men are always lonely.
Takumi-kun is trying to act tough,
but I'm sure he's actually lonely...
Papa, you idiot!
Kouta!
H-Hey, Exkaiser!
Has something happened?
Well...
There's just something I want
to ask from you, Exkaiser.
What is it?
My friend is feeling down because of his family,
but that friend doesn't want others
to be involved in that situation.
What do you think I should do at a time like this?
Your friend, huh...
Yeah.
If you're true friends,
then there's no need to be awkward and
just say out loud what you're thinking.
If we're true friends...?
There's trouble, Kouta-kun!
What's the matter?
Takumi-kun isn't in his room!
Exkaiser! Let's talk again later.
Geisters appeared again at the Kusunoki village's ancient tomb last night.
They dug up the ruins.
Damn Geisters!
What are they targeting this time?
So this is the cache of the Emerald Stone
that Lord Dino Geist mentioned...
Well then, time to get to work!
This is good!
Who on earth built such a big pyramid...
So he was over here!
He's going to retrieve the New Year's
gift that he threw away...
Even if he's acting tough,
Takumi really loves his father!
There it is!
Oh, it's just a sphinx...
Hey, brat!
This isn't a playground!
What a bother! Kill him!
Look out!
Kouta!
We must escape, Takumi!
Kouta-kun, over here!
Exkaiser!
Geister appeared at the pyramid!
Help us!
Got it! I'll come immediately!
Dragon Jet!
Kouta! I'm coming now!
I guess I should inform Lord
Dino Geist about this...
Hey!
If some other people come, smash them up!
Kotomi-chan, are you alright?
I'm fine...
Where's Takumi-kun?
I'm so scared... I'm so scared, papa!
Help! Spare my life!
Takumi!
Kouta!
Here!
It's all because you two came
that we fell to this place!
Such thing is rubbish!
Takumi-kun!
I didn't ask for you to come!
How cruel...
If you're true friends,
then there's no need to be awkward and
just say out loud what you're thinking.
This place is...?
Takumi!
Takumi-kun!
What is this place?
Maybe it's a king's room?
It might be that we found a new
room in this pyramid!
I wonder where Takumi-kun went...
What's wrong, Kouta-kun?
Takumi is so selfish that there's no helping him!
That's why his father won't even see him!
Kouta-kun!
I'm ashamed to be his friend...
Kouta!
There's no way...
There's no way you would
understand my feelings!!
Well, I don't!
There's no way I would understand
the feelings of someone
who easily throws away the New Year's gift
that his father especially got for him!
But I think I do understand your
feelings of retrieving this.
Kouta...
Everyone, we must hide!
It's this room!
There's no doubt that the
Emerald Stone is in this room.
T-The shield shone!
It's a proof that it's close.
T-That's...!
We've found the Emerald Stone!
Emerald Stone?
So if we have this, we can
imprison those guys, right?
That's right!
There's no need to fear Exkaiser anymore!
He can imprison Exkaiser with this...?
How terrible!
Takumi, lend me your strength!
We can't let Geisters have this Emerald Stone!
W-What do we do?
We must take it and run!
Takumi, Kotomi-chan... Let's lift it!
Hey! What are you doing!
Hurry!
Wait!
No way!
Hey! Let go!
This suit is made in Italy!
You should be the ones to let
go of the Emerald Stone!
No way we'll let go!
D-Dammit! They escaped!
Go after them!
Yes!
Why must I end up in a situation like this...
The exit is close! Hang in there, Takumi!
But...!
Stop complaining!
It's the exit!
Impact Flash!
Are you alright, everyone?
We're alright, Exkaiser!
Another hindrance appeared!
I won't let you have the pyramid's treasures!
The pyramid's treasures? Looks
like you don't know anything!
What?
Crush him!
Breast Beam!
Exkaiser! Behind you!
What!
Dragon Jet!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, Dragon Kaiser!
You should power up too!
What?
Dragon Anchor!
Rocket Cluster!
The Emerald Stone!
My New Year's gift!
This is...
Dino Geist!
As long as I have this, you bastards
won't be bothering us anymore!
That went well!
Dragon Kaiser!
This is an Life Energy Capture Device
that your ancestors left behind!
What?
Dragon Kaiser!
Get back the Emerald Stone!
Let's leave the rest to that guy and retreat!
Wait!
Dammit!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Super Giant Fusion, Great Exkaiser!
Great Tomahawk!
Kaiser Sword!
Thunder Crash!
This is yours, right?
Y-Yeah!
Thank you!
"Let's play catch together with this ball.
I'll try to make as much time as
possible for that. Regards, father."
Papa!
Geisters have appeared once again!
The sphinx has disappeared from Egypt!
S-Sphinx?
Well then, let's interview the eye-witnesses now.
Takumi-kun? Kotomi-chan?
Yay!
Papa! Thanks for the New Year's gift!
Um... What about the sphinx...
Tokuda, are you watching? It's a scoop!
Please give Mario food!
It's a bit early, but Happy New Year!
C-Chief editor, madam... and also Fuuko-chan!
Exkaiser fixed it!
Thank you, Exkaiser!
Geisters stole that weapon...
Even though it was something that Exkaiser's
ancestors had left behind on Earth...
Life Energy Capture Device, huh...
Seems like things will get troublesome...
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
The treasure that Exkaiser's ancestors had left
behind was taken away by Geisters!
I feel like something awful will happen...
Everyone of Kaisers, be careful!
Dino Geist is waiting in ambush at the oil platform!
How terrible! God Max is...!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
The Oil Platform Trap
3 episodes left until Geisters get arrested!