Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Be Careful of Dream Thieves
Help me!
Kotomi-chan!
Kouta-kun!
Kotomi-chan, leave this to me!
Form Up!
Change, Kouta!
I won't forgive you villainous Geisters!
Don't make me laugh!
Let go! Let go!
Everything's alright now, Kotomi-chan.
Thank you, Kouta-kun! You were very cool.
Huh?
Kouta, does your tooth hurt or something?
No, it's just that I forgot my dream
as soon as I woke up.
I feel like I saw a cool dream...
You can always see the dream again.
The same dream?
I see dreams of going on a date with a young man every day!
I can see the continue of it every
day like a serial drama,
going on dates with the young papa, that is!
It's really fun to sleep!
Since it's about Kouta, perhaps you saw a dream where you ate tons of yummy food.
That's a dream my sister would be happy about!
Um... This is this and...
You're counting calories again?
Even though you hate studying arithmetic...
Shut up!
It's a matter between life and death to me!
So it's about 700 calories...
If I ran to school at the speed of 20km/hr... Okay.
All of the calories will be consumed!
I'll be eating!
Thanks for the meal!
My teacher told us that if you eat your food fast,
you'll become as fat as a pig!
Pig?
That's not true!
A dream?
I feel like I saw a great dream,
but I can't remember it...
That's true.
I can remember scary dreams very well, but I don't remember nice dreams.
It's the same for you, too?
Yeah.
You two sure have free time.
I can't see dreams, even if I wanted to.
I'm so busy studying, that I only sleep three hours every day like Napoleon!
Napoleon?
Yeah!
The great man of France, Napoleon!
In other words, those who can't control their sleeping can't become remarkable!
Well, I bet you two couldn't do it!
It's a tough job to be a great man, huh?
But my mother said that if you don't sleep well, you won't grow up.
They do say that "sleeping kids grow up".
Well... That could be true too...
Mammalia, Perissodactyla, Tapiridae
"Malayan tapir"
Southeast Asia
What do you think about this treasure?
What's this?
It's humans' dreams.
Dreams?
It's dreams that humans like so much.
I stole it from an animal called tapir, that eats dreams.
Hey, don't touch it!
Well, this just proves that I'm much clever than that idiot Ptera.
After all, I've got my hands on dreams that are humans' treasure!
You're the idiot!
What?
It's only a legend that tapirs eat dreams!
In other words, that food you stole from a tapir has no value at all.
What's so funny?!
You're so cocky!
Then why don't you tell us what dreams are exactly?
Dreams are illusions that humans see while they're sleeping!
Illusions?
Yeah.
Then how do you steal those?
Well...
You idiots!
Dreams can't be stolen!
Don't waste your time on such unstealable things and go steal a proper treasure!
... Is what Lord Dino Geist said.
I can't even put up with you, if you're thinking of stealing something unstealable!
Goddamn it... Okay then!
Hey, what're you thinking of doing?
I can't stand it if something can't be stolen!
These "dreams" sound very interesting.
Yeah, if you see a good dream, you're happy all day.
But there's times when you see bad dreams...
Those times you still have a bad feeling even when you wake up.
But humans can't live if they don't sleep, right?
That's right, so since it's inevitable, I'd rather see a good dream...
You don't see dreams, Exkaiser?
I don't sleep so...
You don't get tired even if you don't sleep?
My body is built differently from humans, after all.
I see!
Kouta, wouldn't it be better for you to head to bed?
Yeah, I'll do that. Let's go, Mario.
Have nice dreams, Kouta.
Yup, good night!
What's going on in the middle of the night?
What's going on?
I don't understand any of this.
Even if I press the off switch, it doesn't shut.
W-What?
Even if you say that, miss!
Even if I press the off switch, it's still moving! It can't be helped!
We're troubled here too, cut us some slack!
Sheesh, even though they say sleep deprivation is the worst enemy of beauty!
Give it to me for a moment.
What the heck is that Tokuda doing?
Papa, don't get so angry and let's watch the TV.
It's very interesting!
Well, we can't sleep, so might as well.
»You think I don't know... You'll regret that!«
»Someone help me!«
Mama?
Oh my, it's so scary! What should we do!
I'm absolutely going to sleep!
What will you do?
Like this!
Then me too!
It doesn't help at all!
Just let me sleep already!
Sky Max!
What is it, Exkaiser?
The town is noisy even though it's midnight.
Could you investigate if there's anything suspicious?
Roger!
Is this Geisters' doings...?
Oh, the sound stopped!
I can finally sleep now.
Eh, it's already this time?
We're going!
I can't fall asleep now...
Look out!
Oh dear...
Oh crap!
Huh? I've arrived all of a sudden... Oh well.
If this continues, a great accident will happen at any minute.
Good morning!
Huh? Everyone's asleep?
Even the chief editor is sleeping
in the middle of the day!
Sheesh, you sure are slacking off!
Chief editor! Please wake up!
Oh, it's you Tokuda...
Don't wonder about me, what's going on?
You sure are energetic.
Where were you during the ruckus last night?
Ruckus? I was sleeping at my apartment through the whole night.
You were sleeping?
Yes! I was fast asleep and now I'm ready to work my hardest today, or something like that!
I got it, so go over there already.
Go over there! I'm sleepy!
Last night, all around Japan happened a strange occurrence where TVs, radios and factory machines
started functioning all by themselves.
That's why there are a lot of sleep deprived people.
And the city is very quiet, unlike usual.
But on the other hand, parking violations have increased and the police headquarters are...
Those humans, how dare they be sleeping in the middle of the day!
Aren't they supposed to sleep at night?
It's no use telling me about it...
Goddamn it! At this rate, I'll make them
learn their lesson real good!
I absolutely won't fall asleep!
I'm going to become a great man!
What is this?
Just what is this sound...?
Last night's incident and now these sound waves... It could really be...
Exkaiser!
Kouta!
Do something about this awful noise!
I'm sure this is Geisters' doings!
They're trying to stop us from getting sleep!
Understood. Hang on there a bit longer.
Blue Raker, Green Raker!
Please come quickly to the source
of these sound waves!
Sorry but I can't, Exkaiser!
The passengers are suffering from these sound waves so much, that I can't let them off!
Sorry, Exkaiser!
I'm in the same situation as my big brother!
I see.
Exkaiser!
Drill Max!
Don't go around forgetting me!
I'm heading towards the source
of the sound waves now!
I'm hurrying there too!
I'm counting on you, Drill Max, Sky Max!
Now those humans can't sleep at all!
Serves them right!
Hey, some energy waves are getting closer to us.
What?
Could these be those Kaisers?
So they really came!
Just watch! Today's the day I crush them!
What's this?
Just put it on your head!
I stole these from that Ptera bastard.
Alright, now it's your turn.
That's it!
Change, Exkaiser!
Where are you Geisters?
Don't hide around and show yourselves!
No thanks! Take this!
This is horrible!
My head... My head will burst!
Serves him right. Let's go!
Yeah!
Now this is interesting!
It's like hitting the bullseye every time!
Change!
Did we kill him?
Served him!
Lord Dino Geist will be so delighted about this.
That won't happen!
What!
I'm here too!
Sky Max!
It's your turn next!
This is way too easy!
So loud! My head will break!
Stop it!
You bastard, you're still alive?
As long as you villains exists,
I can't let myself be defeated!
You're so cheeky!
Damn!
Time to power up!
What!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
Kaiser Blaster!
Kaiser Sword!
Oh no!
We won't let you do as you wish!
That's right!
Do it now, King Exkaiser!
Alright...
Kaiser Flame!
This is bad, let's escape!
Thunder Flash!
It stopped...
How great!
Thank you, Exkaiser!
Kouta, now you can sleep without worries.
Yup!
I'm home!
Huh?
Even Mr. Tokuda is sleeping...
I'll sleep too.
Good night.
Today's Happenings
The mysterious radio waves that suddenly attacked the whole country have stopped.
The city has finally regained its silence.
Being able to sleep is truly a blessing.
Well then, everyone. Good night...
A great man will not sleep!
He won't sleep...
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
We're going to see a motorcar race soon!
Kotomi-chan's cousin and even Dash Max are participating in it!
It's really thrilling and so cool!
But during that race, Geisters appeared!
Hey, let me in the car!
No matter what obstacles appear, we must win!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Run! Supercar
Is there an alien in your home, too?