Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Protect the Computer
Are you certain?
Is it really true that the areal computer of Yuuhidai and Midorigaoka got stolen?
It's not a lie!
That's exactly why I came here to gather information.
But this place is still fine!
No! My strong intuition tells me that this Asahidai is also being targeted...!
A strong intuition, you say?
Just show me the computer room quickly...
So this is the areal computer that manages the Asahidai district...
There's nothing wrong here, right?
No! It smells like a scoop...
From over here...
W-What?
My intuition was really right!
Oh no! I forgot the camera again!
Huh? What's going on with this TV game?
You handled it too roughly that a glitch happened!
A glitch means a program failure, right?
That's right.
But this is an areal computer game that comes through the phone line.
There's no way that there would a program failure at the areal computer...
Well, that's true...
Help me!!
What the heck is going on with this? Mama, please do something!
Even if you tell me to do something...
Things are kind of... troublesome here too...
It's not even time for dinner yet...
Just what's going on?
Evil spirits!
Evil spirits have taken over this house!
Hello!
No, this is not the electrician.
But this is a good timing,
our electricity machines are acting strange too.
Could you request a checkup at our house too?
Oh, it got cut.
Mama, what's going on here?
T-They're evil spirits...
Mr. Tokuda!
I'm visiting!
So side effects really happened...
Side effects?
An evil spirit!
This city's areal computer got stolen!
Eh, really?
And right in front of my eyes!
This is my great scoop!
Since it's a scoop that only I know.
Asashidai's areal computer was stolen, so this makes it the 4th case.
Since an areal computer is a very important computer, that manages the living and safety of its district,
in the districts where it has been stolen
money is flying from the ATM machines,
the traffic lights have broken and other various troubles have occurred.
Too bad!
Seems like it isn't a scoop that only you know.
Looks like there's still something the TV channel doesn't know.
Something they don't know?
I... I...!
I saw the criminal!
T-The criminal?
The criminal is...
It's that dinosaur robot!
D-Dinosaur robot?!
Yeah!
I saw it with my own eyes, so I'm certain.
Madam, I'll be borrowing the chief editor's room.
This is terrible!
Kouta-kun, where are you going?
I just thought I'd go see the state of the city...
That's true! Doing that seems more interesting.
I'm going too!
Kouta-kun?
Weren't we going to check out the city?
Oh, yeah!
I forgot something...
Go on ahead!
Well then, we'll wait for you.
Just go on ahead!
Kotomi-chan, let's go.
Sheesh...
Mr. Tokuda.
I brought you some tea.
Oh, thank you!
Huh? This was connected to the areal computer too?
If it's come to this...!
There was no word processors back in the day!
Newspaper reporters wrote with a pen like this!
Mr. Tokuda, you're wonderful!
You remind me of papa in the old days.
That's an honor.
Give it your all!
Oh? It doesn't open...
I was thinking that the city seemed strange... So it's Geisters' doings again!
That's right!
I knew that computers are useful machines to humans,
so how dare those Geisters target them!
Kouta! Kouta!
Ah, it's my sister!
You were in here? I was looking for you!
W-What's the matter?
Mr. Tokuda and mama are in trouble!
Mr. Tokuda and mama...?
They both got locked in?
The door's safety lock seems
to have locked on by itself!
Are you two okay?
We're alright, Kouta-kun. But moreover, I have a request for you!
Oh, what could this be?
A request?
Please deliver this to chief editor.
It's the manuscript.
A manuscript is something that's more important than life to a newspaper reporter!
More important than life?
Kouta-kun, please!
Deliver it quickly to chief editor!
I got it! I'll definitely deliver it, Mr. Tokuda!
I wonder if Kouta-kun will be alright...
Mr. Tokuda, if you're so restless
you'll turn into a bear.
Look, even the TV is telling us to calm down.
Everyone in the districts who have been affected by the areal computer theft case
please feel at ease!
This is the Big Mother computer
that's located underground of Shintoshin.
In the replacement of the stolen areal computers,
this giant computer will take care
of the city functions.
The connecting of the cables are in full swing.
See what happens, damn humans!
Serves them right!
The areal computers sure are high in value.
Precious treasure!
Hey, Ptera! You've been silent for a while now.
Do you got a problem?
Are you being sulky since I got ahead of you?
You bastard!
What? You wanna fight?!
Be quiet! Be quiet!
Come on!
How long are you going to be excited over stealing little computers?
What did you say?
Lord Dino Geist's target is...
The Big Mother computer!
Exactly!
Go steal it!
Ptera, how did you know that?
My brain is built differently from yours. Let's go!
Such a cheeky bastard!
Built differently...
You've no right to say that to me!
What's that Big-something?
Isn't it food?
Thank you, Exkaiser!
I want to do what I can for the
important manuscript.
I feel at ease since Exkaiser is escorting me!
However, Kouta... That isn't my only object for going downtown.
This actually caught my attention.
If Geisters also saw this TV broadcast, "then perhaps...!" is what I felt.
Do you mean that Geisters will attack the Big Mother computer?
It's very likely that it will happen.
If Big Mother computer gets stolen,
then Japan will truly be in absolute chaos!
Seems like humans depend too much on computers.
If you depend too much on useful things,
you might get in trouble when things get serious.
Yeah...
Train is coming
W-What was that?
Evoke, the check is ok!
A-An earthquake!
Now let's get to work!
The second block's floodgates are still closed!
No good! The computer controls don't work!
This is terrible!
At this rate, many water pipes will rupture!
Water leakage?
That's cold!
What's going on?
That's an amazing amount of water!
Damn Geisters, I won't let you do as you please!
The computer broke down, you say!
The speed doesn't fall! The steering isn't working!
Just what is going on?!
We can't go this way!
We'll crash!
What? This is bad!
That was close... What is going on
with the computer controls?
You better be careful.
If it breaks, it's good for nothing.
We know already!
Huh? What is this?
Oh no! The boiler's controls don't work!
At this rate, it'll explode!
There's explosions again!
Exkaiser!
Seems like there's something wrong with the areal computer.
Could you investigate it urgently?
I got it, Blue Raker!
I'll go immediately!
We'll crash!
Let's part our ways here, Kouta.
You have the important job of delivering Mr. Tokuda's manuscript, right?
I must deliver this to papa's
newspaper company!
Well then, be careful.
You too, Exkaiser!
Now this is ours!
W-What's wrong?
I thought I heard something...
What about it?
It couldn't be...!
This sound...
Change, Exkaiser!
He appeared!
Exkaiser, so you came to bother us again!
As long as you thugs do evil things,
Kaisers will definitely appear!
T-This is bad!
Don't fluster!
There's more of us here!
That's right!
All we have to do is defeat him!
I wonder if you can?
What!
Change, Dash Max!
Change, Drill Max!
Change, Sky Max!
Max Team has arrived!
Now that we're here...
We won't let you do as you please!
Prepare yourselves!
W-What do we do?
Time for plan B!
Wait!
What's wrong, Kouta?
It's terrible, Exkaiser!
Since the computer controls don't work,
the subway is going crazy!
What?
If I don't fix this computer, awful things will happen!
Where is it?
Where is the circuit that controls the subway?
Is it this?
Alright, I got it!
We'll crash!
They stopped...
Kouta, be at ease! The subway is all right now!
Really? Thank god!
Ah, I can't just stay here, I must hurry!
Go! Steal that Big Mother computer!
I-It's the Geisters!
They're coming!
This is bad!
How dare they!
We must stop that thing!
Alright!
Max Team, Form Up!
Triple Fusion, God Max!
Exkaiser, it's terrible! They turned
the bridge into a robot!
What did you say?
Please come aid us quickly!
I'm close at getting this fixed.
Please hold on somehow!
I won't let you go!
G-God Max!
I-I'll fall!
What on earth is this?
Well, this is great!
Let's cook him nice and slow!
I can't move!
Alright, I'm done!
God Max!
Jet Boomerang!
Oh no, let's escape!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
Kaiser Blaster!
Save me!
Kouta!
Now, hurry!
I'm about to fall!
God Max, please help Kouta!
Roger!
Damn you!
It's all good now!
Kaiser Sword!
Thunder Flash!
Computers are useful,
but when one thing goes wrong,
things take an awful turn.
Yeah, I agree.
Kouta, how come you're here?
Mr. Tokuda gave me an article about this scoop!
A scoop?
Seems like he wrote about who the true criminal was in this incident!
Is that true?
Let's see now...
"Dear mother,
I enjoyed very much the sweet chestnuts you send me the other day.
Mother should be careful too to not catch a cold. Please take care of yourself."
M-Madam, please don't let go!
Yes, yes.
Oh, seems like the lock opened.
M-Madam! M-Madaaam!
Mr. Tokuda, did it go well?
Oh, what could this envelope be?
That's an article I wrote about the scoop...
Eh?! Does that mean that I accidentally gave Kouta-kun the letter I meant for my mother...
I'll get scolded by chief editor again...
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
When you're sleepy in the morning
and getting waked up,
have you ever been like "Damn that clock!"?
Then suddenly, people around the world really lost the way to tell time!
TV doesn't know when to show what
and the trains are a chaos, too!
Papa is taking a long time to come home,
and no one knows when to eat school lunch!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Time Is a Mess
Is there an alien in your home, too?