Brave         Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Takumi Likes School?!
Aseda University
In fact, the so-called island country's
democratization destroyed the Marxism-Leninism...
I'll be taking the treasure!
Touto University
I'll be taking this red gate!
Treasure! Treasure!
What's wrong, Fuuko? Aren't you going to eat?
When I think about tomorrow's test
I don't feel like eating at all...
Then I'll give it to Mario.
Sister!
Wouldn't it be better if there
were tests every day?
Why?
Because then you could diet every day!
Elementary school kids have it so easy!
I have tests too!
The value of tests is different in
elementary school and middle school!
Could an earthquake happen so that
my school would collapse...
Oh my...
Today dinosaur robots Geisters
have attacked various schools.
The statue of Aseda University and the red
gate of Touto University were stolen.
They are the schools' symbols.
Also elementary schools' swings
and iron bars have been stolen.
Geisters did that?
It's me.
Yeah, I just heard! Please make a feature
article about it immediately.
That's it!
My school just needs to be stolen by Geisters!
Then I won't have tests anymore!
But fortunately the students and teachers were safe.
All of the schools will be holding
their classes as usual tomorrow.
Hey! How come they'll be held as usual?
Didn't we steal the treasures called school?
I-I don't know...
Idiots!
What?
The things you stole are only garbage!
Seems like you don't know
why schools are treasures.
What did you say?
Do you know then?
I'll tell you!
As well as how to steal the treasures!
Geisters attacked schools?
That's right!
Damn Geisters!
How dare they attack schools that
are important for children!
My sister is saying that it'd be better
for her school to collapse, though.
Would be better to collapse?
Because of tests!
She's saying that because there's tests!
You're talking about exams, right?
Yeah! If only there weren't tests,
school would be more interesting...
I see.
Exams do compare one's skills to others.
Hey! Have you had tests too, Exkaiser?
Well, yeah...
Dear Geisters! Please!
Steal my school! Please!
It's not like I don't understand the feeling...
What's the matter?
No, it's nothing.
Kouta.
It's true that exams aren't fun.
But a certain amount of studying is needed
in order to become an adult.
And school is also an important place where
you can socialize with your friends, right?
Yeah!
If there wasn't school, I probably wouldn't have
become friends with Kotomi-chan and the others.
In any case, even if the school gets attacked, we'll protect it for sure.
Yeah! I'm counting on you, Exkaiser!
I fell asleep without studying at all!
My school...
It's still there...
I'm going!
They always appear when unneeded, but then
they don't attack the crucial place...
Geisters, you idiots!
Young sir, wouldn't it be better
to be absent from school?
No way! I'll absolutely go to school!
But young sir... Don't you always
say that school is boring?
I'm going!
Stop the car!
Hey! Good morning!
Takumi... Why are you dressed like that?
The truth is that I caught a cold.
Although with my grades, I could stay
absent from school for many days...
The classrooms are small, the lunch is bad...
There's no beautiful teachers...
I don't even want to attend such a school...
But I thought that everyone would
miss me if I were to be absent.
W-What's funny, Kotomi-chan?
Takumi-kun, you look like a tanuki!
He really does!
♪ Over a million of them shine with a blue light. ♫
♪ The shards of love... ♫
Pass! Pass!
Everyone is so cruel... Why'd they make
me the keeper when I have a cold...
I get unnecessarily cold when I
just have to stand still...
Takumi, here it goes!
Nice, keeper!
Good job, Takumi!
N-No big deal...
So bad...
Why must I eat a tasteless lunch like this?
Can't they serve proper French and Italian cuisines
once in a while like the dinner at my house?
Takumi, you can't really tell the taste
because you have a cold.
That's not it!
It's all because I'm a gourmet!
Then just don't eat it.
What are you saying!
I've caught a cold, you know!
It will only get worse if I don't get nutrition!
Then eat it.
Safe!
Well then, everyone!
Solve this problem.
Why do I have to do calculations like this?
I'd know the answer in a second with
my family's latest computer...
G-Gei...
That's cold! What is this?
Is this the treasure?
No doubt about it!
Just like Ptera said, there's a lot of kids inside!
Geisters, you say?
I-I certainly saw a Geister looking here!
There's nothing there.
Advance like that till the hideout!
There really are Geisters!
Exkaiser!
What did you say?
I got it! I'll come immediately!
Max Team! Depart at once!
Kouta's school got attacked by Geisters!
Got it!
I'll go there immediately!
Roger!
Asahidai Middle School
I can't do it!
Ah! That is...!
Kouta's school...
Why didn't you steal our school?
Geisters, you idiots!
How could I sleep in late for 5 hours...
This is a lifetime blunder for Tokuda Osamu!
That was chief editor's car...
Lucky!
If chief editor is out of the office, then I'll have
no worries about getting scolded for now!
Let's drive slowly and safely!
Hello, this is the Social Affairs.
What? Asahidai elementary school
is walking around in the city?
Ouch!
Huh? Chief editor!
You idiot! How come you're so late?
Anyway, come!
But why...?
I'm sure I passed by chief editor's car earlier...
So how can this be?
Dash Max, there's students inside the school.
We can't attack thoughtlessly!
I know already!
Anyway, saving the children comes first, right?
There it is!
Change, Exkaiser!
Change, Dash Max!
Exkaiser!
Everyone, it's alright now!
We will protect you!
Do your best, Exkaiser!
Exkaiser!
So you've shown yourselves, Geisters!
It's our important treasure!
No way you can have it!
Change, Armor Geist!
Change, Thunder Geist!
Advance now! Hurry to the hideout!
Exkaiser!
Spike Cutter!
Let's retreat for now!
Dash Max, let's chase after the school!
Yeah!
What?
You idiots! You fell for it!
Damn...
There it is!
I'll land on the rooftop!
I won't let you bother us!
Drill Max!
Sorry! I'm late!
Leave this place to me and Drill Max!
Please!
Dragon Jet!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, Dragon Kaiser!
Dragon Kaiser!
I won't let you escape this time!
We'll collide with Dragon Kaiser!
We stopped...
Kouta!
While I'm stopping the school...
Tell everyone to escape to the next
building from the rooftop!
Okay!
I got it!
Everyone! Now's our chance to jump
to the next building from the rooftop!
That's right! Everyone, hurry!
D-Don't leave me behind!
Kotomi-chan!
Thank you, Kouta-kun!
Seems like everyone is safe.
Thank goodness!
Where's Takumi-kun?
Now that you mention it...
I'm sure he's still inside!
Kouta-kun!
I'll bring him here in a flash!
Kouta-kun...
Kouta... Aren't you done yet?
Looks like you're so busy that you
can't fight against me, Exkaiser.
Don't hurt the children!
Unlike that idiot Ptera, I have no
business with the brats!
The one I have business with is you!
I'll repay all my debt a hundredfold to you!
Someone help me!
Science Lab
Fire extinguisher
Staff Room
It's the test from before...
I'll obviously have a perfect mark!
Oh no... I made a mistake...
Much better!
It wasn't the time to be doing this!
Takumi!
Where are you?
Someone help me! I'm still here!
He's in the broadcasting room!
Broadcasting Room
Is there anyone here?
God, Buddha, Christ... Save me quickly!
Takumi!
Thank god! I was worried that no one would come...
No... It's not like I was scared...
I just thought that if there's someone
else here, I could help them...
Anyway, let's escape quickly!
Serves you just right, Exkaiser!
Exkaiser will get defeated!
Damn you for getting so big!
What will you do?
Help me out!
Yeah!
Just take this!
Firing!
W-What is this?
It worked!
Now's the chance!
Dragon Shooter!
This is bad! I leave the rest to you!
T-This is amazing!
Chief editor, this is a scoop!
You idiot!
Lifesaving comes before a scoop!
Kouta, please be safe.
The newspaper company's helicopter!
It's Kouta-kun!
R-Really?
He's waving his hands on the rooftop!
The ladder! Lower the ladder!
Alright!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Super Giant Fusion, Great Exkaiser!
Kaiser Sword!
Wait!
Don't break it!
I like school!
Takumi...
But...
Exkaiser!
It's coming this way!
Kouta!
Help us!
Look out!
Oh no!
The school...
I'm sorry.
I broke everyone's important school...
Thank you! You're amazing!
The building doesn't matter.
You did protect the important lives
of the children, after all!
The school is gone...
What should I do from tomorrow on?
You liked school that much?
I attended school every day
because I could see everyone...
And still...
Even if school is gone, we're friends!
Friends?
That's right! We're all friends!
I see!
That's right! Even if school is gone, we're all friends!
No! Even if the building is gone, school isn't gone!
Sheesh, how can this be...
I was feeling relieved that school is gone,
but now we have to study here...
If it starts raining, we're drenched.
Seems like it's worse than yesterday.
He should rest even for one day...
What was that!
I'm coming here because I thought that
everyone would miss me if I'd be gone.
Would you all prefer for me to be absent?
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
A shining tree and a big cake!
Christmas parties sure are fun!
But papa will come late due to work...
Mama said that she'll dress up
as Santa instead, but...
It just doesn't seem right!
Santa's statue is attacking us while
saying "Merry Christmas"!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
There's a Lot of Santas
Is there an alien in your home, too?