Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Our Olympics
The torch has returned to Japan once again!
And the competitors are also
arriving one after another.
There's no doubt, that the most notable athlete in this year's Olympics
is Florence Joyner!
This isn't interesting.
Let's change the channel.
Shut up!
She's expected to run under 10 seconds.
The arena, that will welcome all these amazing athletes, has been successfully completed.
It's now waiting for the Olympic opening ceremony in 2 weeks.
Here's orders from Lord Dino Geist!
Go steal the Olympics!
Olympics!
Asahidai Elementary School
Great Sports Day
Do your best!
All the competitors that participate in the 100m run, gather at the starting line.
I'm sorry for you all, but I'll be
getting the first place prize!
Since I think that your legs won't be able to beat my special shoes!
What are those?
Takumi!
That's not fair...
Who are you?
It's sad that there's a student like you in this school.
Do you want to win so badly that you'll do that?
I don't know who you are, but a person like you has no rights to say such things to me...
Um, are you perhaps Ms. Joyner?
That's right. Good job at recognizing me.
Um, I'm your fan! Can we shake hands?
Okay.
How did you become able to run so fast?
It's because I loved running.
You're able to do anything if you give it your all.
You too can run fast without relying on those shoes, if you give it your all.
T-That's right!
I was also thinking that!
But it's not like you can become fast immediately, so didn't you start disliking it at times?
Well, there has been times like that so far.
But one teacher told me that if I love it, then I mustn't ever stop.
That's a nice teacher!
It's a teacher from this school.
I went to school here for 2 years
due to my father's work.
This school?
Teacher Mushano Kouji!
It's been a long time!
I'm happy that you came to visit us.
But I'd prefer that you wouldn't bother our sports day!
I'm sorry...
Come on! It's time for the 100m run!
But my shoes are...
Can't you just run barefoot?
Eh? B-Barefoot?
Alright! I'll do a good luck spell
so you can run barefoot.
Alright, now you can run.
Ready!
Yay! I'm 1st place!
I-I'm 3rd place...
See? You can do it if you give it your all, right?
Y-Yes! Um, thank you very much!
Oh yeah, I heard that the torch runners come from this school?
It's me!
Olympics began in order for people around the world to become friends through sports!
You know it very well, Kouta.
Ms. Joyner told us!
And she also said that being a torch runner is a very important duty
where you carry the symbol of Olympics, so we must do it well!
Then you need to do your best!
Yeah!
Everyone in the country!
The day for the long-awaited opening ceremony of Olympics is here!
The torch that's been relayed through various places is finally heading towards the main stadium.
The current torch runners are students from Asahidai elementary school!
Kouta-kun, it suits you well!
I-Is that so?
Hi!
Ms. Joyner!
Are you the final runner of Asahidai elementary school?
Yes!
I'm the one who'll receive your torch.
Nice to work with you!
Y-Yes!
See you!
Yes!
Alright! I'll do my best!
Everyone is fascinated by my coolness!
W-What?
Olympics!
Geister!
This is a scoop!
Give me that!
You can't give it!
Kouta-kun...
Wait!
W-What on earth?
Exkaiser!
Geister has appeared!
He's targeting the torch!
What did you say?
Give me that!
Oh no!
Come on, give it to me!
Torch is the symbol of Olympics! I won't give it!
Kouta!
Give me the torch quickly!
Yes!
There goes!
Ms. Joyner!
So fast...
I won't let you escape!
Spike Cutter!
W-Who's there?
Change!
Thunder Geist!
I can't let you have the important torch!
Shut up!
Breast Beam!
Look out!
Take this!
Hurry! Now's your chance!
Yes!
The treasure ran away!
Flaming Nova!
The athletes are entering!
Sport loving athletes around the world have crossed the boundary and gathered at this Olympic stadium!
They sure are fired up.
I was so close!
Did you think that that thing was the Olympics?
That's the Olympics!
Idiot! No way our boss would make us
steal such a puny thing!
You aren't mistaken! That's truly what Olympics is.
Yeah!
Those guys managed to protect the Olympics,
so they're feeling assured.
It's easy to steal it now that they've lowered their guards. Let's go!
That thing really was the Olympics?
Damn! I can't let him get ahead of me!
Don't kid me!
That's mine!
Idiots! That thing obviously isn't the Olympics.
While those guys are dealing with Kaisers,
I'll take the real Olympics.
I got Ms. Joyner to sign it!
That's so nice!
It's finally the entry of Florence Joyner!
Can she really run under 10 seconds?
Ms. Joyner! Do your best!
Do your best, Joyner! Do your best, Joyner!
It's Geisters!
That's it!
Let's take it!
Everyone, calm down! Please calm down!
I must inform Exkaiser quickly!
Kouta!
I must do something until Exkaiser arrives!
I got it!
Olympics!
It's mine!
No, mine!
Hey, Geisters!
Look! Here is the real torch!
Olympics!
I'll be fine if I can take refuge in that park!
Damn!
Hey, Thunder! Search for him!
Hmm...
There he is!
Hand that over!
Help me!
Change, Blue Raker!
Change, Green Raker!
Raker Brothers!
Blue Raker! Green Raker!
Those who try to steal the important
symbol of Olympics...
We won't forgive them!
Shut up! Let's kill them!
Damn! So you're over there!
Now's the time when I'll take the real Olympics.
Transform!
Carry that arena!
Main stadium is...!
Bind Crush!
Give up, Geisters!
What?
Blue Raker! Green Raker!
If the arena is taken, Olympics can't be held!
What did you say?
I'll be taking the Olympics!
We won't let you!
Alright! Keep carrying it!
Hey! Don't run away!
Is he going to abandon us?
Come back!
Over here!
Now's the time, little brother.
Okay, big brother!
Form Up!
Left&Right Fusion, Ultra Raker!
Ultra Cannon Beam!
Oh no!
Ultra Chain Crusher!
Damn! Full powers then!
Ultra Raker!
Exkaiser!
What?
The important treasure is...! Dammit!
Let's leave the rest to those and get out of here!
What?
Dragon Jet!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, Dragon Kaiser!
I'll try to stop its movements! Use that chance!
Alright, I got it!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Super Giant Fusion, Great Exkaiser!
Kaiser Sword!
Ultra Cannon Beam!
Alright!
Do it now, Exkaiser!
Thunder Crash!
Damn! Next time for sure... Remember that!
Even though I aimed for a world record...
If there's no arena, it's all over...
That's not true!
How can we compete without any courses?
Why do you say that, Ms. Joyner?
Wasn't it you who said that anything
is possible if you give it your all?
That's right! If there's no courses,
we can just make them.
Teacher...
Did you come to the Olympics in order to get a world record?
You won't run if there's no grand arena?
You run because you love it, right?
Yes!
Ms. Joyner! Do your best!
On your marks!
Ready!
Keep on going!
Give it your all!
Joyner broke the world record
and ran under 10 seconds!
9.95 seconds! This is a really amazing record!
Thank you, teacher!
Thank you, Kouta!
It's all thanks to you that I ran under 10 seconds!
No way... I didn't do anything...
We managed to hold the Olympics, Exkaiser!
I'm happy for you, Kouta!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Soon a concert will be held for Exkaiser.
And Kotomi-chan will play the piano there!
I promised to bring her flowers before her performance!
I'll try to be my coolest!
Ah! Kotomi-chan got captured by Geisters!
Just wait! I'll come save you now!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Concert for the Braves
Is there an alien in your home, too?