Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Go! Go! Luxury Liner
Now, it's almost the time for the super luxury liner Antony Cleopatra to set sail.
Look at this!
How elegant it is!
The suitable speed makes for a relaxing cruise.
It's the king of traveling!
It conveys a romantic sense of
"loneliness on a journey".
It can be called the treasure of traveling.
Lord Dino Geist!
I'll do the job this time!
We're going!
Mama, what's wrong?
When I think that this is a goodbye to Japan, I get so sad...
Mama, it's a special overnight commission.
We'll come back by tomorrow's night.
I know that...
But tears come out when I hear the sound of the steam whistle.
Chief editor!
What is it?
I'll go gather information inside the ship right away.
Alright, I'm counting on you!
Yes!
It's finally time for the cruise!
It's like a dream to be on such a luxury liner!
Yeah!
Well then, I'm going, Exkaiser!
Yeah! Have fun, Kouta.
Harbour Parking
Kouta-kun, you meanie!
Sorry, sorry!
Hi!
Kotomi-chan, how about it?
Would you like to come over here and drink a tropical drink?
Were you surprised that I wasn't coming up?
Huh? Kotomi-chan?
Amazing!
I had this tropical juice made
especially for Kotomi-chan!
Go ahead!
Where's Kouta-kun's share?
Hi!
What? You were here too?
I've been here for a while.
It's delicious!
Give him the same thing!
Yes!
Mario says he wants one too.
Give the dog something too then.
Yes!
Oh yeah, Kotomi-chan!
Would you like to come to my room?
It's an executive suite!
Really?
That's amazing! I'm totally coming!
You just ordered the drink, right?
Aren't you going to wait for it?
Come on, Kotomi-chan! Let's go!
But...
It's fine!
He's waiting for the drink he particularly
ordered, after all.
That's right.
I can't swim!
There's only one meter there.
How strange!
Huh? I'm back here again!
Okay, this way!
Here again? Well this is troublesome,
what should I do...
That's right! I should just ask someone!
Um, seems like I got lost...
Huh? There's no one here...
This is...!
It's the food storage!
Beef stew and white sauce, curry, borscht and doubanjiang!
There's also all sorts of ingridients here!
This is...!
It's caviar!
Well then, time for a little taste test...
This is...
This mellow texture! This rich taste!
I'm so happy to be alive!
Cruising is so nice.
And since it's the super luxury liner,
the food is the best, too!
Oh? Is that a whale?
Eh, where?
Look over there!
I don't see anything.
Oh, it disappeared...
I'm sure it saw us and thought
it's best not to bother us.
I wonder if that's so?
That's...!
Ptera Geist!
Here you come...
What? Ptera Geist appeared?
Kaisers!
All of you, come quickly!
Roger!
How's the attaching of the energy boxes going?
They're all done!
There's been no mistakes.
Alright, let's do this!
Wait!
The cosmic police,
Kaisers!
You evil Geisters who disturb the peace on Earth!
I don't know what you're planning,
but as long as we exist
we won't let you do as you wish!
So you've all come!
Kill them!
What an amazing food!
Takumi-kun, is it really alright for us to eat this?
Yes, please don't be reserved. Go ahead and eat!
Then I'll gladly be eating!
I bet you were actually lonely to eat alone?
Well, isn't it fine?
They do say that a trip is better with companions.
Right, Kotomi-chan?
Yes, I'm feeling like I'm very rich!
Being on a cruise is really the best!
The quality of a cruise is decided by who you are traveling with!
Kouta-kun, thanks for inviting me!
I'm having the best time too!
Earlier I got asked on a date by a foreigner who looked like Tom Cruise!
It was a hard job to reject him!
You're one to talk! You can't even speak english...
What did you do that for?!
Oh yeah, where is Tokuda?
Don't be worried about him.
When Mr. Tokuda doesn't show his face during dinner, it always means that he is sleeping somewhere!
I'm sure he's seeing a great dream somewhere.
I'm so happy...
If that's the case, then sheesh!
We're on the sea, right? There should be no earthquakes here...
Ah, it stopped!
How strange...
I'm sure we bumped into a whale!
Whale?
What was that shaking just now?
Captain, we can't steer the ship!
What?
No good!
Captain, I can't use the radio!
Seems like there's something disrupting radio waves!
Just what's going on?
Just keep on playing around like that!
Let's get going!
Yeah!
Everyone, we must combine!
Max Team, Form Up!
Triple Fusion, God Max!
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
God Sonic Buster!
The shards of love have scattered
Form Up!
It's brewing in this world
Left&Right Fusion, Ultra Raker!
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
Ultra Chain Crusher!
I'm not afraid of anything
King Loader!
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
Form Up!
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
Kaiser Sword!
Don't you think this is quite strange?
Yeah... What was their objective?
They might have some other scheme...
It's an island!
That's true! We're heading towards an island.
Looks like a desert island.
Stopping by an island wasn't in the schedule...
But it's somewhat romantic to
stop by a desert island!
Help me!
Exkaiser, it's Geisters!
Exkaiser?
What's wrong? Please reply!
This is Exkaiser. Has there been any response of Geisters?
This is Sky Max. There's no response here.
Same thing here!
Likewise!
I see...
Then just where can those Geisters be...
It couldn't be...!
Kouta, can you hear me? Kouta! Kouta!
How strange! The radio doesn't work!
We got the treasure so nicely!
It turned into a plane!
What is it planning to do?
Kouta-kun, I'm scared...
Exkaiser, why won't you come?
It's an amazing treasure!
As expected from Lord Dino Geist.
This is a scoop!
Papa, be careful!
Looks like the space merchant Trader has come.
Oh, if it isn't Sir Dino Geist!
It's been quite the long time!
Remember me?
What is that ball of light?
Trader, this is the treasure.
This is quite a rare piece!
Well then, I shall take a closer look!
Change, Trader at your service!
How nice to be in this form!
Well then...
Papa's camera is...!
It's quite a great item!
Let's see here...
G'day, everyone!
What's up with this guy? Bad!
Mario!
So everyone, what do y'all think about this boat?
What do w'all think, uh... um...
Well, it's the best!
Is that so? It's the best, huh?
Um... So how much will it be... Click and click...
Alright! This might be better than I thought.
Sir Dino Geist, I'll be taking this!
How about 1 hundred million?
1 hundred million? That's way too little!
Then how about 2 hundred million?
Don't you dare look down on space pirates!
5 hundred million!
That's crazy talk! At highest it could
be 2 hundred million and 5 thousand!
It's something Lord Dino Geist stole himself! If I say 5 million, it's 5 million!
Well then! I'll give you a great discount service!
How about 200 007 515 space dollars!
5 hundred million!
I'm no match for Sir Dino Geist!
Alright then! I'll give you 5 million! Can I take the goods first?
Do as you wish.
Well then, here I go!
What!
Exkaiser!
It's been a while, Dino Geist!
Now that you've appeared before us,
we won't let you escape!
If you think you can capture me, then just try!
There was no talk that the police is coming!
This deal never happened, 'kay!
How dare you ruin my business!
Change, Dino Geist!
Damn you Exkaiser!
I'll pay back all the resentment
you've caused till now!
It turned into a robot this time!
This is bad! It's bigger than Exkaiser!
Ultra Raker, relocate the ship to a safe place!
Got it!
Let's go, God Max!
Yeah!
That Mr. Robot is going to save us!
Change!
Kaiser Shot!
God Sonic Buster!
Do you think this Lord Dino Geist would be captured that easily?
God Sonic Buster doesn't work!
God Max!
Are you alright, God Max?
Y-Yeah!
Ultra Raker!
How dared you do that! Unforgivable!
God Max, save the boat!
Kaiser Sword!
God Slicer!
All right!
This is bad!
We have no chance of winning at this rate!
Let's leave the rest to boss and retreat!
Let's escape!
Die!
God Bird Attack!
Now's the chance!
Let's combine our powers and attack!
Gather Wave Beam!
Kaiser Sword!
Thunder Flash!
They did it!
Did we get him?
I'll leave for today, but things
won't be the same anymore!
What?
Dino Geist...
What a formidable guy...
Seems like he's gotten a more powerful body since coming to Earth.
We must be careful.
We'll have tough battles from now on.
I slept well!
You idiot!
Even though such big incident happened,
you secretly ate the boat's food
and was fast asleep?
I'm so sorry!
See? I knew he was having great dreams.
Yeah, I'm sure.
But today was really scary!
It's alright now, since I'm here with you!
And who was it that fell on his knees and was all shook up!
I was trying to keep the boat steady
since it was shaking!
But still, I wonder where Mr. Exkaiser lives?
Maybe he lives surprisingly near!
But I haven't seen such a huge
person in the neighborhood!
Well, you'd get surprised if something like that was walking in the city!
There's dolphins!
There really is! How cute!
That's why cruising is so nice!
But it might be true that Exkaiser really is somewhere near watching over us.
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Big news!
They're making an amazing medicine that will cure any sickness!
Then there's no need to do those unpleasant preventive injections anymore!
But I heard that the medicine is made from awful pathogens.
That makes me worried...
If Geisters got a hold of that,
things would be horrible!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Virus That Disappeared at Sea
Is there an alien in your home, too?