Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Piggy Bank That Scattered in the Sky
All About J. Loan
This isn't enough at all...
And J. Loan's photobook just came out...
I bought them!
Good job!
Here's your reward.
Thanks, mama!
Just a little more to go!
Kouta-kun...
D-Do you want something?
Would you like to exchange that piggy bank to this cake?
But that's today's snack!
No way!
Is that the right thing to say when I'm here lowering my head?
Obviously!
Besides, isn't helping out something that's done voluntarily?
Do you think it's fine to take money from that?
That's...
Right? That's why you should give it to me.
Why must I give you the money
that I've saved up?
That's because I'm an adult!
Children should help out voluntarily and adults will get money by working.
But you don't even work yet?
What's up with you!
Don't you know what kindness is?
It's almost my birthday!
Can't you be nice and listen to me at a time like this!
Oh no, there's no salt.
Ah! I'll go buy some!
Is that so? Sorry to trouble!
No!
Don't be such a cheapskate! Money lover!
Lend me even a little!
If I say no, it means no!
Isn't it fine?
What the heck! You're the money lover here!
How dare you say that to me!
Sun Avenue
Why does she like such a blank face?
It's the Game Center! Playing once is fine, right?
I know already...
Thief!
A lot of slot machines and game coins have been stolen from Game Centers everywhere.
Why steal such things...
Game coins?
They're coins that can only be used in slot machines.
Salt
Kouta, weren't you doing an errand?
Uh oh!
I must bring it quickly to mama and get my reward.
Reward?
I get pocket money by helping around.
Why did you suddenly start saving up money?
I can't tell.
It's a secret!
This is so great! Go!
Looks interesting!
Go! Go!
I'm telling you to move!
Jeez!
Why this-...!
This is mine!
It's mine!
Stop it! Stop it!
Won't you stop already!
What are you doing?
We were just checking the condition of the treasures!
Treasures?
Don't be worried!
The treasure is right here...
These toy coins aren't a treasure!
You big idiots!
What?
... Is what Lord Dino Geist said.
Look at this!
Finally the 100 000 yen commemorative gold coins
will be issued the day after tomorrow.
Since they're a limited amount of 50 000,
it's expected that they'll run out
immediately after they're issued.
These are the coins that you'll steal!
Don't fail this time!
Wow, it's so beautiful!
It really is.
I could buy many copies of that photobook with just one of those coins...
Oh yeah, I wonder if that Tokuda is alright...
What's going on with Mr. Tokuda?
He went to the mint today to get information.
Mint is the place where these
gold coins are made, right?
That's right.
Mint?
I hope he's properly gathering information, but I'm having some bad feeling...
Chief editor!
Oh! Mr. Tokuda!
My car happened to break down.
Can I borrow chief editor's car?
I knew it!
Tokuda! You are such a...!
Just get going.
Thank you very much!
The mint, huh?
Maybe one coin has fallen down...
Hey, Mr. Tokuda! Please take me with you!
I want to see the gold coins.
Papa, It's fine, right?
I can go too, right?
Why must you come too?
It'd be worrisome to let you go alone!
Because you're thinking of picking up
gold coins while you're there...
No way I'm thinking that!
I just want to see the gold coins!
Just don't bother his work, okay?
So it's fine!
Sheesh, sister knows nothing about my hardship...
Chance, chance!
I'll just borrow it.
Sister!
There's something wrong with you if you're taking that piggy bank to the mint!
It's fine!
Kouta-kun, that's the mint.
So that's the place where money is made!
It's so amazing...
If I had this much, I could fill our house with that person's photobooks...
Currency Museum
Museum of money, huh...
This is money, too?
Why hasn't a single coin fallen in the place where they make money...
What are you doing, sister?
Hey, Mr. Tokuda! So money has existed since a long time ago.
But how did they buy things before that?
Kouta-kun, that's a good observation.
The answer is...
Kouta! You don't even know that much?
They bartered, of course!
Bartered?
They exchanged things!
Let's say that there's a person who wants rice and another who wants fish...
OK.
They exchanged their possessions and thus, a happy ending.
But what about times when the person wants fish, but the other person only has vegetable?
Well, that's true...
That's...
That's the exact reason why money was made.
The person who wants rice, buys rice with money.
And the person who got the money will buy fish from another person.
I see! We sure learned something new!
Right, Fuuko-chan?
-chan?
This is the gold coin that will be issued tomorrow.
Whoa, it's so pretty!
There's only one?
Well, tomorrow is finally the day.
They'll be transported to various banks.
This response is...
Could it be...!
Oh... I thought I'd be able to take a photo of a gold coin mountain...
The packaged ones are over there.
Can you show me them? Those...
W-What's that hole?
S-Something appeared!
Look out!
Spike Cutter!
Change!
How dare you steal the money that people have worked hard to obtain!
I, Exkaiser, won't forgive you!
What did you say?
We're your opponents!
That thing is aiming for the 100 000 yen gold coins!
M-My camera is okay! It's a miracle!
I see! This is a sign that's telling
me to obtain this scoop!
Alright! I'll give it my all!
I see! Come on, we should go too!
Eh, where?
Obviously to take the gold coins!
It's much better for us to have them,
rather than those guys!
Sister!
Sheesh, I'm joking of course... Do I look like a thief to you?
You do!
I was thinking of going to protect them, not take them!
To protect them?
I see! Sorry for doubting you.
If I do my best to protect them, maybe they'll give me 10%...
There's 50 000 gold coins worth of 100 000 yen, so 10% of them is...
500 million yens?!
500 million...
I gotcha!
Impact Flash!
Oh no!
What an idiot.
Lord Dino Geist!
You two should also go steal the treasures!
Yes, sir!
I won't let you go!
Shut up!
It's game over now, Exkaiser!
Get out of my sight!
Dragon Jet!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, Dragon Kaiser!
What an idiot!
He should've just get the hell out of here...
Let's go, Dino Geist!
Dragon Cannon!
Change, Dino Geist!
I can't do it anymore!
Sheesh! It's because you're carrying that piggy bank around!
Which is more important to you,
that piggy bank or the gold coins?
The piggy bank!
I can't believe those words are coming from my little brother...
Kouta-kun...
W-What is it?
Kouta-kun, let's leave this here.
Why?
Don't you understand?
10% of this box we're carrying
will easily exceed your piggy bank!
No way!
Give me that!
I'm saying no!
Leave this piggy bank behind!
My gold coins...
Give them back, you thief!
Dino Crusher!
Alright, this will end you!
Dino Buster!
Die, Exkaiser!
I won't be defeated that easily...
Are you seriously thinking that you could beat this Lord Dino Geist?
What are you being fascinated about?
If you've got the treasure, let's get out of here!
Yes!
Wait!
Shut up!
The treasure is ours!
You can play nicely with that guy!
Wait!
Dragon Beam!
Exkaiser!
Exkaiser is in danger!
Just what should I do...
That's right... With this...
Kouta, what are you doing?
I'll distract that robot with this!
Are you serious?
That's the money you saved up little by little by helping around!
It's more important than the gold coins, right?
I'm sorry, sister...
Look over here!
Here's the coins that you like so much!
There goes!
Now's the chance!
Dragon Archery!
Thunder Arrow!
It's a scoop!
The gold coins!
Gold coins!
G-Gold coins!
G-Gold coins...
My scoop...!
How amazing!
Kouta...
Exkaiser!
I'm sorry that you lost your important money because of me...
Exkaiser is much more important than money!
Kouta...
Money can be saved up again,
but the same can't be done for Exkaiser.
Thank you, Kouta!
What's this?
It's just pieces of paper!
It'd be awful if boss found out
that you stole such things...
S-Shut up! I know that without you telling me...
Yesterday bills worth of 50 billion, that hadn't yet been issued, were stolen from the mint.
The police has started their investigation and suspect that the criminals are Geisters.
Get rid of them quickly!
I know already!
You guys!
Lord Dino Geist said that you must bring him the banknotes!
Banknotes?
The treasure we got from the mint!
Huh? They were a treasure?
What's the matter?
T-Those are...
You couldn't have...!
That Ptera told us to get rid of them...
You were the ones who got rid of them!
That's dirty!
This is a present for Kouta from
the mint's employees.
J. Loan Photobook
They said it's in return for protecting the gold coins.
That's J. Loan's photobook!
Why only Kouta gets it?
He had saved up money a long time for this purpose!
Sister, it's a bit early but... Happy birthday!
Kouta, you're so...
If that was the case, why didn't you say earlier?
I could've avoided some embarrassment...
Sister, it's painful!
Thank you, Kouta!
Here's the sign of my gratitude!
Let me down!
Stop it!
I got it already!
Let me go!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
I hate cigarettes!
They stink, they're smoky and
bad for your health too!
So why do adults like those things?
Eh? Papa is going to stop smoking?
As expected from him!
But something seems to be wrong...
Whoa, it's Geisters!
Papa, it's dangerous to go there!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Papa Is a Non-Smoker
Is there an alien in your home, too?