Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
Everyone, listen!
Things have gone horrible!
Look at this!
God Max and Ultra Raker got captured by Dino Geist!
And Mr. Tokuda was also taken
instead of me!
Exkaiser!
At this rate, Dino Geist will havoc Earth!
The True Treasure
Exkaiser, open the door!
It's dangerous, Kouta!
Mr. Tokuda got abducted instead of me!
That doesn't mean that I can take
Kouta to a dangerous place!
Exkaiser!
Let me help!
I'm sure I'll be of some use!
But...
Anyway, we must go save Mr. Tokuda quickly!
And also God Max and Ultra Raker...
Got it!
But don't do anything dangerous.
Okay!
Please open this!
Let me out of here!
This couldn't be a prison?
N-No way! Tokuda Osamu, 29 years old.
Am I going to die here without
even doing filial piety...
No!
I don't want to die in a place like this!
Someone!
I'm saved!
I don't know who you are,
but thank you very much!
W-Who's this guy?
Lord Dino Geist!
This isn't that brat.
What?
P-Please spare me...
I've seen him before...
Now that you mention it...
You're the assistant of that quack
doctor that we once captured!
N-No such thing!
I'm meeting you all for the first time... Yes...
Don't lie!
I remember it clearly!
It was you guys' fault that our
previous base got destroyed!
I'll crush you!
Wait!
Lord Dino Geist!
This guy was the one who called that
Exkaiser bastard to our base!
Then that means that Exkaiser will
come here even if it's not that kid!
I see! That's it!
He isn't coming...
Idiot!
It's not like he'll appear immediately!
Exkaiser will come?
For my sake?
Was I that much of a celebrity...?
Lord Dino Geist!
In that case, if we put a trap here...
That's exactly right!
Can you hear Mr. Tokuda's voice?
Help me!
Yeah! It's from this direction!
Mr. Tokuda's voice has been inputted in my ears.
There's no doubt!
Please stop this!
This is funny!
It's fine to be amused, but don't kill him yet!
I'll... I'll die already so please stop...
You don't die yet!
So he's come...
Exkaiser!
How dare you torment a human
who can't fight back!
Today's the day when I'll settle things with you!
And today's also the last day when
you'll be able to say that line!
Change, Dino Geist!
Damn you!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Super Giant Fusion, Great Exkaiser!
I'll save you now!
You fell for it!
Don't come, Exkaiser!
This pond is a trap!
Alright!
What a lucky bastard...
Thunder, let's go!
Double Fusion, Pteder!
We'll do it too!
Yeah!
Double Fusion, Hormor!
Take this!
Oh no!
You can't dodge now, Great Exkaiser!
You coward!
It's the end of you!
At this rate, Exkaiser will...!
Alright!
Kouta!
God Max! Ultra Raker!
Just wait!
That's it!
And now off with your head!
Kouta!
You saved us!
Dammit!
They escaped!
Now's the chance!
Huh? Kouta-kun!
Mr. Tokuda!
Damn that kid!
You're in the way!
I thought that I was going to die!
Exkaiser, thank you!
Hurry to a safe place!
Yeah!
Oh yeah!
I bought this camera with my
efficiency bonus for times like this!
Mr. Tokuda! It's dangerous to go back!
I'll be sure to make this scoop of the
century my own! Just watch!
Mr. Tokuda!
Kaiser Sword!
Let's go, Dino Geist!
How impudent!
It's the greatest shutter chance!
What?
Take this, Dino Geist!
Dino Geist!
Give up already!
Damn you!
Damn bastard!
Now we'll get you with this!
Exkaiser, look out!
Sorry to kept you waiting, Great Exkaiser!
God Max!
You bastard...!
Leave these guys to us!
God Max! Ultra Raker!
Damn you!
Damn, let go of me!
I've captured this brat!
Kouta!
Oh no!
This will be the last souvenir from this planet!
Kouta-kun!
Kouta!
God Max! Ultra Raker! I leave the rest to you!
Yeah!
Kouta-kun...
I won't let you escape, Dino Geist!
Damn you!
Throw away your weapons if you don't
want this kid to be crushed!
You! Is this kid that important to you?
It's not only Kouta who's important!
All the lives that exist in this
universe are important!
Are you saying that in order to protect
this puny Earthling's life,
you don't care what happens to you?
No matter how small it is, life is a treasure!
Even if it's a life of a villain like you!
You say amusing things.
Then I'll steal your important life!
What!
Exkaiser!
That won't be happening!
Dark Thunder Storm!
Dragon Jet!
Damn you!
Kaiser Sword!
Dino Twin Blade!
Take this!
Damn you, Exkaiser!
Bring it on, Dino Geist!
You're nothing!
Thunder Crash!
Dark Thunder Inferno!
Kill me at once...
That won't be happening.
I'll arrest you under the laws of space!
I wonder if you can...
Wait!
Exkaiser!
Things won't be going your way!
Oh no!
We've entered the sun's gravity range!
Dino Geist!
Life is a treasure, you say?
Then I can't let you have this life of mine!
Dino Geist...
Damn! Let me out!
I haven't done anything wrong!
I won't do bad things anymore, so forgive me!
You guys were so clumsy that
we ended up like this!
What did you say?
I'm sorry...
What a noisy bunch...
Exkaiser!
Kouta-kun!
Mr. Tokuda!
So you were safe...
Thank god!
Seems like our mission is finally over.
Oh yeah! I managed to get a lot
of photos of this scoop...
So let's take a commemorative photo!
Oh dear...
You're so big that you don't all
fit in the camera's frame!
Okay, everyone! Don't move!
Alright! I'll take it!
Cheese-...!
Mr. Tokuda!
I-It's alright... My camera didn't break!
Sheesh...
Kouta!
Huh?
Where's everyone?
Well... I think they'll be back soon...
You're going?
You've helped me in various ways until now.
Thank you.
Exkaiser...
Don't go!
Don't ask for the impossible...
My next mission is waiting for me.
But...
Parting is tough for me too...
Because you're my important friend.
If that's so...
If that's so, then why?
Kouta!
Don't forget about me either.
Sky Max!
It would've been great if you could've played once with my little sisters and brothers...
Drill Max!
Kid! A lot of things happened, but it was fun!
Dash Max!
We made some nice memories at Earth.
Shinkansen trains were certainly
interesting vehicles!
Blue Raker! Green Raker!
Exkaiser!
Shall we get going?
Kouta...
It's our farewell at last.
But this planet sure was a
planet with a lot of treasures.
Yeah! There were a lot of unusual treasures, too.
The greatest treasure for me was that
I could meet Exkaiser and you all!
It's the same for me.
Be well, Kouta!
Exkaiser...
Can we... meet again?
Well...
I can't promise that.
But...
No matter where I am in the universe,
I'm always watching over you.
I'd like for you to remember that
I'm always in your heart.
Yeah...
Well then, kid!
Send my regards to your sister!
Kouta! Goodbye!
Goodbye!
Dino Geist Is Finally Defeated
Peace Returns on Earth
"Peace Returns on Earth."
Well, Tokuda! You sure did it!
I'm just that skilled!
It's your first big scoop since
you started as a reporter!
Eat plenty!
Here's a second helping!
Mr. Tokuda, you're so easy to please!
Soy boiled food is your reward!
Don't flatter me so much, Fuuko-chan!
Oh? Where is Kouta?
Kouta, what's wrong?
Nothing...
You somewhat look like you've separated
from your important friend.
I don't know what kind of friend
you've separated from...
But doesn't Kouta have papa and your sister?
You're an important child for me too!
I'm sure that your separated friend
will come back one day!
Well then! Eat breakfast and cheer up!
If you don't, everyone will be worried!
Kotomi-chan and Takumi-kun too!
Takumi-kun, thanks for giving me a lift!
Kotomi-chan, weren't we going to
go to school together?
Kouta-kun, good morning!
What's wrong?
It's nothing!
Then, let's go to school quickly!
Wait a little!
I'll eat breakfast and get energetic!
No matter where I am in the universe,
I'm always watching over you.
I'd like for you to remember that
I'm always in your heart.
Kouta-kun!
Thank you!
Exkaiser!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path