Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Fire Truck, Set Out!
Danger!
No Trespassing!
So cold!
Damn!
Hey, Ptera! Do something about this!
Don't ask for the impossible!
If I could do something, I would've already-...
Beware of Fire
This is it!
This is what needs to be done!
This is good!
So warm!
You guys! Don't just be all cozy and
throw flammable things in there!
Yeah!
Inflammable
This too!
What? Hey, Thunder! That's-...!
You idiot!
This is nice...
So warm!
Isn't it kind of noisy?
Don't care for it!
Now this residence doesn't seem too bad.
This is paradise!
Let's light a fire in Lord Dino Geist's room too!
That's a good idea!
W-What's going on?
That's cold!
Freezing!
What the hell are you doing?
W-What are those?
That's damn cold, you dumbasses!
What a ridiculous cars for splashing water on me!
Wait!
Do you have some reason for stopping me?
It's this!
Cars that splatter water are rare!
We can sell these!
Really?
Bind Crush!
What!
You villainous Geisters!
On top of causing a fire...
You're trying to steal the important fire trucks
that protect people from fires!
We, Raker Brothers, won't forgive you!
T-This is bad!
You guys!
Let's take the treasures and leave!
Wait!
That's...!
Oh no!
The fire will spread to the other buildings!
Let's put it out!
Yeah!
They stole the fire trucks?
Seems like they're targeting fire trucks.
I see.
Tell Max Team to be on alert also.
Roger!
Fire trucks, huh...
These are the latest models?
Don't try to lie to me!
I won't buy such old models!
What kind of fire trucks will you buy then?
The authentic and real latest models of fire trucks!
Latest models?
Excuse me for a little...
Change, Trader at your service!
I'm talking 'bout these!
The latest fire ladder that prolongs
to a maximum of 200 meters!
Calibrated water gun.
And the newest floodlight that
illuminates up to 100 meters.
What do ya think? Look at this gallant shape!
It's the greatest fire truck in space!
If you've got these, I'll buy many.
Let's see... Um...
I'll give ya 20 million for one!
L-Look out!
Kouta...
What birthday present will you give to mama?
I did give flowers last year...
I wonder what would make mama the most happy...
What will you give, sister?
The truth is that I spent all of my pocket money...
So can you buy a present with your money
and write my name on the card too?
Sister!
Mama...
Mama!
What's the matter, dear?
The truth is...
Sky Restaurant?
The one in that skyscraper?
The one in the Plaza Hotel?
It's a secret to Fuuko and Kouta...
Why is that?
Because I want to go on a date with just the two of us on mama's birthday...
Oh my!
Unfair!
Oh, Fuuko...
You're going to eat high-class
food all by yourselves...
Take me with you!
I'll save you some leftovers...
So let us go on a date with just the two of us
at least on mama's birthday...
No way! No way! No way!
Sister!
What?
It's mama's birthday so let her do as she wants!
Kouta, thanks!
I'll definitely save you some leftovers... Okay?
I'm definitely tagging along!
Sheesh!
So hot...
What a beautiful sunset...
Sunset?
How terrible! I'm late!
12 o'clock?
So it's noon?
That can't be...
I-It's a fire!
I'm saved...
Treasure!
It's a monster!
G-Geister!
It's a scoop!
Huh?
Oh no! I forgot my camera!
It's not this... And neither this...
There's none! I'm going back!
Damn... I was too late!
Hurry! Let's resume the fire procedures!
But how strange...
Why did he leave the fire trucks?
Weren't they targeting fire trucks?
I'm sure this is what Geisters are targeting!
That's why they didn't steal the other fire trucks.
What's that?
The latest model with a ladder!
It was developed for the fire safety of skyscrapers.
For skyscrapers, huh...
In other words, if we keep on eye on
those, Geisters might appear.
Thank you, Kouta!
This was an easy task!
My apartment is all drenched
due to the fire, after all...
We're just about to go out, so unfortunately
we don't have time to be hospitable...
Well then!
Gas is okay!
The oven is okay!
The refrigerator is okay!
Mama! It's alright, so just get going!
I-Is that so?
You need to hurry.
Papa is already waiting in the car.
Ah, that's right... Did I check the washing machine?
I'll check it!
Let go, Mario!
That's from sister's room!
Hey! Let go already!
My feast is escaping!
Sister!
Sister, just give up already!
But they're leaving us behind and going
to eat a feast by themselves!
Don't you think that it's unfair?
I don't think so!
No matter what you think, I'll definitely go
to the Sky Restaurant since I have the chance!
I definitely won't let you go!
I can't let you bother mama's date-...
Did you just say Sky Restaurant? In that skyscraper?
I-In that Plaza Hotel?
That's right!
Bye then!
S-Sister...
I'm coming too!
So delicious!
If I can eat something this delicious
then fires once in a while aren't so bad...
What was that?
Oh well!
This sucks... If it's this jammed, we won't make it in time for our reservation...
Papa, look!
That's a cute cafe!
Why don't we take a little break in there?
Let's do that, mama.
Sister...
Papa and mama aren't here.
Alright! Let's go inside, Kouta!
Wait! We can't!
Sister, let's go home already.
What are you saying!
While we're doing this, papa and
mama are already eating a feast!
Ah! Sister!
They really aren't here.
Maybe you misunderstood something?
There's no way I could have misunderstood!
I heard it with these ears-...
Have you made a reservation?
No need to exaggerate...
Well then! Let's go, Kouta.
Mister! B-Behind you!
Everyone, escape!
Exkaiser!
Were you able to cancel the dinner reservation?
I tried calling many times but it didn't connect...
It's like the Sky Restaurant disappeared...
That couldn't be! It's not like it's a ghost!
Well, that's true!
»A fire has occurred at the 57th floor.«
»Customers in the 57th floor,
please evacuate promptly.«
Everyone, calm down! Please do as I tell you-...
Escape quickly!
»A fire has occurred at the 57th floor.«
»Customers in the 57th floor...«
Sister!
Sister, what are you doing?
Can't you tell by looking?
I'm taking the feast!
As if I could leave behind the feast just
because Geisters have appeared!
Keep your heads low, so you don't inhale the smoke!
Cover your mouth with a wet handkerchief!
Is there anyone left? The shutter will be closed soon!
Alright!
Let's go!
Sheesh!
Let's go, Mario!
My feast!
What did you do that for!
Hey! We are still here!
Sister, calm down! There's a door at the side!
The door is...
It's dangerous to be here.
Let's get further away from the fire!
What are you doing?
If you put damp cloths in the door's gaps,
the smoke won't come in, right?
I see!
But how can we escape from here?
There's a lot of fire trucks...
Such small ones won't be able to save us!
It's alright!
The latest model fire truck will
come soon and save us!
But that's only if Geisters don't get in the way...
Kouta, that's...
Sister...
He'll come to save us!
It's a monster!
Hey! Don't leave your positions!
I'll be taking the latest model fire truck!
Change, Raker Brothers!
What?
Twin Bind Crush!
Are you alright?
Yes!
Change, Exkaiser!
In order to steal the latest model fire truck,
you created a fire and made the people suffer!
It's absolutely unforgivable!
Breast Beam!
Form Up!
Left&Right Fusion, Ultra Raker!
Ultra Chain Crusher!
Dragon Jet!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Super Giant Fusion, Great Exkaiser!
Do it now!
Alright!
Kouta!
Help us!
I'm coming now!
It's so hot!
I don't want to die yet!
Come on, everyone! Hurry!
Sister!
I-I got weak at the knees...
You can't be helped!
Thank you, Exkaiser!
Great Exkaiser is...!
I haven't forgotten about
what you did earlier!
Damn! What can be done?
Firefighter! Please!
Please help Great Exkaiser somehow!
I'll do anything!
Alright! Then step into the
fire truck's driver's seat!
Yes!
I'm ready!
There's buttons on the upper right, right?
Yes!
First you'll press the black button
until I tell you to stop.
Yes!
That's good!
Alright, stop!
Yes!
Then press the red button next to it.
Serves you right!
That's good, kid! Leave the rest to me!
Exkaiser!
Damn monster... I'll blast you with
the maximum water pressure!
Take this!
Now's the chance!
Kaiser Sword!
Thunder Flash!
This is bad! Time to leave!
You did it, Great Exkaiser!
You did a good job, kid!
Fuuko and Kouta, you really don't want cake?
Well then!
In the place of Fuuko-chan and Kouta-kun,
this humble Tokuda Osamu will take one...
So delicious!
Maybe I'll stay here forever
if I can live like this every day...
No way you can stay!
I have enough of looking after
you at the company!
No way...
Sheesh...
We've had enough of fires!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Everyone, do you like school?
I don't like tests and homework, but it's fun to eat lunch together with friends, right?
Takumi came to school even though he has a cold, and all he does is complain!
If he dislikes it that much, then
he should've just rested.
Whoa! It's Geisters! How come
they're attacking the school?
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Takumi Likes School?!
Is there an alien in your home, too?