Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Defeat the Meteor Shower!
Soon the shuttle that's carrying the
Meteor Shower Special Observation Team
will launch towards the space station that's in Earth's orbit.
As you know, this Observation Team consists of recommended scientists and press.
Their object is to stop and observe the large meteor shower that's approaching Earth.
Everyone in the country!
No, everyone around the world!
I am Tokuda Osamu!
Chief editor! Kouta-kun! Are you watching?
I'll definitely get the first great scoop of space!
I'm awfully sorry for that.
We'll continue on reporting the
situation of the launching.
I'm so jealous that Mr. Tokuda can be in a shuttle...
Tokuda is there so he can get information.
Is it going to be okay? Isn't he going to blunder again?
A meteor shower is shooting stars, right?
I'm sure it'll be pretty when shooting stars come in a shower.
They'll be like huge fireworks...
You sure are carefree, mama...
It'd be an awful thing if a meteor falls to Earth without burning away.
Awful thing?
When a meteor falls to Earth, even if only this big,
a hole as big as the Tokyo Dome will be formed due to the shock.
It's that powerful?
There's even stories that the dinosaurs long ago perished due to them.
What's going to happen to us?!
Have no worries, sister.
The artificial satellites Sweepers exist to save us.
Look!
There's currently 3 Sweepers launched.
Meteors that fall to Earth will be shattered into pieces by their powerful laser beam.
Oh, I was worried for nothing...
I was properly taught it in school!
And tomorrow we're going to the Space Research Center to look at the Sweepers in action!
Is that so? Well, good for you then!
Oh, Kouta... You have an excursion tomorrow?
It's a field trip!
Do you need a lunch box?
Of course!
Well then, I'll be reporting from the shuttle.
I'll start by interviewing the captain of this Observation Team, Professor Tokoroda.
Professor Tokoroda... Professor! Professor!
Everyone, be at ease!
He's saying that Sweepers that are made with mankind's greatest wisdom
will completely destroy the meteor shower!
Sweepers are the artificial satellites that can truly be called the treasure of mankind.
Artificial satellites, Sweepers, huh?
Interesting!
0!
It left!
I'm so jealous of Mr. Tokuda...
What should I do about tomorrow's lunch box...
You're still talking about that, mama?
Well, there's no side dishes since I made
a lunch box for Mr. Tokuda...
Eh? You made a lunch box for Mr. Tokuda?
Did Mr. Tokuda possibly take the lunch box with him to the shuttle?
Yes, that's right!
Oh man!
Hot!
I see...
So the artificial satellites Sweepers will protect Earth's people from the meteor shower?
Yeah!
They also said that they've been protecting Earth's safety this far without us even knowing.
They're kind of like Exkaiser!
Huh? What's wrong?
W-Well...
What? Are you getting embarrassed?
So you're surprisingly shy, Exkaiser!
Oh, it's zero gravity inside the station also?
Yes, this facility is still under construction.
Once it's complete and reopened you can walk on the floor normally.
I don't really get it, but this way is more interesting!
There I go!
Wow, it's amazing!
It's like a sci-fi movie!
This is reality, not a sci-fi movie!
Can't you call things as what they are?
Kotomi-chan, let me explain!
There's 3 Sweepers that will defeat
the meteor shower.
Huh? It's dark... It's a blackout!
That's Ptera Geist.
Where is he going?
Exkaiser!
Exkaiser, please reply!
What's the matter, Sky Max?
Ptera Geist has left the atmosphere range and is heading towards space!
What did you say?
Perhaps Geisters are targeting the Sweepers, that are currently the hot topic!
I got it!
Sky Max, please be careful.
I'll head there immediately, too.
Roger!
It's such a nice weather!
It feels so good!
How troublesome...
Let's tidy up!
Oh my!
Oh, is it the wind?
How awful...
Mario, thank you!
The movement and angles of Sweepers 1, 2 and 3 are adjusted at this center.
But the control for the disposal of the meteors is entrusted to the space station...
I can't see!
Takumi-kun, please be quiet!
It's your own fault for wearing that!
I-I can see!
In about 30 minutes, the meteors
will approach Earth!
If this fails, Earth will be in trouble, right?
I'm kind of scared...
It's alright! Sweepers are made out
of the latest technology!
Ah, again...!
Be quiet, Takumi-kun!
Everyone around the world!
I'm inside the station now.
The meteors will be approaching soon, so the tension is through the roof.
Look at this!
Hey, wait! My fried shrimp!
Oh sheesh! There goes mama's lunch box...
They really are targeting the artificial satellites Sweepers...
Dino Geist!
That's...!
You fool!
You let that guy follow you...
I-I'm so sorry!
Let's go!
Yes, sir!
We've located the meteor shower.
There's 5 minutes left until they arrive to the Sweepers' shooting range.
Entering the prevention system.
Adjust the Sweeper's angle and distance.
Sweeper 1, adjusting distance.
It has started all right!
The greatest scoop of this century!
I won't let it go pass me!
Look at this!
Now the greatest event of this century, Meteor Shower Prevention Plan, is about to start.
H-Hey! Let me go...
Sweeper 1, distance and angle adjustment complete.
Release the laser lot!
Roger!
The first section of the meteor shower
is in shooting range.
Energy charge 120%!
Ready to fire!
Starting countdown!
Starting countdown, ok!
0!
Firing!
What's wrong? Did it miss?
All right!
Amazing! Sweepers really are like Exkaiser!
Change, Dino Geist!
W-What's that?
I-It's Geisters!
I'll be taking this!
Guess I'll take that as well.
It's coming our way!
This is a scoop!
This will sell at a high price!
Ptera Geist! Go take the rest of the Sweepers!
Yes, sir!
I won't let you!
I won't let you do as you wish!
Such a persistent guy... Take this!
Hyper Phonon!
Dino Buster!
This will be your end!
Die!
Who's there?
Oh! It's Exkaiser!
That's...
Exkaiser!
Are you alright, Sky Max?
Yeah!
So you really appeared...
Dino Geist!
It's unforgivable that you're trying to steal the Sweepers that protect Earth!
That's good! Beat him!
Thank god! Now we're safe!
But the meteorites will be falling soon, right?
Don't care for them!
Go steal the rest of the Sweepers!
Yes, sir!
How horrible! The rest of the Sweepers
will be stolen too!
Professor! A fast meteorite shower will arrive in Sweepers' shooting range in 7 minutes...
What should we do?
Let's go!
You're running around...
Is that all you got?
Get off me!
What great powers!
Oh no! The station is in danger!
It's coming this way again!
Ptera, steal the rest of the Sweepers quickly!
Y-Yes!
Why you!
D-Dammit! The treasure!
This is bad! Sky Max, protect the last Sweeper!
Roger!
That useless idiot!
Exkaiser! Look at this!
How terrible! The Sweepers' transmission antenna got attacked!
At this rate, we won't be able to fire the laser!
No way!
Stop it, Dino Geist!
Your selfish actions are unforgivable!
Shut up! You should be the ones to get the hell out of here already!
If you don't, I'll smash this station!
Wait!
Give the last Sweeper to us nicely!
This is bad! Everyone, put on your helmets and lifelines!
L-Lifelines?
Where are such things? Hey! Wait!
This time the space station is in trouble!
Come on, hand over the Sweeper quickly!
What should we do?
If we give it, a lot of people on
Earth will lose their lives...
But if we don't give it, the lives of the people in the space station are lost...
As long as I have this on, it'll be alright!
Just give me the Sweeper already!
Help! Help me!
This is nothing! I won't lose here!
Shut the hatch quickly!
Roger!
Huh? W-Wait a minute! I'm still here-...!
Oh no! Someone got outside!
I-I'm so scared!
Wait, Dino Geist!
Alright then, I'll give you the Sweeper.
Get away from the space station!
The Sweeper comes first! Give it!
It can't be helped...
Sky Max!
I got it...
Sweeper is...!
We did as you wanted!
Now get away from the space station!
You idiot!
Did you really think I'd keep my promise?
Die!
I'll die!
Ah! It shut again!
What's going on with this?
Let me inside!
Mr. Tokuda! Since you're outside, fix the antenna!
Eh?! I'll do it?
The meteorite shower is coming in shooting range in 3 minutes.
If we don't fix the Sweepers' control antenna by that time, Earth will be in big trouble!
It's impossible for me!
I'll give you the instructions! Just go!
N-No way!
Dino Buster!
Take this and that!
Alright, now's the time! Come, Dragon Jet!
W-What's this guy?
He got it back!
Amazing! Kouta-kun, what is that robot's name?
I don't know... I don't know, but he's on our side!
Alright! If it's come to this,
I, Tokuda Osamu, will get the antenna fixed in the name of being a Japanese man!
Mr. Tokuda, hurry! There's only 2 minutes left until they come in shooting range!
If they go past the shooting range, Sweepers won't be able to shoot them down!
Exkaiser, this is bad! If you don't hurry, they won't be able to shoot the meteorites!
I got it, Kouta!
Alright, this is it!
It's in such bad shape...
Mr. Tokuda! Please connect the same colored wires.
There's only 90 seconds left until they come in shooting range! Hurry!
I understand that! I just have to connect the same colors, right?
70 seconds left until they come in shooting range!
If the Sweepers don't work, what will be the fate of Earth... or Japan!
Chief editor! Tokuda will become a man!
Such power! At this rate, we can't keep up defending!
What should we do?
I'll lure him! Back me up!
How impudent!
Is that all you got, Dino Geist?
Alright! I did it!
The control antenna is working again!
Alright! Starting energy charging.
Adjusting the direction.
Energy is charged 20%.
It moved!
Will it be in time?
Hurry! Please hurry!
Take this!
How long can you hang on with those measly powers?
Energy charged 80%!
30 seconds left until they're in shooting range!
Alright, release the laser lot!
Energy charged 100%!
20 seconds left until they're in shooting range!
Alright, start the countdown!
Energy charged 120%!
0!
Firing!
Why you...
We did it!
As expected from the Sweepers!
This is bad! There's 2 huge ones still left!
It's no good! Firing the Sweepers now wouldn't make it in time!
W-What should we do? Everyone will die!
Let go! What are you trying to do?
Come, Dragon!
Dragon, destroy those meteorites!
Dragon, get away!
I-I can't get off...
Kaiser Sword!
Thunder Flash!
He did it! That was amazing, Exkaiser!
We're saved...
That sure was a close call...
Thank goodness!
Somehow I'm kind of tired...
What's that shirt? It's a child's clothing, right?
T-That's my shirt!
How strange... Kouta's one shirt is missing.
I wonder where it flew to...
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
There's 2 weeks left of summer vacation.
I was thinking of doing my homework soon, but lucky!
Geisters stole our homework!
Eh? They also stole juice, ice cream and even the pool?
On top of that, even the fireworks festival is cancelled?
I don't want to have a summer that's only hot with no excitement!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Retrieve Summer!
Is there an alien in your home, too?