Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Secret of the Geoglyphs
Isn't it amazing?
These are the Nazca Lines!
I'm tagging along with papa who's going there tomorrow for work and see these!
They're quite interesting pictures.
There's a theory that aliens came to Earth a long time ago and drew them.
Aliens?
These are so huge that the entirety can only be seen from the sky, after all!
It's hard to believe that the ancient people of Earth would've drawn them.
They can only be seen from the sky?
Maybe Exkaiser's grandpa or someone drew them when they came to visit Earth!
Like this... and like that...
How's that?
I remember seeing this shape somewhere...
I think they're doing a feature on TV now.
I'm currently in southern Peru.
As you know, here are the ancient Inca Empire ruins and Nazca Lines,
so this is a place of unexplained mysterious treasures of Earth, or rather space!
Place of treasures?
This is shot from the sky.
These geoglyphs stir us up with ancient romance.
They can be called the treasure of mankind!
They're just pictures though.
Wait...
Perhaps...!
Here's orders from Lord Dino Geist.
Go steal the Nazca Lines!
What's the use in those?
They're just pictures, right?
They don't even serve as snacks!
Idiots! This is why you're so useless!
What did you say?
... Is what Lord Dino Geist said.
No way he'd say that!
Jeez!
You're always acting so superior
of what he said or not!
We'll rip you apart and eat you!
S-Stop it!
These geoglyphs might be a treasure map that was done by a space creature in ancient letters!
It's what Lord Dino Geist said!
A treasure map, you say?
Papa, it's in sight now!
This is amazing!
There's a lot of runways!
Those are not runways.
Those are also part of the Nazca Lines.
But no matter how you look at them, they're runways...
Maybe they're runways that aliens made a long time ago when they visited Earth?
I wonder about that.
They're obviously made by aliens!
That's the only possibility, chief editor!
But a newspaper reporter can't write an article based on a speculation.
Chief editor, you're so hardheaded!
If we write that aliens made them,
the readers will surely be happy!
You idiot!
The newspaper's purpose is to be truthful!
Just making it interesting isn't enough!
I'm sorry...
Does it really matter who made them...
But rather than that, I'm airsick...
Stop it, Fuuko-chan...
I'm feeling alive again!
We'll go to the site via helicopter from here.
We're going to fly again?
It would take many days if we'd go by car.
I've had enough already...
We'll lodge over there so we'll come back in 2 days!
Eh?! Wait! Don't leave me behind!
No good...
No matter how many times I analyze it,
I can't remember.
But I have a feeling like this geoglyph is trying to tell me something.
Alright!
Change, Exkaiser!
Dragon Jet!
Dino Shield!
I'll bring down that Exkaiser with this new weapon.
Ah! I know that!
It's the frigatebird!
So amazing...
There's one that looks like Mr. Tokuda!
Let me see!
Ah, it's true-...
Oh come on now...
There's also one that looks like a monkey.
Kouta, take a good look at them.
These are the real Nazca Lines.
Yeah!
We don't know for what reason the ancient people drew these.
But there's no doubt that they made them in order to tell us something.
I think that our job is to figure out exactly what our ancestors wanted to leave behind for us,
and then teach that to our offspring.
Figure out exactly what they meant, huh...
Seems difficult!
Huh?
That's...
That looks exactly same to the Exkaiser that I saw in the Kusunoki village's coffin...
Say again?
Oh, it's nothing!
Is there perhaps a connection with Exkaiser and these geoglyphs?
So there is Nazca...
I don't understand...
That's...!
That huge shape can only be seen from space.
But for what reason...
Kouta, this ditch is one of the lines of those huge geoglyphs.
But when you look at it this close, you can't understand at all what's been drawn.
Chief editor!
It's a scoop! A scoop!
What's the matter, Tokuda?
I've found a person who holds the key to the secrets of the Nazca Lines!
What?
You're trying to make this overly interesting again!
Did you perhaps bring an imposter?
No! No such thing!
I found her after searching frantically through the nearby town.
It's the old lady Casna who's claimed to know everything about these ruins.
That's right. I know everything about this place.
Seems kinda fake...
Aliens have taught me various things since I was little.
Really?
That's a lie.
She said that there's a certain legend here. Right, old lady?
That's right.
What's the legend?
Papa, don't go along with this nonsense!
"When the giant walks and the frigatebird flies,
the great sun hides its face!"
What does that mean?
Perhaps the giant and frigatebird refer to these geoglyphs...
"Sun hides its face" means...
That sun disappears?
It means that the end of this world is coming!
No way!
Don't take it that far, old lady!
It's a giant!
A giant is walking!
No way such a convenient	 thing would happen...
Why...
A giant... A giant is walking!
It's a scoop!
Camera! Camera! Um...
Oh no! I forgot my camera again!
We must escape, Kouta!
It's Geisters!
We'll take them all.
Save me!
Let's get away from here with the helicopter!
Ah, old lady!
Kouta!
Help me!
Old lady, let's escape!
Exkaiser!
Escape quickly!
But how come you're here...?
Hurry!
Come on, old lady!
You dare follow us even here.
Crush him!
Kouta!
Hurry inside!
Do your best, Exkaiser!
You bastard!
I will always appear to where you
villains do evil things!
Let's beat him!
Change!
Jet Boomerang!
Damn you!
Shoulder Bomb!
The giant is already walking.
The frigatebird will fly next!
Everything is going as the legend told.
The bird is trying to fly.
At this rate, the sun will hide its face.
In other words, this world will end!
No way!
It's the end of this world...
Help!
Kouta!
Dragon Jet!
We're saved!
Geisters!
I can't let you have this Earth's treasure that's been left here since a long time ago!
Damn you!
This is bad!
Let's scatter!
I won't let you escape!
Dino Geist!
Change, Dino Geist!
Take this!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, Dragon Kaiser!
Let's go, Dino Geist!
Dragon Anchor!
Dino Shield!
Dragon Wave!
Did I get him?
Now it's my turn!
Dino Shield!
Dragon Kaiser!
Keep on going! Don't lose to that Dino Geist!
The sun is...!
The sun is fading away.
The legend was true.
The sun has begun to hide its face.
It's the end now! The end of this world!
I see... It's a solar eclipse!
"Sun hiding its face" meant a solar eclipse!
I'll let you have a good taste of all the resentment you've caused me so far!
Damn you, Dino Geist!
Dragon Archery!
Thunder Arrow!
Thunder Arrow is now defeated!
What!
When it comes down to it, your weapons are powerless against this Dino Shield!
Dino Blade!
Let's go!
Oh no!
Try to avoid my deadly swords if you can!
Dark Thunder Storm!
Dragon Kaiser!
Looks like the battle is over, Dragon Kaiser.
Suffer the retribution of going against the space pirates Geisters!
I can't be defeated here!
I must protect this Earth... and protect Kouta and the others from Geisters!
Off with your head!
That's...?
W-What's this light?
I can feel energy flowing into my body.
Kaiser Sword!
This is...!
It's big!
It's a big Kaiser Sword!
Damn you!
Dark Thunder Storm!
Impossible!
I can't afford to lose to you villains!
Let's go, Dino Geist!
You're so damn impudent!
He did it!
His powers had definitely ran out already... So how?
How can he still use such a powerful technique?
Dammit!
Next time things will be different!
Old lady, it's alright now.
The legend really was true!
The end of this world didn't come though.
There was a continuation to the legend.
Continuation?
"When a Brave appears, God's powers will save Earth."
Brave! God! Please keep on protecting this planet!
Fuuko!
Have you seen Tokuda?
Now that you mention it, where did Mr. Tokuda go?
Save me!
Hey! No! Don't-...!
Mother! Please forgive me, Tokuda Osamu, for dying at the young age of 29 years!
Why does this happen...
From the viewpoint of the ancient people,
aliens could've seemed like Gods, right Exkaiser?
It might be better to let mysteries be mysteries, Kouta.
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
There's a crazy wind and a rain like a waterfall!
It's terrible!
But the weather forecast didn't mention this...
Ah! Geisters are creating a typhoon!
How horrible! All of the Kaisers got captured!
Huh? What's that light?
Is it Exkaiser's new power?
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
It's Here! Super Giant Fusion
Is there an alien in your home, too?