Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Virus That Disappeared at Sea
Infirmary
Ow!
Did it hurt that much?
I'm sorry...
You're exaggerating!
It's just a 	scratch	.
Takumi!
You'll get scolded by the teacher
if your wear that without permission!
It's fine!
Anyway, do you both know the story of the doctor Jenner from England?
Jenner?
I know!
It's the person who invented the
smallpox vaccine, right?
As expected from Kotomi-chan.
You have much more knowledge
compared to some idiot.
Why are you talking about this Jenner?
He used his own son as a guinea pig in the development of the vaccine, you know.
What?
Kotomi-chan, hold him down!
It's absolutely necessary to have a human guinea pig for the progression of medical science!
What are you doing!
If I can't become a soccer player,
I'll become a doctor like Jenner, who contributes to humankind.
I need to do injection experiments for that to happen!
Why am I the guinea pig?
It's an honor to be the first one, Kouta-kun!
Kaneari-kun! What are you doing?
If you like injections that much, I'll give you one!
N-No, I'm... Uh... Help me!
Well, do you like injections too?
N-No! I'd rather not get one!
These cause harm to people.
They're pathogens that are put together by the help of biotechnology.
This is the world's worst pathogen
combination substance, X-Virus.
World's worst pathogen combination substance, huh?
How creepy!
The X-Virus is currently contained in gelatin substance.
The Eastern Medical Center is currently developing a vaccine made from this X-Virus.
Once it's complete, most of the diseases that torment people
can be cured by this vaccine.
You can create such medicine
from the virus inside this?
Yes!
Because it's the world's worst,
it can create the world's best medicine.
Is that how it works?
However, the completion of the vaccine is not done yet.
If you touch that now, you'll die.
Although it's the most dangerous
virus at the moment,
this is a treasure that's needed
to make the best vaccine.
No! It can be called the treasure of mankind!
I see... The treasure of mankind, huh?
Yes, seems like it also increases the lifespan of people all around the world.
But chief editor looks like he'll
live long even without it...
What was that?
Oh, nothing!
So when will the vaccine be completed?
Um... Well... The completion is...
You didn't ask?
No, well...
Idiot!
The one who'll live long is you!
Which one is it?
D a n g e r o u s
Warning     Dangerous
There! That's it!
This will make Lord Dino Geist so delighted!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Really?
Was such an dangerous pathogen really stolen?
That's not it!
It was a tanuki ornament that got stolen.
A tanuki ornament?
What do you mean?
I'm saying that they thought the pathogen carriage truck got attacked,
so there was an uproar.
But it was someone's moving luggage that got attacked, which was next to the research institute.
Moving luggage?
Oh, that's boring then!
Could those Geisters be collecting
ornaments this time?
I wonder about that...
It's not that?
It bothers me that the attacked car was near the place where X-Virus is being researched.
Then...
Can medicine really be made from such a dangerous virus?
Yeah... I don't really understand it, but poison becomes a medicine.
My teacher told us that once the medicine is complete,
we might not even need preventive injections anymore.
Preventive injections?
I hate injections because they hurt!
If injections will go away, I'll happily accept the alternative even if it's made out of poison!
It's really that important?
So when is that virus being transported?
They said tomorrow.
Got it.
I'll inform everyone and tell them
to be on alert just in case.
You fools!
W-We're so sorry!
It really was a mistake to leave it up to you guys.
They'll finally transport that virus...
What's that?
What?
This is it!
T-That's...!
I'll be taking this treasure!
I won't let you!
What?
Change!
Dammit!
D-Dino Geist!
Oh no!
O-Oh crap!
You sure got in our way.
Lord Dino Geist...
Ptera Geist! Go search for the treasure.
Yes, sir!
Don't move!
We've found you, Dino Geist!
You'd better give up!
Don't you care what happens to your comrade?
Sky Max!
D-Don't worry about me!
If you want to get him back alive,
go search for the treasure that fell in the sea and bring it to me!
What did you say?
As expected from Lord Dino Geist, that's a great idea!
I'll wait for 2 hours of Earth's time.
The place is the crater at Mt. Oototsu.
Understood?
Goddamn it!
If we had just arrived earlier...
I'm sorry, Sky Max...
»Chiita!«
»Takeshi, save me!«
This is an emergency news flash.
The X-Virus that was just moments ago transported from the microbiology institute,
seems to have been stolen by dinosaur robots!
What did they say about Mr. Virus?
It got stolen!
The moving luggage of Mr. Virus?
We're talking about the X-Virus!
It's that dangerous pathogen!
That's horrible!
Did you find it?
No luck! It might have floated
away by the strong current.
Exkaiser, it's terrible!
X-Virus got stolen by the Geisters!
I know, Kouta.
However, the virus isn't yet in their possession.
Eh? So it wasn't really stolen?
That's right. X-Virus is in the sea.
Eh? In the sea?
We're doing our best searching for it right now.
That can't be!
The news just told that the gelatin which hardens the virus will melt in water!
What? What does it mean?
When 3 hours go past, the gelatin melts
causing X-Virus to contaminate the sea
and all of the fishes will die!
And not just the sea!
It causes a chain reaction, that could kill all the living things on Earth!
What did you say?
All the living things on Earth might die?
Can you possibly find it within 3 hours, Exkaiser?
Don't worry! We'll definitely find the virus!
I'm counting on you, Exkaiser!
I hope my sensor will pick it up somehow...
Exkaiser, it'll soon be 2 hours.
What'll we do about Sky Max?
I'll go ahead and try to extend the time.
Please do what you can in the meanwhile.
Got it! We'll definitely find the X-Virus!
I'm counting on you!
That Exkaiser sure is late.
Let's kill Sky Max!
Don't be so impatient, Horn!
It's not too late to do it once we get the treasure.
What? You're so cocky!
The time has passed!
Let's kill Sky Max!
Wait!
Change, Exkaiser!
We got tired of waiting, Exkaiser! Did you bring the treasure?
No...
You came here with nothing?
Don't look down on us!
Hey!
I-I'm sorry, Exkaiser...
Are you alright, Sky Max?
If you don't bring the treasure, then we just have to kill this guy!
The X-Virus will definitely be delivered.
In the meantime, I'll take Sky Max's place and be the hostage!
Are you telling us that you'll
become his substitute?
That's right! Let go of Sky Max!
Don't make us laugh!
You'll obviously try to escape once you become the hostage. You can't fool us!
If you don't have the treasure,
then we're just gonna kill this guy!
Wait!
Think this through, you villains!
If you kill Sky Max, you'll never get the treasure.
Are you fine with that, Dino Geist?
I can't allow the hostage to be changed.
I'll wait for 30 minutes more.
But if the treasure still isn't here...
You do understand, right?
What's that?
It's a shoal of fishes... Let's go check it out!
There it is!
It's here! We've found the X-Virus!
Is the X-Virus intact?
Yeah, the gelatin around it hasn't
completely melted yet.
That's good! Alright, let's deliver it quickly!
Wait, Dash Max! Are we really going to hand over the X-Virus?
Yeah! If we don't, Sky Max will be killed!
But if we give this to Geisters, the living things on Earth might perish!
Are you fine with that?
Nah, don't be worried, Blue Raker!
I've got a good idea!
Time's up!
Kill him!
That's right, let's do it!
Wait! Kill me in the place of Sky Max!
What?
That could be interesting!
Prepare yourself!
Serves you right!
It's time for you to die as you wanted!
Wait!
We brought you the promised thing!
You sure made us wait...
Time for the exchange.
Yes, sir!
Exkaiser!
It'll be an exchange between only you and I.
Alright, I got it!
Don't do it!
If you give it, all the living things
on Earth might perish!
Shut up!
Sky Max!
I don't mind getting killed...
So please save the living things on Earth...
Shut up!!
P-Please save the living things on Earth...
Sky Max!
Come on! Let's do this, Exkaiser!
Yes...
He's so honest...
Seems like his friend is more important than Earth.
I'm giving him to you.
Take this.
You're too naive, Exkaiser!
What!
Now that we have the treasure,
things will go our way!
Kill him!
How despicable!
Be as vexed as you want to, Exkaiser!
Now's the chance!
Impact Flash!
Damn!
Wait!
We got the treasure! Let's retreat!
We won't let you escape!
Hey you, kill them!
What?
Are you alright, Sky Max?
Yeah...
What is this guy?
King Loader!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
Hey! Are you alright, Sky Max?
Don't worry! Let's combine!
Max Team, Form Up!
Triple Fusion, God Max!
Left&Right Fusion, Ultra Raker!
What?
Oh no!
Punches and kicks won't work against him!
Alright! Let's do consecutive attacks!
Alright! I have an idea!
Wait!
God Max!
God Sonic Buster!
Exkaiser, do it now!
Kaiser Sword!
Kaiser Flame!
Thunder Flash!
But the X-Virus got in the hands of Geisters...
It's alright!
This Dash Max changed it into a fake one.
Then the X-Virus is...
It's right here!
The X-Virus that was stolen by Geisters
has been delivered to the microbiology institute safely by the help of Kaisers.
The virus entrusts the dreams of mankind, however it's also a scary existence.
Damn you, Kaisers!
How dare you give me a fake one!
Eh? The completion of the vaccine takes that long?
Yeah, they'll do multiple tests for now
and it'll take about 10 to 15 years.
Oh! And here I thought the injections would go away immediately.
Me too..
Well, isn't it fine!
Injections hurt because they're effective.
That's right.
Being sick is much more horrible than the pain of an injection.
Well, that's true...
Are injections really that awful, Mario?
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
I love zoos!
Even if I'd be there a whole day,
I wouldn't get bored!
But I bet in reality the giraffes, elephants and lions would like to walk in a more vast place...
It's Geisters again!
They'll take the panda's cub!
Huh? What?
That plane is... Dragon Jet?!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Panda Cub Competition
Is there an alien in your home, too?