Brave         Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
There's a Lot of Santas
Sale
Would you like a Christmas cake?
What on earth is this commotion?
Merry Christmas!
Do your Christmas shopping at
the Kaneari department store!
There's incredible presents waiting for you
that you can't find anywhere else!
Christmas?
Chief...
Do I absolutely have to go?
Isn't tomorrow's party a gathering for all the chief
class persons of the newspaper industry...
That's exactly why I want you to participate
as you're the next chief!
Please, Hoshikawa-kun!
I beg you!
If I don't go back home this Christmas,
my wife has said that she'll take the kids
and go back to her parents house!
It's the same for my house too, though...
Please attend it!
Think of this as saving me!
Earth sure is a planet that has a lot of festivals.
Yeah...
But Kouta and the others are very excitingly
looking forward to Christmas.
I've heard that it's a yearly event,
when a person called Santa Claus brings
presents for children around the world.
Santa Claus?
Who on earth is he?
Well... I don't really know either...
No... Well... It's not like I won't
be coming back home...
Tonight is Christmas Eve!
If papa doesn't come home, then what
will happen to the presents?
That's...
Santa Claus will...
Then it's a Christmas Eve without papa, huh...
Sorry! But I'll try to come home
as soon as possible.
Isn't it fine?
It just means that dinner will be later than usual.
Which also means that I can make
more food than usual!
Mama...
Well then, I'll try to come back home early!
Have a nice day!
Well then, papa! Go to work!
Yes!
Um... Mama...
Mama? That's it!
Me as Santa wouldn't be too bad, right?
I know it now!
What is the cause of this fuss then?
This is something called Christmas.
Christmas?
You guys! Orders!
Go kidnap Santa Claus!
He has a lot of treasures!
... Is what Lord Dino Geist said!
I see.
Santa Claus...
I'm glad that there was still one left
at the rental clothing shop.
It's a female Santa!
Hi!
Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas...
It's a monster!
I found you!
There's one here too!
It's easy to catch the ones who don't move!
Oh, there's one here too.
Is mama really going to be Santa?
Most likely.
Mama as Santa, huh?
It feels kinda off though...
Well, I'm happy with just getting what I'll get.
Special newsflash.
Geisters have appeared again.
Around the city, people who have dressed as Santa Clauses are getting captured one after another.
Dressed as Santas?
Could mama have been...!
I'll go look for her!
Kouta!
Exkaiser! There's trouble!
Geisters are targeting the Santas around the city!
Santas?
The people who've dressed as Santa and
advertise in front of department stores!
I got it! I'll come immediately!
Car... Car...
Ah! My car is gone!
I bet that damn Tokuda has
taken it again without asking!
Oh no!
At this rate, I'll be late to the party!
I got so many!
Could mama be inside one of those...!
Mama!
What?
Give my mama back!
Shut up!
Change, Exkaiser!
Exkaiser!
Damn Geister!
Let those people go!
No way!
These are mine!
If you get in my way, I'll crush this.
Exkaiser...
You coward!
Exkaiser!
Today's the day when we'll be taking the treasure!
We have this many Santa Clauses!
There's no doubt that they've stashed
a mountain of treasures!
Those people aren't Santa Claus!
What did you say?
Those are wrong! They are fake Santas!
Is that true?
What!
They did it!
Geisters!
Too bad for you!
Goddamn it!
Damn humans! Why have they
scattered fakes around?
What do we do?
What, you ask? We'll obviously do this!
Hurry up!
As usual, they're fast to escape!
We're saved.
What on earth was that?
This is good!
Mama wasn't among them.
Kouta!
Exkaiser!
Seems like Geisters are targeting the real Santa Claus.
Yeah!
Kouta...
Could you tell me his whereabouts?
"His"? You mean Santa Claus?
That's right!
We must guard him quickly or he'll be in danger!
I don't know either where the real Santa Claus is...
Then who knows it?
In brief, if you think that Santa Claus exists then
he does but if you don't think so, then...
No... Well, I think it's something like that...
The world is rapidly changing!
The mission of us journalists is to constantly
spread new information to many people.
And like in any era, the pen is mightier than the sword...
Oh no!
I haven't bought presents yet!
Well then, please fully enjoy the party.
Merry Christmas!
I wonder where mama went...
Jackpot!
Christmas ✩ Chance
I won?
Congratulations! The special prize
is a trip to Egypt with your family!
Oh my! A trip to Egypt!
Mama!
I've looked for you!
Kouta!
Mama, Geisters are targeting Santa!
If you wear that-...
I won in the lottery!
Everyone!
Right here and now, the world's largest Santa Claus
statue has been illuminated in the night sky!
Merry Christmas!
And the sack on his back is tightly packed with
presents for the unfortunate children of the world.
This Santa Claus statue will surely be handed down
as a symbol of world peace and love for children.
Oh my! What a big Santa!
Thank god...
The Kaneari department store is still
open due to a Christmas event.
Um, you don't need to hurry so much...
There's still 30 minutes till it closes.
Hurry! We must choose presents
for everyone in 30 minutes!
Yes! Even if it costs me my life!
I've found him!
A big Santa Claus!
What's that?
The largest Santa Claus in the world
must also have the greatest treasures!
Santa's presents are...!
Heavy!
Hey! Carry it yourself!
Merry Christmas!
How terrible!
The largest Santa Claus statue in the world
has been changed into a Geister robot!
Alright! Carry the treasures like that!
Mama, get on quickly!
Kouta!
Change, Exkaiser!
I won't forgive you for exploiting Santa Claus
who's the symbol of love and peace for children!
Exkaiser!
So you've appeared, Exkaiser...
Then prepare to get hurt plenty by
that symbol of love and peace!
What did you say?
Merry Christmas!
The Santa statue is...!
Next up is the game that Kouta wanted!
Why is everyone in such a rush?
We are in a hurry too!
Yes, yes!
Kill him!
Exkaiser!
Merry Christmas!
Oh no!
It's here! It's the toy section!
Um... Game softwares are...
There! That's it!
What's going on?
Now it got buried!
Chief editor, isn't something strange here?
Exkaiser!
Merry Christmas...
W-What is that?
It's a Santa Claus monster!
Merry Christmas!
This will be your end, Exkaiser!
Finish him off!
Exkaiser!
What?
Change, Drill Max!
Change, Dash Max!
Change, Sky Max!
Max Team!
Form Up!
Triple Fusion, God Max!
Come on then!
So cheeky!
You'll be defeated at once!
Exkaiser, hurry!
Dragon Jet!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Super Giant Fusion, Great Exkaiser!
Great Exkaiser!
Damn! The situation doesn't seem too good.
You guys, join the fighting! I'll take the treasure!
The presents!
Chief editor!
Santa and the reindeer combined!
I'll take care of this!
God Max, go retrieve the presents!
Okay!
Damn! It's so heavy...
I won't let you take them!
God Max!
Exkaiser!
Kaiser Sword!
Merry Christmas!
Damn you...
I won't let you escape anymore!
Damn...
Remember this!
Thunder Crash!
All right!
He did it!
Thanks to Exkaiser, Santa's presents have been protected from the evil hands of Geisters!
Thank you, Exkaiser!
The modern day Santa Claus!
Papa sure is late...
Really!
Sheesh! I'm so hungry!
Let's wait a little more.
I'm home...
Ah! It's papa!
Oh my!
Papa, how come you look like that?
Sorry, I'm late...
Merry Christmas...
They're like this now, but...
It's your Christmas presents.
This is the packaging of the
Kaneari department store...
Then, papa... You got these during that ruckus?
Well, that was the only place open at this hour...
The best present is that papa is safe!
Here you go, papa!
Christmas where mama is the
Santa just doesn't feel right!
That's right! And it's no Christmas
if we aren't all together!
Family must be together at Christmas!
That's exactly right...
Oh yes... I have a present for us also!
Here!
A trip to Egypt!
Catalogue
Special Prize
Trip to Egypt
I won it in a lottery!
That's amazing, mama!
We'll be in Egypt on New Year!
All right!
It's Egypt!
Oh, Mr. Tokuda, I'm sorry...
This is apparently only for family.
Of course it's so...
Well then! Let's start the
Christmas party all together!
That's right! I'm so hungry!
Let's do that!
♪ Jingle bells, jingle bells... ♫
♪ Jingle all the way! ♫
♪ O what fun it is to ride in a one-horse open sleigh. ♫
♪ Hey! Jingle bells, jingle bells... ♫
Hey, Mario...
So for Kouta, his papa and
mama are Santa Claus?
But I heard that Santa Claus doesn't exist?
No! He does!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Everyone, do you have plans for winter vacation?
We're in Egypt currently!
There's big pyramids in the vast desert!
They're the perfect places to explore!
The sphinx is attacking us!
What are you so angry about?
I see! This is a treasure!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Great Adventure at the Pyramids
Is there an alien in your home, too?