Brave         Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Run! Supercar
How did it manage not to crash?
That scared me!
So cool!
Big brother!
Big brother?
Kotomi-chan, you came to watch?
Sheesh, I thought my heart was going to stop!
If I'd crash in something like that, I wouldn't be able to race.
Yeah, that's right!
The upcoming Figure Eight Race is on a completely different level compared to this mediocre circuit.
It's a really tough course with rocky ground and marshland in it!
Hm? Are these your friends?
Yes, they're Kouta-kun and Takumi-kun.
Good day!
This is my cousin, Shuntarou.
He's an university student, but he doesn't go to school and plays around with the motorcars all day.
Hey, come on now!
What's up with that introduction?
But it's all true!
Oh you!
I'm no match for Kotomi-chan!
Are those people also participating in the Figure Eight Race?
Yeah.
There's so many!
Everyone is aiming for the championship.
Although, we're the ones who'll win.
That's right!
We'll see about that! It might be a little impossible.
Why?
Because our car is participating in it, too!
Your car?
Yup, my father's team bought the
best supercar in the world!
Look at this!
These lovely curves!
This beauty of functions!
This is its first appearance in Japan.
It's the best race car in the world, Bellini!
Its high speed is 450 km/hr!
The maximum output is 1000 kW!
Including its past championship wins,
it's literally the world's best race car!
So nice! So nice!
I can't get enough of the specialty of this design.
I'd love to have one too...
Mr. Tokuda!
Don't touch it with your filthy hands!
My Bellini will get dirty!
Your?
Are you the owner of this car?
Let me ask a few things too! Hey!
Well, it's that, you know?
Even if one would search through the whole world, there wouldn't be any car as wonderful as this.
In other words, this car is my treasure!
No! It's the treasure of the motor racing world!
Treasure?
Tsukiyama Motorcar Repair Shop
Old man! Hide!
A newspaper reporter came to write about us!
What?
Hello!
Kouta-kun, so what's the candidate car for winning the Figure Eight Race...?
It's that!
Eh?! This shabby-...
Ow ow ow!
Go ahead!
Don't be reserved, write an article or whatever you like!
It really is a good car,
but Takumi-kun's Bellini sure
makes it look second-rate...
That's enough!
Shun!
I know that it's the best car in the world!
But a race has more put into it
than just the car's abilities!
Above all, the passion you have for machines is what matters!
Its appearance might be shabby...
But this machine is filled with
our passion for racing!
All of our youth is poured into it!
Well said, Shuntarou.
I absolutely won't lose!
No way I'll lose to that monster car,
that only has lots of money used in it!
Let's do it, Mr. Shuntarou!
Yeah!
What an amazing passion...
Kotomi-chan and Mr. Tokuda were both surprised!
Mr. Shuntarou had such great passion!
Does he want to win the race so badly, that he becomes that serious?
It's not a bad thing to do something with the utmost effort.
Do you have something like that, Exkaiser?
I'm giving my utmost effort in
capturing those Geisters!
I see!
If an outsider complains about something that I'm risking my life to do,
then I would get angry like Shuntarou-kun too.
Yeah.
I think it's something like that when you're serious about fulfilling your dreams to your best.
As expected from the leader of Kaisers, you sure say some nice things!
It's Dash Max!
That Bellini is getting adjusted
right next to me currently.
I'll dash right past that kinda car!
Are you participating too, Dash Max?
I'm a race car too, after all!
Sorry, but I'll be getting the championship!
W-What is that?
Oh, oops!
Please don't get worked up so much that you'll reveal your true self.
I know already!
The starting time of the 23th Figure Eight Race is getting closer!
There's a total of 47 participants!
At the pole position's no. 1 mark is the Kaneari team's Bellini!
None of the teams are doing a final check-up of their machines before starting.
Figure Eight Rally
The race begins here at the center of the figure eight in the Tsukudani circuit.
The road goes past the rocky ground and through the center again,
then over the marshland and river,
then returning back to the goal in the center.
It's a very tough course.
Figure Eight Race is starting soon!
It's finally starting!
How about it? Do I look good?
Takumi-kun!
What's up with that outfit?
Thanks to the authority of being owner, I'm going to be the navigator of Bellini.
What's a navigator?
It's a very important duty where I tell the time and the course from the passenger seat.
Young sir, it's the time soon...
Yeah.
Well then, everyone! Let's meet at the podium.
Young sir doesn't have to do anything.
Just sit calmly.
It started!
Big brother, do your best!
And now, they started all at once!
Which team will bask in the championship glory of this Figure Eight Race?
As expected, the Kaneari team's Bellini is the first one to break away!
The next one is a private team's Tsukiyama no. 5!
Amazing! It isn't losing to Bellini!
See now? That's why I told you!
Alright, I'll follow them with chief editor's car to gather information!
Cars are crashing in a row to the spun racer!
The course is blocked!
The Figure Eight Race is extremely exciting!
H-Hit the brake!
No one is able to stop me!
Piece of cake!
This is amazing, the no. 7 car!
He avoided crashing with a great jump!
Amazing!
Sheesh, Dash Max!
If you drive too showy, you'll reveal yourself!
I'll go steal that supercar.
You three should block those cars that come from the back.
Don't take the glory all by yourself, though.
I know!
Did I take the wrong route?
I can't drive on such a bumpy road...
Watch out!
We'll crash!
That was a close call!
Hey! Somebody save me!
Oh sheesh...
Here they come!
Do your best, big brother!
The top cars have just now passed the middle point!
Is Bellini going to be at the top position again in this Tsukudani circuit?
Or will it be Tsukiyama no. 5?
It's currently a very intense racing situation!
W-What's that?
Something appeared!
Help me!
Damn!
This is awful!
Suddenly a strange trailer appeared on the course!
This is no attraction! This is an intrusion!
Don't let it escape!
Chase the treasure!
Big brother!
We can't just stand around. Let's go!
Exkaiser, Geisters appeared!
I got it, I'll come immediately!
Huh?
The car... The car is gone!
Those are Geisters!
Damn you Geisters!
Change, Dash Max!
You bastard are... Dash Max!
You damn villains!
The long-awaited race is ruined now!
Like we care!
I won't forgive you!
The race has completely stopped due to the
sudden appearance of mysterious giant robots!
Is there any chance for resumption?
Big brother!
Did you get hurt?
Yeah...
My arm won't move!
It's impossible to continue the race, huh...
Dammit!
How can such idiocy happen!
All because of them...!
But without a navigator...
Let me do it!
It'll be alright!
Since Takumi is doing it too!
You will...?
We're not just playing around, okay?
Yes!
Be careful, Kouta-kun!
Let's go!
After 200 m, we'll arrive to the marshland.
Got it!
We haven't gotten apart too much...
We're able to catch up!
You're better at this than I thought.
We'll get caught!
Let's escape already, the race is cancelled!
The only escape route is this way.
Alright, catch them in a swoop!
Who goes there?
Change, Exkaiser!
Geisters!
I won't let you bother the race that people have put their dreams in!
Talking all big!
Look at this!
Cut that Exkaiser into pieces!
Exkaiser!
Kouta!
Look out!
Smash that Exkaiser!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
Kaiser Shot!
Kaiser Kick!
Alright! Finish him off!
You bastard!
Exkaiser, now's your chance!
Alright!
Kaiser Sword!
This is bad! Let's get outta here!
Thunder Flash!
The only two cars that are continuing the race after the unexpected intrusion
are Bellini and Tsukiyama no. 5!
It's time for the duel of these two!
Mr. Shuntarou, it really is great to put your utmost effort into something!
I think I understand it now somehow!
Huh? Did you say something?
Racing is really interesting!
That's why I can't stop it!
Tsukiyama no. 5 is getting faster and faster!
They're crazy fast at the last corner!
They almost crashed!
Tsukiyama no. 5 managed to level the car!
Now, which one will rush to the goal first?
Goal! Goal!
The championship goes to Tsukiyama No. 5 !
The runner-up is Kaneari team's Bellini!
You did it, Shun!
Nice run!
You both are cool!
Yay!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
There's an amazing computer in my city.
It makes the traffic lights change, manages that trains don't collide and everything else too!
Thanks to it, we can also play new TV games at home immediately!
Eh? That computer got stolen?
If that's true, then the city will be in chaos!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Protect the Computer
Is there an alien in your home, too?