Brave         Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Become the Wind, White Horse
Today's main race is the Rothenburg Special!
They've ran all the laps and now it's finally time for the decisive moments!
All horses turn from the 4th corner and now it's a straight way!
At the lead is...
Oh! How can this be!
It's the 12th most popular, Masakausso!
What an unexpected race development!
That's good, Masakausso!
Chief editor, this is one of the sleepers!
Oh, Super Ace is advancing!
It's striving so much!
So fast! It goes past 5 horses in a flash and is now in lead!
The one on the reins is Takara Yutaka!
Super Ace puts distance between him and Masakausso as usual and arrives to goal!
It's truly the white lighting! The young genius rider is Takara Yutaka!
The fans' prince, Takara Yutaka!
He did it! As expected from Takara Yutaka!
Damn, I lost... Goddamn it!
Papa!
Why are you making so much noise?
No... Um...
Oh no...
Ah! Mr. Takara!
So wonderful! I can't get enough!
Fuuko, do you know Takara Yutaka?
Of course!
Takara Yutaka is the most popular super idol at the moment!
See, chief editor? It's as I said, right?
The next interviewee was a right choice!
Interviewee?
Could it be Takara Yutaka?
Yeah, I'm going to meet him at the ranch.
Really?
Papa, take me with you!
But it's for work...
That doesn't matter! Don't be so strict!
Kouta wants to go too, right? Say yes...
Yes, yes...
We could have a picnic at the ranch!
Let's all go!
That's a good idea!
A picnic while working!
Idiot! Work is work!
But since the ranch is vast,
a picnic would be quite nice, mama...
I can meet Takara Yutaka!
H-Hey, can we perhaps ride a horse?
Of course you can! It's a ranch, after all!
Really?
Yahoo!
Wondrous 9 consecutive victories!
It's Takara Yutaka who has once again showed us his overwhelming powers!
Horse racing?
It's just humans riding on horses.
How is this a treasure?
You fool!
That many humans are making a fuss over it!
It must have a high value!
The ones we want are Takara Yutaka and this horse!
Don't fail again!
... Is what Lord Dino Geist said!
I won't be joining this.
Four legged animals aren't my style!
So you got scared?
Nonsense!
I'm saying that there's no need for me to go for something like that!
You cheeky-...!
Now, now... Let's stop fighting among ourselves.
You stay out of this!
Alright, I'll do it! Thunder, let's go!
Me too?
Training Center
Are you alright? You aren't scared?
I'm fine!
Be careful!
A horse's back is pretty high up...
Mario, no! Go away!
Mario, stop that!
Kouta!
Someone! Save me!
I'm scared! Help me!
Are you alright?
Yes...
Mr. Takara Yutaka!
Oh, thank you very much!
No problem...
Horses are gentle animals so that
doesn't usually happen, but...
Kouta-kun! I hope you don't think
that horses are scary.
I-I don't think that way...
Um, please let me interview you!
Are you feeling confident for the next Sunrise Cup?
I'll win it of course!
As long as I have this Super Ace,
I definitely won't lose to other horses.
Unbelievable that I can see him this close...
Mr. Takara is so cool and gentle...
Mr. Takara! Things won't go your way.
Takumi!
Why are you here?
Well, everyone, just look at this!
Money Maker!
That's right!
Papa bought this world's fastest
thoroughbred in France.
This is amazing!
But it won't win against Super Ace!
No, Kouta-kun...
Money Maker is the most powerful rival candidate.
That's right!
Specialized food, gorgeous sanatorium and super top-class training done by a super top-class trainer.
We've spend many billions on this one horse,
so it'd be ridiculous if we didn't win!
Well then, everyone!
Let's meet at the racecourse!
Ciao!
Mr. Takara! Don't lose to them and do your best!
Of course!
Oh yeah, Kouta-kun! Would you like to ride Super Ace once more?
I'll teach you the wonderfulness of horses!
Are you serious, Mr. Takara?
Please!
Me too...
Why does Kouta get all the attention...
That's it!
I'll also make a horse bolt and
Mr. Takara will come save me!
Oh, Fuuko!
Come on, bolt!
Come on! Hurry!
You just can't get a clue...
What's that horse?
I heard that this horse is called Hoshikawa Honour!
It's the same as our name!
Now that you mention it,
it kind of looks like chief editor.
How dare you!
I don't make the horse run.
I become one with the horse, so I'm running too.
Become one with the horse?
When mine and this guy's feelings combine,
both me and Super Ace can use our greatest powers!
And at that time, I'll become the wind too.
Kouta-kun, hang on tight!
You'll become the wind too!
Become the wind?
That's right!
He said that when human and horse become one, they become the wind!
I see...
Isn't it cool?
I'm now a big fan of Mr. Takara!
Cheer him well!
Yeah!
I want Super Ace to win again at the Sunrise Cup!
Don't you agree, Mario?
Tokyo Racecourse
They've passed the 4th corner and the most popular Nabekumin is in lead.
The one behind him is the the
2nd most popular Aikoujou!
Will the two favorites be winning this race?
Will they be overtook... No!
The two horses keep on going!
Nabekumin and Aikoujou arrive to goal!
Goddamn it! Favorites again!
You'll never win if you keep on
betting on those sleepers.
The sleepers must be bet!
Isn't that the best part about horse racing?
Hey, papa...
You've been talking about favorites and sleepers
for a while now, but what are those?
Kids don't need to know that!
What? Do you know then, sister?
Of course!
In brief, favorite is Mr. Takara!
Although J. Loan was my favorite a while ago...
Sleepers are... Well, something like Mr. Tokuda.
What are you saying?
Favorites are horses that have
the highest chance of winning.
Sleepers are the opposite.
They're horses that don't look like they'd win.
I see... So Mr. Takara really is a favorite.
He's a great favorite!
Papa, isn't it Mr. Takara's turn yet?
Seems like it isn't yet.
Maybe he's coming to the
paddock soon. Go take a look!
What's the paddock?
It's the place where they show
the horses before the race.
Let's go, Kouta!
Yeah!
Mr. Takara!
The 10th race.
1600 meters with 4 year old horses!
They have started!
In the lead is the fastest one to
break away, Chiakimori!
This time my sleeper will win!
It's a very steep turn!
They're going to the 2nd corner!
W-What's that?
Treasure!
Is it a horse monster that appeared
near the 2nd corner?
W-What?
Geister!
Treasure!
Wait!
The race is still continuing, but the horse monster has joined it too!
I'm fast!
H-He arrived to goal!
Unbelievably the 1st place is...!
T-This is terrible!
Chief editor! What'll happen to
this horse ticket now-...
Idiot! Just get to work already!
I'm 1st place!
You dumbass!
It's not the time to be playing!
Mr. Takara!
You're so cool!
Sister, something seems to be wrong.
Shut up! Can't you see that I'm busy at the moment?
Where's the treasure?
Geisters!
Kouta, we must escape quickly!
There it is!
Treasure!
You won't escape!
Mr. Takara is...!
What's wrong, Kouta?
Exkaiser, it's terrible!
Geisters came to the racecourse!
Alright, I got it! I'll come immediately!
Hurry!
Wait!
You won't escape anymore!
Mr. Takara, over here!
Kouta-kun!
Hurry! Hurry!
Tsk, they went to the underground!
I'll do it!
Mr. Takara, look out!
I got them!
Alright! Good job!
What's wrong?
I can't get my hand out...
This time I got saved!
Kouta-kun, thank you!
No need to...
What the heck are you doing?
I can't get it out!
Change!
What?
I got it out!
Y-You bastard!
You villainous Geisters!
It's unforgivable that you're trying to steal the enjoyment of people!
Just give up obediently!
Shut up!
Damn monster!
We are your opponents!
Take this!
Well then! Go steal the treasure!
Wait!
No you don't!
Damn you!
Good job!
Exkaiser!
D-Dammit!
Now it's your turn!
Do it!
See what happens!
Today we'll give you plenty of our
thanks for all the earlier times!
Take this!
Your luck ran out when you came here alone!
Exkaiser!
Serves you right!
Dragon Jet!
What?
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, Dragon Kaiser!
I need to save those three first...
So that's the part that controls the tentacles!
Dragon Archery!
Thunder Arrow!
Damn!
Go on! You must hurry now!
Thank you!
Do your best, Dragon Kaiser!
Come on, monster!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Super Giant Fusion, Great Exkaiser!
Kaiser Sword!
This is bad! Let's leave!
Thunder Crash!
He did it!
It's finally time for the big Sunrise Cup race.
Here are the tremendously popular Takara Yutaka's Super Ace,
and Money Maker who'll try stop his 10th consecutive victory!
The highlight of Sunrise Cup could
be the battle between these two!
All horses start at once!
Give it your all, Super Ace!
Mr. Takara!
Money Maker, don't lose!
The horses go from the 3rd corner to the 4th corner!
Oh! Super Ace is taking lead!
Money Maker isn't going to lose!
Money Maker restrained Super Ace and took the lead!
Super Ace!
Money Maker!
Super Ace dashes!
He passes Money Maker and
puts distance between them!
Super Ace is strong! It's truly the white lightning!
He arrived to goal!
And the 2nd place is...
Oh! That horse is...!
Hoshikawa Honor is 2nd place!
Mr. Takara did it!
No way... My Money Maker was...
Mr. Takara! I love you!
C-Chief editor...
Isn't Hoshikawa Honor a sleeper
for getting to 2nd place...?
Good for you that it was a sleeper!
No such thing!
I bet all my money on Super Ace
and Money Maker in this race!
Dear, did I do well if Mr. Takara is in 1st place
and Hoshikawa Honor is in 2nd place?
M-Mama! Mama, you hit the jackpot!
Madam, you bet on a horse like Hoshikawa Honor?
Well, it has such a nice name!
Oh?
Wait!
Come back!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
I'm going to board a space shuttle!
It's only a practice one, though...
But before that, various training has to be done.
It's so very tough!
But I'll do my best!
Huh? Something's strange here...
Whoa! We got confined in the shuttle!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Aim to Be a Space Pilot
Is there an alien in your home, too?