Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
This mysterious and boundless Universe...
Earth is but one tiny planet where life is known to exist.
The humans don't know it yet....
But there is a battle between good and evil for the peace of the cosmos...
Boss! This planet looks like fun!
Looks like non one has touched it yet...
Judging from its appearances, humans' greed is whirpooling.
I like this place!
There are swarms of humans there! There'll be a huge amount of treasures, too!
That's right.
Something that space pirates like us Geisters take a fancy to...
First let's look around. We need to find suitable bodies!
Yeah!
Those scum... they're taking refuge on this planet!
This is Exkaiser of the cosmic police.
The Geisters have taken refuge on Earth.
Requesting backup!
Our Family Car is an Alien!?
Today's field trip!
Thank god, clear skies...
Thank you~
Brrrr! Cold!
I gotta pee.
Huh? What's that?
What!?
I wonder what that could be?
Why, a dream!
Holy crap! Nee-chan!
Nee-chan, big problems! Wake up!
What is it... you're so noisy...
Lightning hit the garage!
You were just dreaming. Go pee and let me sleep.
I'm telling the truth!
Shaddup!
Lemme sleep!
Mario!? Don't scare me!
Mario, you saw that light?
Shhh! Don't bark!
Mario, if you see anything, tell me. I'll take a picture and then we'll run away!
Huh... there's nothing here.
Weird...
What is it, Mario?
What? There's nothing here.
I guess it was just a dream...
I forgot!
Ah! I gotta pee! I can't hold it!
Mario! Hurry up or I'll pee right here!
Kouta, wake up. You're going to be late.
Let me sleep a bit more...
You have a field trip today, right? I made you a lunch box for that...
Are you going to eat at home?
Oh no! I forgot!
Papa, aren't you the Editor in Chief of that newspaper?
It's nice that you're enthusiastic about your work, but that's not an ashtray.
Oh! Oopsie!
Mama, did Kouta wet his bed?
Why?
Last night he created such a ruckus with his babbling about lightning hitting the garage....
Lightning struck it?
Is the car all right, mama?
Don't worry. He was just half asleep at the time.
Oh well.
Morning!
Kouta, did you wet your bed?
Wet my bed?
Don't you know?
I ain't no bed wetter!
-Oh really?
-I ain't!
Good morning!
Excuse me!
It's Tokuda-san!
(Note: Tokuda comes from 'tokudane' meaning 'scoop')
I bet he'll offer a scoop that everyone knows already...
Chief! Have I got a scoop for you!
Knew it.
No other newspaper knows about this yet! It's my own scoop!
And what is it this morning?
Let me explain...
Oh, look at that. Mind if I have a bite?
Delicious!
Tokuda-san, if you'd like, I have plenty left, so please help yourself.
Thank you! I'll take some!
-What did you come here for?
-Huh?
Ah! That's right! Let me tell you...
A museum and a research institute...
...both had cases of disappearing full-scale dinosaur models!
Dinosaur models?
So far, there are 4 missing.
This is my own scoop that I'll investigate!
Four full-scale dinosaur models have gone missing from the museum, the research facility and the amusement park.
-This news is our station's exclusive scoop.
-Too bad! Looks like the TV reporter knows about it already.
As usual.
Tokuda-san, cheer up.
Here's more of the Tsukudani you had just before.
Is the dinosaur exhibition all right?
The dinosaur exhibition?
Yeah, I'm going on a field trip there today.
Don't worry! Theirs haven't been stolen yet.
Really? That's great!
Hmm? Dinosaur exhibition?
I'm off, mama.
Have a nice day.
-Let's go, Tokuda.
-Yes, chief!
See you!
Kouta! Hurry up!
I'm off!
Be careful!
What is it, Kouta?
No, it's nothing. Bye!
Kouta-kun sure had a great camera there.
It's a memento of his grandfather. He's always trying to take photos of scoops with it.
Again... geez!
I guess it really was a dream...
Oh, well!
It's huge...
It's incredible! I can't believe so many of these were running around back then.
That's for sure! If we were around then, we'd be eaten in one bite!
What is it, Kouta-kun?
Kotomi-chan, didn't this dinosaur just move?
Eh? Impossible!
What is it, Kotomi-chan?
Takumi-kun! Kouta-kun said this dinosaur just moved!
I'm sure I saw it move when I was framing.
That dinosaur got mad at you for looking at him through an old camera like that!
There's nothing wrong with its age!
But there is.
We don't call those "camera" anymore.
Cameras are now like this!
Auto-focus, auto-zoom, everything is automatic in this state of the art camera.
Huh?
Kouta's camera is cool, too.
It is?
Old cameras are stylish!
Do you really think so?
This camera is a memento of my grandfather. It's my treasure.
That's awesome!
Hmph. Well, cameras are judged by the pictures it took.
Since it's old, don't overuse it, anyway!
What'll I do? I can't stop it! It's papa's camera...!
-Should we get going, Kotomi-chan?
-Sure!
An old camera... A treasure...
You really think this will be the next target?
I'm sure of it, Chief!
Among the places where one-to-one scale dinosaur exhibition is going on, this is the only place intact.
My scoop-sense is telling me to stake out and we'll surely get the story!
Well, it sounds reasonable.
In the meantime, I'll get an approval for coverage from the office.
Please do.
All right! Time for info!
I smell the scoop!
Allosaurus! Check!
Ankylosaurus! Check.
Iguanodon! Check.
Triceratops! Chec- huh?
T- Triceratops isn't here!
Chief! Chief!
Huh?
Isn't this the dinosaur from before?
Now that you mention it...
They might look the same but it could be a different one, right?
Since a lot of dinosaurs looked alike.
Kotomi-chan, you shouldn't get too close to it!
Why's that? It's just a model.
Look out!
W- what the-!?
Kotomi-chan! Hurry!
Kotomi-chan, are you all right?
What was that thing!?
Grandpa's camera!
Kouta-kun! Where are you going!?
If I take a picture of it, I can give the photo to papa's newspaper!
Stop! It's dangerous!
As long as I have this...
Kouta-kun!
Help me!
Why the heck is it following me!?
Why me!? Did I do something wrong!?
Hey, kid.
It- it- it spoke!
Gimme that treasure.
Treasure? This camera?
No way! This is a memento of my grandpa!
Our car...
That hurt! Who the hell are you!?
Geister, you scoundrel!
I won't allow you to practice your evil ways on this Earth!
Our car spoke!
That voice! You... you must be...!
Change! Exkaiser!
It- it turned into a robot!
You bastard...! You followed us all the way here!?
Dammit! Well, in that case...
A... awesome! That's right! A scoop!
Take this!
Now you've done it...
A... awesome!
That's right! I must take a photo!
Ah! Don't touch that!
What the hell is this!?
That's why I said not to touch it...
Take this!
Oh no!
Looking good there!
Die!
Serves you right!
Dammit! The treasure!
Now!
Bastard... You haven't dropped dead yet!?
You-!
Until the my life burns out,
I won't let evildoers like you do as they please!
Impudent scum!
Jet Boomerang!
Shit!
All right!
Damn you! The treasure broke!
Exkaiser! This battle isn't over yet!
Are you all right?
Yeah, but...
My name is Exkaiser. And you are?
I'm Hoshikawa Kouta. Exkaiser, right?
Kouta-kun! Are you all right!?
Kouta-kun!
Kouta, I don't have time to tell you all the details now.
In the meantime, please keep my existence to yourself.
In other words, this will be our secret.
W- wait!
Kouta-kun!
Kouta-kun, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Kouta-kun! Where did that robot go?
Where? It just disappeared!
It disappeared?
Did it disappear through this hole?
Just what in the world happened?
Oh, chief! It was such a scoop!
Two robots appeared and then disappeared.
What? Robots?
The dinosaur moved then became a robot!
What the hell are you talking about?
But...
Papa!
Oh, Kouta.
Did something happen?
What happened...
Chief! I'm telling you that the dinosaur robot is one of the stolen dinosaurs!
Did you take a photo?
Well, the camera was broken...
Idiot! It has already been quite some time since you became a news reporter, and you're still like that!?
Huh?
Why is your car here, chief?
Hey! Don't change the subject!
Kouta-kun, are you really all right?
I'm fine!
Kouta-kun!
My grandpa's camera must have brought me good luck!
And a new friend!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
Preview for Next Episode
Have you heard about the Linear Motor Car?
It's the fastest train in the world!
And that's what the Geisters found out!
Exkaiser! Do something! Papa and mama are on board!
Eh!? That Shinkansen is a friend of Exkaiser's!?
Next on Brave Exkaiser,
Save the Linear Motor Car!
Is there an alien in your home, too?