Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Great Shaking! At the Baseball Dome
Wow, another over the fence.
As expected from Kiyono.
Oh, Kiyono is coming.
Mr. Kiyono, tomorrow is finally the opening match. How are you feeling?
I'm in my best condition.
Just one more and you'll be beating
the home run record,
so does it mean you'll achieve it tomorrow?
Yes.
Your opponent is Naniwa Konjohs' pitcher Awahara, can you hit his pitches?
Awahara-kun will be a great opponent.
I'll definitely hit them!
Mr. Kiyono!
I'm from the Touto newspaper.
Can I have your signature?
Well, sure!
I'm so touched that I can get Mr. Kiyono's signature!
Mr. Kiyono, please let us interview you.
Mr. Kiyono has said that he'll give the world record breaking ball to the fan who picks it up.
It'll surely be the greatest treasure to the child who picks it up.
Yes, I'll be happy if someone cherishes it as a once-in-a-lifetime treasure.
Treasure...
W-What was that?
I'll tell you lord Dino Geist's next orders.
There's a new treasure!
Alright, it's a chance for us!
It's your turn next, Kouta-kun. Do your best!
Alright, I'll hit one out there and show my good sides to Kotomi-chan.
I did it! A home run!
Too bad, huh?
And just as we had the chance...!
Don't worry, there's still me.
Could that bat possibly have Kiyono's signature?
That's right, it's a bat with the signature of Kiyono from Tokyo Ganbals!
I got it with my father's connections.
With this bat, I can bring us to victory with one hit!
Well, just watch!
Takumi-kun is so eager!
But he's so bad at sports...
Even if he has a bat with Kiyono's signature...
Strike!
See?
Yeah...
Strike two!
Damn, I'll definitely hit it!
For this day, I've secretly done tough special training!
Alright, alright...
I did it!
Takumi-kun, amazing!
I can't believe it...
Now I might be able to become a professional baseball player!
Thank you!
Hey! Who was it?
Were you the one who just hit this?!
Thank you for cheering!
So Takumi-kun, you wanted to become a professional baseball player?
And specifically a home run batter.
That's why I've built a batting training facility in my home and continued my special training.
Well, from today's home run I can see it becoming true.
I don't think professional baseball is that simple.
I know, but...
I do have this talisman!
I'd love to get a signature from Kiyono, too.
If it's Kiyono's signature, I can get it too.
Really?
Yup, Mr. Tokuda promised to get me it
when he interviews him today.
Ah, speaking of the devil...
Mr. Tokuda!
Sorry, Kouta-kun! It's a lifetime blunder for me, Tokuda Osamu.
What's wrong?
I didn't get the signature.
Ehh, no way!
I don't know if this is a good apology, but forgive me with this...
Ah, these are tickets for tomorrow's match at the baseball dome!
They're outfield seats, but if you're lucky,
you just might get Kiyono's home run ball!
Really? Gimme, gimme, gimme one!
I'll let you borrow this signed bat, okay?
Well, fine.
How great! Unbelievable that I have a platinum card ticket that even my father's connections couldn't get...!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
It's the symbol of gratitude, you know. See ya!
Ah, the bat!
He's gone.
Can I?
Of course, let's go together tomorrow.
I'm so happy, this is exactly why I like you Kouta-kun!
See you tomorrow!
Kouta-kun, wasn't this better than the signed ball?
Well, yeah.
Don't be so modest, I know you're happy!
Are baseball dome tickets that important?
I'm going!
Fuuko, did you like baseball? (yakyuu)
Oh, you like fried udon? (yakiudon) But I made fried rice... (yakimeshi)
That's not it, my sister is fan of Awahara from the Naniwa Konjohs.
Oh, the pitcher Awahara?
Eh, mochi made of sweets? (abekawa mochi)
His face is so sweet, right? He's popular among the girls from school at the moment...
Fuuko, if you're so fond of sweet things, don't you care if you'll get fat?
I see.
And that's why everyone wanted the tickets?
Because it is the opening game.
I'll definitely get Kiyono's home run ball!
Kouta!
What's up with that outfit?
I'm going to cheer for Awahara like this.
Hurray, hurray, Awahara!
But what were you doing here?
I just came to take the glove...
Never mind that thing, let's get going.
We're going already?
Of course, if we don't go early, we won't get good seats.
Kotomi-chan's here already, too.
Really? Well then, I'll be going!
Oh, Mario was there.
Kotomi-chan!
Kotomi-chan, that outfit is...?
Kotomi-chan's also a fan of Awahara, you know.
I'm just too happy to see Awahara in the opening match.
That's it! Come on, come on, Awahara! Strike out that Kiyono!
Baseball, huh? It seems very interesting, I'd love to see it once.
What the...?!
Hey, are you that Kiyono?
Where's the treasure called home run or something?
That's...!
Huh? Why did it stop?
I see, it's not here then?
Those Geisters, what are they planning?
What? Honegaist appeared?
Yes, he appeared on a ground where they were playing a sports called baseball, and then he disappeared quickly.
Baseball?
Yeah. Fortunately there were no victims.
Got it. Anyway, thanks for the report.
Just what are they planning? It couldn't be...!
I'll definitely get Kiyono's home run ball
and bring it back home!
You sure? I've come prepared properly.
What's that puny thing? I brought this with me.
I ordered it especially to get Kiyono's home run ball.
W-What does that matter? I won't lose to you!
Awahara, you're so cool!
This year's opening game is finally starting.
Naniwa Konjohs' pitcher is popular for his sweet face, the very talented Awahara.
And the 4th batter of Tokyo Ganbals who's made his goal to make a world record of home runs, Kiyono.
We're excited to see their duel.
So that's the baseball dome?
Now that we're at it, let's take the whole thing.
That could be interesting. Alright, let's go.
Those were Geisters!
Blue Raker, can you hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you.
I think I figured out their target, they're going to-...
Wait a bit!
Sheesh, there's no parking allowed here!
Violation!
This sucks...
What's wrong?
Nothing. Looks like the Geisters are targeting baseball.
Contact Green Raker immediately and come to the baseball dome.
Roger!
Alright, the baseball dome is right in front of us.
Finally it's time for Awahara vs Kiyono.
It's their fourth duel.
Kiyono has been struck out today, but if he can hit this one, It'll be their comeback.
It's an important hit that would break the home run world record.
He's going against Awahara,
who will try his best to stop Kiyono.
The situation is getting more heated every moment!
I'm so excited!
Kiyono, hit it!
Do it, do it, Awahara! Blast off that Kiyono!
Strike!
What is this?
An earthquake!
What?
This is way too easy.
Let's take this back now.
I won't let you do that!
Change, Exkaiser!
Disrupting the peace on Earth, you awful Geisters!
Now that I'm here, you won't succeed!
So you appeared, Exkaiser.
Do it! Crush him!
It stopped, what a strange earthquake...
It really was...
It couldn't be...
Where are you going?
To the bathroom for a bit.
Could it be that you almost peed your pants due to the earthquake?
That's not it!
Exkaiser!
Now that the earthquake has stopped, we'll continue the game.
This time, I'll hit it for sure!
No way you'll hit it!
He hit it! It's flying very far!
Will it be within boundaries?
It's a foul!
An earthquake! There's another earthquake!
What could be going on?
Exkaiser, sorry we're late!
Change, Blue Raker!
Change, Green Raker!
Raker Brothers!
Blue Raker! Green Raker!
Leave this to us.
Go rescue the baseball dome!
Got it!
Kill them!
Form up!
Left&Right Fusion, Ultra Raker!
King Loader!
Form up!
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
This isn't good.
Going to the side and falling down, what a strange earthquake!
What're you doing? Hurry up and defeat him!
King Exkaiser!
Thanks, Ultra Raker!
Kaiser Blaster!
Ultra Shoulder Crash!
Now's the chance!
Kaiser Sword!
Kaiser Flame!
What're you standing around? Let's withdraw!
Thunder Flash!
He did it!
Kouta, you were watching?
I had no idea the Geisters were targeting the baseball dome!
I didn't want the baseball match be cancelled,
since you all were looking forward to it so much.
It's best not to tell about this to everyone inside.
We wouldn't want to ruin their long-awaited pleasure.
Thank you, Exkaiser.
Although the earthquakes have stopped, they're having a discussion whether or not continue the match.
Announcement to everyone, due to those rather sporadic earthquakes,
we've decided it's impossible to continue,
this match is cancell-...
No! This long-awaited match has to continue!
That's right! That's right!
The match should continue!
Continue it!
Continue!
Let's continue the game!
Yeah, the score isn't settled yet!
We beg you!
Please let us continue!
As our discussion's result, the match shall continue!
Great!
Kiyono, hit the ball right here!
And now, the match finally continues.
Will we see a world record home run?
Or can Awahara shut him down and make this opening game his own?
I absolutely won't...
Let you hit it!
I'm gonna hit it!
Strike! Batter out!
Amazing...
Awahara! You're wonderful!
Thank you for the great game.
Nah, I should be thanking you!
But one day I'll definitely hit a world record from you.
Bring it on!
So cool! This was truly a duel between men.
That was great, Awahara!
Good job, Kiyono!
I've decided, I'll become a pitcher!
Eh? Wasn't it the home run batter?
I'll be the best pitcher in Japan!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
We'll be having a play in the ancient ruins soon!
Kotomi-chan is the princess and I'm the prince!
But I can't remember my lines, so I'm troubled.
Kids in the past probably didn't have these sort of worries.
Huh? There's Exkaiser's picture inside the golden coffin!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Great Discovery at the Ancient Ruins
Is there an alien in your home, too?