Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He's the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
The Pharmacy is Empty!?
"Mysterious Robot Attacks Rocket"!?
Idiot!
This isn't a grade school newspaper!
But chief!
Didn't you see them as well?
You blockhead!
I told you that unless we have a photographic proof, I don't want it in the newspaper!
But my camera was--
Shut up! I've had it with your excuses!
Next time this happens, I'll take three months of your pay!
That's right... I'm on the short end of the stick...
Never give up! Scoop is my name, and scoop is my game!
MAGMA MAGMA MAGMA MAGMA MAGMA
And if I have these, I'll be number one in Japan!
Very Very Power Up!
Joanna...
I love you...
It's getting better...
-Please! Let this pass!
-If we keep doing like this...
Hey, you jerks! How long are you going to sit around!?
What did you say!?
...is what Dino Geist-sama told me to say.
Didn't he instruct us to gather information on this planet?
-Yeah, that's why we stole TVs first--hmm?
-When you're feeling down...
...take Magma Drink and Power Up!
Very Very!
Power Up!
Gulp gulp gulp gulp gulp
Magma Power!
Take Magma Drink and Very Very Power Up!
Hey, if we had that...
and we'd be Very Very Power Up!
Alright, let's go get it!
Eh!? Onee-chan caught a cold?
Mama, bring me more covers!
Really? Shouldn't you be cooling down?
Cool down? That's nonsense!
I can't help it that I'm shivering with cold!
I think I should call the doctor...
It's fine! When you catch cold, you'd better stay warm and sweat a lot,
and that will bring down the fever and lessen my weight, too!
Never mind that! Just bring me more covers!
Okay. Just drink up your medicine
I will!
Only three more kilos...
Onee-chan, are you alright?
Thanks to this, I'm skipping school and dieting at once! Two birds with one stone!
I wouldn't dare give up this opportunity!
So that's what this is about...
Well, I'm off!
Hey, hold it right there.
You're gonna help me with my diet!
Now, pretend you're a hot-water bottle...
Bye!
Come on, move it! You're gonna make me late!
Is it not working again?
Kouta, can you kick it from behind?
Maybe that'll help it move.
Papa, doing that will get you nowhere! Even cars might have feelings!
Don't worry about it! Just get in!
Papa doesn't mean any harm.
He really likes this car, so he wants you to keep up with the good job!
Got it?
Bye bye!
I see... Even cars have feelings...
Good, this is the place.
Alright.
Yamai Pharmacy
Earthquake!
Huh? Nothing's shaking...
Thief!
Good morning!
Everyone-
Class is cancelled today since more than half of the class called in sick--
and our class is closing down for the day.
So I ask you to study at home--
I guess Kotomi-chan is sick, too...
I see it's true what they say, that the stupid never fall ill.
Oh, really? And aren't you as bright as day!?
The cook at my estate creates nothing but A1 healthy meals.
Also, we have direct access to all the herbal medicines straight from the origin.
I'm far different from you commoners.
That's right, I should pay Kotomi-chan a visit!
Oh no!
Kotomi, hang in there!
Kotomi-chan! Are you alright!?
Kouta...
She suddenly fell ill with a fever.
A fever?
Please, you're in the way..
Scoop... Scoop... Scoop... Scoop...
Tokuda-san!
What's wrong, Kouta-kun? You look down.
Yeah... down...
Oh, right! That drink you got! You said it would cure colds and everything, right?
Oh, you mean that Magma Drink?
That's it! I could use one of those!
Well, I think you can buy them at the pharmacy over-- huh?
What was that?
Let's check it out!
Help me!
It's a scoop!
Power Up! Power Up!
Yes, this is the editorial department of Touto Newspaper.
Chief! It's a scoop!
What in the world is going on!?
It's a medicine thief!
Moreover, they're taking the whole store!
Drugstores are falling down as if they're being eaten from inside!
Ahhhh, there goes another one!
This is the eighth one! Every drugstore in the vicinity is under attack!
Tokuda, you aren't sleepwalking again, are you?
Chief! This is a real scoop!
I bet some alien race fell sick and has to steal all our medicine.
You weren't doing your job and watched some sci-fi videos, right?
Chief! I'm not lying!
Moron! No human could plow through the Earth!
Drugstore? Something humans can't do?
Sounds like...
Well?
I don't feel anything...
It can't be! Maybe we should drink more!
Hey, gimme one!
Screw you! I stole these.
I want to try one for myself.
Someone as brainless as you probably doesn't have anything to power up...
What!?
If you end up drinking all the treasures,
that won't get us anywhere!
...is what Dino Geist-sama said.
Dino Geist-sama has an order.
Take much more.
There must be a location where they create such things.
I see! And that's why he's the boss!
Leave this one to me...
Asahidai General Hospital
Nurse, will Kotomi-chan be alright?
Of course! As long as she takes her medicine and gets plenty of rest, she'll be fine.
But all the drugstores in the city were attacked...
There's a drugstore in the hospital, you know.
There is?
Fuuko!
Fuuko! Fuuko! Fuuko!
Fuuko! Are you alright?
Papa? What about your work?
I was told that Fuuko was brought to the hospital...
It's just a simple cold. Looks like she overheated herself.
Diet... Only 3 more kilograms...
Fuuko, get a hold of yourself!
The pharmacy...
Eh!? This was where the medicine was!?
How could this happen...
Is there any way to replenish the medicine in storage?
I have no idea, but every pharmacy that supplies us hasn't re-stocked yet...
Eh? Then what about Kotomi-chan?
Damn those Geisters...
Sky Max! I'm checking out every location hit.
Don't lag behind!
Ha! You're one to talk!
This type of situation is definitely the work of the Geisters.
Seems they're after this "medicine" thing...
Every place selling that was completely wiped out.
So that leaves us with the source of the medicine.
Kouta...?
Exkaiser! Take me to the pharmaceutical plant!
To the pharmaceutical plant?
I have to get medicine. Please!
But it's dangerous.
Dangerous?
That's right. I'm sure the Geisters will attack the pharmaceutical plant.
You can take care of the Geisters, right?
If I don't get the medicine, Kotomi-chan might die!
Please, Exkaiser!
Hey, Exkaiser...
This boy knows who we are?
Exkaiser?
He is my comrade, Dash Max.
Hello.
Boy! Leave this to us!
Exkaiser!
OK, get in..
From the pharmacy to the hospital...
I bet they'll hit the pharmaceutical plant next.
Yes, what a brilliant deduction!
Maybe I should become a detective instead!
They really came!
So, which one is the Very Very Power Up?
Screw this! We'll take 'em all!
Alright! Rip 'em all off!
This is amazing!
It's a scoop! It's a scoop! Scoop!
All the medicine is being stolen!
Exkaiser!
-All right! We know what to do!
-Boy, leave this to us!
Change, Exkaiser!
Change, Dash Max!
Geisters! We Kaisers will not allow you to proceed with your evil plans!
Damn you, Exkaiser! You had to show up!
I have crossed the galaxy to capture all of you...
You won't get away!
Shut up!
Don't think we'll come quietly...
Well, make your move!
Then, here we come... Do it!
Exkaiser!
-Now's our chance.
-Right!
No! The medicine tank!
Exkaiser!
What!?
Change, Sky Max!
Just a bit more for my scoop! Scoop!
Sorry about that we're late!
What do you mean? You saved us.
Leave this one to me!
Right. Take care of it, Exkaiser!
Drill Max! Let's go!
Right!
Hey now! You'll fight with me!
Change, Drill Max!
The Max Team assembles!
Screw you all!
Max Team, Form Up!
Triple Fusion, God Max!
That's it! Get those Geisters!
Ah! The scoop turned into a bigger scoop!
All of you're going down altogether! Get them!
I'm next in the ring!
Exkaiser! Now!
King Loader!
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
Kaiser Sword!
Thunder Flash!
Dammit!
Alright!
I finally took it! I finally got a scoop! Yay!
This is a rain of Magma Drink!
Is it pouring out for my celebration?
-Kouta! Hurry and get the medicine.
-I will!
Doctor! Here's the medicine!
Thank you! That will just do.
-Give this to Kotomi-chan.
-Yes.
Now everyone should be safe thanks to this.
You must be worried about Fuuko-san as well..
Oh, right! My sister was brought here, too.
I don't need any medicine... My diet...
No way! I gained!
I finally got a scoop!
Ta-da!
Huh? What!? It didn't work!
That can't be!
I failed again.
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
I'm on a date with Kotomi-chan in a submarine!
And we're gonna see a sunken ship that's full of treasure!
Isn't that romantic?
Uwah! The Geisters again!
Ah! They're causing an undersea eruption!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Our Sunken Ship Expedition Party
Is there an alien in your home, too?