Brave         Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He's the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Danger Turns Round and Round
at the Amusement Park!
Be quiet! Be quiet!
This is exactly why you can't win against the Kaisers.
You've been defeated several times,
how can you still watch TV without any worries?
You fools!
What did you say?
... Is what lord Dino Geist said.
Put more effort into it, more effort!
Hmph, what's up with "more effort"? How boring.
And now, the next news story.
Due to these last 7 years, the amusement park that has given children joy, the nostalgic Star Land
is finally going to shut down this month.
Star Land was built a hundred years ago
in order to give joy to people,
but it couldn't catch up with the latest high technique, and lately there hadn't been any visitors even in the holidays.
Although eras go past,
the shut down of Star Land with a hundred years of history is still a rather sad occurrence.
This can be of use.
This run-down amusement park was still operating, huh?
I thought it had fallen apart years ago.
It's unbelievable that it'll be closed this month.
I agree, it's a little sad...
It feels like we're going to lose our playground.
If there were more kids like you,
this Star Land wouldn't have to close down!
Mister, what's wrong?
It's been 50 years since Star Land was left in my care,
I never would've thought this would happen in my lifetime.
Ah, sheesh...
Why did we have to come to this shabby amusement park on a day with such a good weather?
I'm going back alrea-....
Mama, do you remember that Ferris wheel?
Yes, I do remember.
At the highest point it broke down and stopped,
and then you did that...
That failure was scary.
I felt like we can't get back alive,
so I thought if I don't say it now, I'll never have the chance.
Miss Youko, would you marry me?
Mr. Jinnichi...
To think that the Ferris wheel is going to disappear...
Will you ride it with me once more?
Yes, I'd be happy to.
In other words, without this junk...
If there hadn't been Star Land,
papa wouldn't have proposed to mama...
And then perhaps, I wouldn't have been born...
Seems like this Star Land's machines have given great joy to people for a long time.
And with this, today's work is finished.
Hm?
W-What could that be?
My...
Good morning! I'm from the Touto Newspaper.
Huh? You've already cleared the place?
And just when I came to interview you...
No, they were stolen!
Stolen?
Who would stole from such a run-down amusement park?
Run-down you say?
You called this historic Star Land run-down?
No, um, I didn't mean it like that...
Star Land has brought people joy for a hundred years,
and you dare call it run-down...
I didn't say it with such a deep meaning...
If it's not a deep meaning, then what is it?
Uh... I'm sorry! Manager, don't cry anymore, please!
I'm back!
I'm back...
What's wrong, mama?
Star Land disappeared.
Eh, why? Isn't it supposed to be still open this month?
I didn't mean that. It's not closed, but it got stolen.
Who would steal such big things?
It must be Geisters.
Oh yes, a foreign wrestler just might've stolen them.
Mama, it's alright.
Star Land will definitely be back.
Will be back?
That's right, I should cheer up and do some cleaning!
The amusement park was stolen?
I heard that most of the machinery is gone.
That reminds me, I got a strange report from Blue Raker.
A strange report?
He saw a freight car with all different sized machines on it.
That's it! Those were the stolen amusement park machines.
Blue Raker, please respond!
I hear you very clearly, Exkaiser.
Could you investigate the whereabouts of those machines you saw?
Roger, I'll start investigating immediately.
Alright, then we should go search too-...
This is bad, my mama is outside.
That means we can't go out.
How troublesome, we can't waste any time.
I understand. I'll distract mama so you can sneak outside in the meantime.
Oh, is there a visitor?
There's no one here...
How strange.
Was it just my imagination?
Couldn't the scoop just come running to me once in a while...
Ah, a Shinkansen train!
That's right, kid. That's the Toukaidou Shinkansen...
Eh! No way it could be running here!
No film, install film.
F-Film! Film... Where's the film...
There it is.
It's gone.
My scoop...
Where did they disappear?
This reaction is...?
Change! Blue Raker!
A reaction from deep within those mountains, huh?
Change, Horn Geist!
Change, Ptera Geist!
Change, Armor Geist!
Change, Thunder Geist!
Can we really win against the Kaisers by doing this?
Of course, we'll become stronger by training!
Alright!
How dare those guys...
Crap...
Who's there?
Come out!
You are Blue Raker!
All of you Geisters villains,
how dare you turn the Star Land, that's filled with people's memories, into props of evil!
I, Blue Laker, won't forgive you!
Enough talking!
Bind Crash!
Oh no, I hurt a machine from Star Land!
I see, that's it! If we use these guys as shields, he can't attack us.
Alright, then I'll go too!
Let's defeat him!
This is bad...!
That's too unfair!
I'll turn you into scrap metal!
Change, Exkaiser!
Exkaiser...
You Geisters villains,
the cosmic police Kaisers have come to arrest you!
Prepare yourselves!
Let's retreat for now, Blue Raker.
Got it.
How should we fight?
Star Land's machines are manipulated by the Geisters' energy boxes.
So, if we can destroy them, they'll go back to normal.
But just where are those energy boxes?
How can we find them if we don't even know their original form?
T-That's...
I know, Kouta!
Kouta knows Star Land well!
Ehh? Star Land has turned into robots?
That's right.
I'll come immediately, and then I'll find the energy boxes.
But...
There's no way I can explain it with words, so doing it that way is much better.
I got it, Green Raker will pick you up at the nearby station.
Leave it to me. After I've picked up Kouta-kun, I'll hurry to where you are.
Kouta-kun, board quickly!
Take this!
Impact Flash!
Spike Cutter!
Oh no, I injured the machine!
How ironic that you're getting beaten by the machines you're trying to protect!
Do it!
Seems like these guys have weakened a lot.
Step aside!
This is your end!
Kouta! Green Raker!
What?
Exkaiser!
Sorry, we're late!
Bind Crash!
Are you okay, Exkaiser?
Thanks.
We were waiting for you, little brother!
At this point I'll just use my trump card!
Do it!
Star Land combined!
Form Up!
Left&Right Fusion - Ultra Raker!
Exkaiser! Kouta-kun!
While I stop his movements, destroy the energy boxes!
It's no use, I can't see from here.
Take me on that roller coaster!
But, that's too dangerous!
No problem, I've ridden on that roller coaster many times!
Kouta!
I won't let you do that!
Oh no!
Ultra Chain Crusher!
What?
This is bad, Kouta is in danger!
King Loader!
Giant Fusion - King Exkizer!
Kouta, are you okay?
T-This is scaryyy!
You must get a grip, Kouta.
I can't, I'm too scared!
Kouta, courage! You must bring out your courage!
That is...?
That's it, that's definitely it! Alright!
Did you find them, Kouta?
Yeah, there's five in total.
I see.
Get away from it, Ultra Raker.
I got it, Kouta.
Kaiser Shot!
Kaiser Beam!
Only one left.
What? The Kaiser Shot doesn't work?
What should I do?
Guess I'll have to stake on that.
Kaiser Sword!
Thunder Flash!
The energy boxes have been destroyed. This is bad, let's escape!
We did it.
Kouta, thank you.
It's all thanks to you that Star Land got saved.
It wasn't a difficult task.
But will these ever return to normal?
I'm sorry.
I'm unable to return these memorable machines to their original state.
Is that so...
Ah, maybe it'll go well!
What will go well?
I'm talking about Star Land of course!
This is the greateeest!
Mama, this sure reminds of the old days.
Yes, although it's a little changed.
What a miracle this is.
I can hear the voices of joy again, just like before.
My... My Star Land is really back!
The manager's crying again.
It's really great that Star Land didn't have to close down.
But I wonder why they replaced the old ones to these amazing machines?
Y-You're right, I wonder why?
It's mysterious...
I'm glad for you, Kouta.
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE
Everyone loves jet aircrafts too, right?
Even if just once, I'd love to pilot a jet aircraft.
I'd go over big mountains and the blue sea so quickly.
I'd leave those Geisters far behind me!
Eh?! I'm really going to pilot it?
Even if you say that so suddenly, I haven't got a clue!
Next time, on Brave Exkaiser:
I'm a Jet Pilot
Is there an alien at your home too?