Brave         Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Mt. Fuji Explodes!?
Touto Newspaper Company
Hello! This is Touto Newspaper.
Eh? Okay, I got it!
Chief editor!
It's terrible! Mt. Utatane has erupted!
Oh yeah, it was chief editor's day off today...
Alright! I'll have a great scoop in the meanwhile!
Ah, it's Mt. Fuji!
Eh, Where? Where?
How beautiful!
It really is!
It's truly wonderful!
Yeah, it's really the best mountain in Japan.
Alright, we're here.
It feels so good!
There's so much greenery!
Now that's funny! There's two Mt. Fujis.
It's called an inverted Mt. Fuji.
I see...
How great!
It really looks like it's upside down.
Mama...
Kouta-kun, let's go over there!
Alright!
Hey, Kouta! Don't go too far.
Yeah!
It's really romantic that the two us are alone in the middle of this vast nature.
You know, dear...
What is it?
I love you.
Silly!
My loss! I really can't beat Mario.
Looks like you're having fun, Kouta.
Yup! It's the greatest to play in the nature.
Nature?
Yeah! Mountains, rivers, lakes and all the greenery!
It's a beautiful scenery with fresh air!
Is Mt. Fuji also among those?
Of course!
So nature is an important treasure to people, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Right, Mario?
Kouta-kun!
We're going to collect firewood!
I'm coming! See ya!
Everyone, I'm here at Utatane island.
Today at 12:23 pm, Mt. Utatane in the middle of the island suddenly started volcanic activity.
Sorry!
I'm awfully sorry for that.
Look at this!
Incredible smoke is coming out!
The south side of the island, Madoromi coast,
has been completely engulfed by the lava
and wildfires have occurred.
Professor Tokoroda Jusaburou, who's specialised in geophysics, has agreed to help us cover this event.
I'll ask for his opinion immediately.
Professor!
It was thought that it isn't possible for the Mt. Utatane to erupt,
so what could've caused this great eruption?
This makes it its sudden eruption since 235 years ago, right?
Professor, please look at this!
As this shows, Mt. Fuji is in the same volcanic belt as the Mt. Utatane!
What's up with you?
Listen here!
Since Mt. Utatane has erupted, isn't it also possible that Mt. Fuji might start volcanic activity too?
Don't bother us!
If Mt. Fuji erupts, it would cause great damage to the nature around it, professor!
Please! Let me hear professor's opinion about this-...
And thus, the broadcast from the scene is over.
Orders from Lord Dino Geist!
Aren't you bitter that you're getting beaten by Exkaiser all the time?
We'll do something totally crazy this time!
We're going to make Mt. Fuji explode!
This time for sure, we'll catch those humans and Exkaiser completely out of guard!
Mt. Fuji, huh? As expected from the boss, he thinks on a large scale.
Mt. Fuji?
It's the greatest mountain in Japan, even though it's not active.
Looks like things will get interesting.
Whoa, it's a snake!
No! Stupid, stupid! It's a snake, run away!
Alright, it's done.
Hey dear, do you know where the power socket is?
I brought a microwave with us.
Mama...
Papa, don't just stand around and search it with me!
There's no electricity here, mama...
I'm done... I can't run anymore...
But if we don't have firewood, we can't cook food.
There's no need for that, Kotomi-chan!
Takumi-kun!
Huh? If it isn't Takumi, what are you doing here?
It's as you can see!
Electric camping car full of computer functions!
You can live comfortably wherever you are.
Amazing! So cool!
The meal is ready with just one push of the button.
How about it, Kotomi-chan?
Would you like to eat deluxe roast beef with me?
Ah, I'll be going over there!
W-Wait a second!
It's okay!
No, I'm telling you no!
Wow, amazing!
I wonder what this button does?
It's flashing...
Hey! No, don't push that!
Sheesh, that's for the emergency
fire sprinkler equipment!
Huh, what's that?
Ah, it's still here!
Fuji Subaru Line
That was suffocating...
Ah, papa's face is pitch black!
It's the same for you, too!
Madam, I've cut the carrots and potatoes.
This is a must when you're cutting onions.
You scared me... Can I put these in?
Oh yes, you can now.
Okay!
Alright, go!
W-What are you trying to do?
I'm having him to dig a straight hole.
Until it'll get in contact with the magma inside.
Magma?
It's the energy substance for mountain eruptions.
When he digs up the magma and it starts pouring out...
Mt. Fuji will explode!
Here you go, papa!
How very delicious looking curry rice!
The rice is burnt...
It's delicious like that.
That's true, it's delicious!
Good job on collecting the firewood.
It was horrible!
A snake this big appeared!
Yup, it was my first time seeing one so big!
Oh, It's true! There certainly is a huge snake at Mt. Fuji.
Looks delicious!
Oh Fuuko, where have you been till now?
Sorry...
But my stomach is growling so much!
Here!
Would you like to eat too, Takumi-kun?
Takumi's fine. Since he's already eaten roast beef, right?
Yeah! I've also eaten a hamburger,
an omelette, a melon and a sherbet, too!
You don't have to hold back!
The computer broke down, so he didn't get to eat anything!
And who was it that broke it...
Here!
Come on, don't hold back!
I'd feel bad to decline the madam's good will,
so once in a while I might eat vulgar food like this...
Delicious!
It was Kotomi-chan who cut the carrots and potatoes, you know.
Everything tastes good when it's eaten in the nature, right?
You're such a carefree guy!
E-Earthquake!
Mt. Fuji has...
Mt. Fuji has exploded!
Alert to all Kaisers!
Mt. Fuji has started volcanic activity unnaturally.
It's highly possible that Geisters are behind this.
Let's gather at the Mt. Fuji immediately!
Roger!
I'll be there right away!
Professor, please look at this!
This is big news, Mt. Fuji has exploded too!
Professor!
Could this guy just be a regular old man...?
Ah, that's right! I just remembered that Kouta-kun and everyone came here!
Chief editor!
Help! We must escape!
Wait for me!
Go further!
Dig up that magma and make
Mt. Fuji explode massively!
I won't allow that!
What?
Change, Exkaiser!
Exkaiser...!
You villainous Geisters!
How dare you destroy the beautiful nature that gives humans a peace of mind.
You are too insolent!
Shut up!
Exkaiser!
Prepare yourself!
Change, Dash Max!
Change, Drill Max!
Change, Sky Max!
Max Team has arrived!
Damn you!
Exkaiser, leave these guys to us!
Alright, I'm counting on you!
Oh no you don't!
I won't let you go!
You bastard!
Turbo Tornado!
Damn!
Before he digs up the magma, I've got to stop him!
It's all over now!
It's the end of the world!
Get a grip!
Come on and hurry now!
Ah, chief editor!
Oh no!
The magma is...!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
King Barrier!
Exkaiser, help us!
Kouta, where are you?
The forest next to the lake is on fire!
I got it! Sky Max, I'll leave it to you-....
Look out!
Are you okay, Kouta?
Yeah...
Now that was quite vivid.
Thank you, Sky Max!
I don't... have enough energy!
That's good! Kill them!
Now's the chance!
Max Team, Form Up!
Triple Fusion, God Max!
God Cosmic Bomber!
Sorry to have kept you waiting, Exkaiser!
Blue Raker!
Change! Blue Raker!
Change! Green Raker!
Raker Brothers!
Form Up!
Left&Right Fusion, Ultra Raker!
That's good, let's keep this up!
You two must fill up this hole while I'm holding back the magma!
Will you be fine alone?
Hurry!
Alright, we got it!
Exkaiser...
All right!
Next up is destroying that monster!
Okay!
T-This is bad, let's get outta here!
Do it! Kill him!
Let's do a three way attack!
Kaiser Blaster!
Ultra Double Chain Crusher!
God Sonic Buster!
Kaiser Sword!
Thunder Flash!
We should be alright now that we've come this far.
Looks like the eruption and earthquakes have stopped.
Chief editor!
Here! I'm over here!
He's over there!
Chief editor!
What are you doing over there?
Did you get a picture of this scoop?
Well, no... I was so worried about you guys that I completely forgot about it...
You idiot!
But the most important thing is that everyone is safe.
Mt. Fuji didn't explode massively either!
Right, professor?
Thank goodness...
What's the matter with you?
I'm hurting from all over today.
I've used up energy enough of one Mt. Fuji, after all.
It's a tough job protecting the nature, right Kouta?
Thank you for protecting Mt. Fuji!
Kouta-kun, who are you talking to?
Oh, it's nothing! I'm just talking to myself.
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Has everyone already figured out what to give as a present on Mother's Day?
Mr. Tokuda invited her countryside mother to the World Fair of Flowers.
And of course, we're tagging along!
And then suddenly, even though they weren't invited, Geisters appeared!
Why?
Why do you attack my mama?
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
It's Terrible! Mama Is...!
Is there an alien in your home, too?