Brave         Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Great Flood at the Rainbow Waterfall
Fuuko, wake up!
We're going on a hiking to the
Rainbow Waterfall today!
No can do...
Wait for three more minutes, please...
Why are you saying such cup noodles-like things?
You demon!
Kouta!
"Those who have business, press the switch"?
»It's forecast to rain heavily tomorrow.
If it's raining, let me sleep till afternoon!«
Kouta, wake up!
We're going to the Rainbow Waterfall once papa gets home from working overnight!
What? It's raining heavily, though...
It'll stop soon!
My teru teru bouzu has immediate effect!
Stop the rain! Stop the rain! Stop the rain!
Stop the rain! Stop the rain!
Eh, no way!
See?
The weather forecast does say
that the rain will stop...
Oh, is that so?
Oh my, it's beautiful!
It really is! What a great rainbow!
So beautiful...
A beautiful rainbow has formed in the Tokyo skies after the rain.
The seven-colored bridge in the polluted skies is very touching.
It could be called the forgotten treasure.
Treasure?
How many years has it been since we last saw such a great rainbow like this in Tokyo?
I see, so this is a rainbow?
It looks like a big bridge!
Folklore regarding a rainbow
Has everyone heard a story like
this when you were little?
At the end of a rainbow, there's gold, silver and beautiful jewels buried.
And that's where the beautiful rainbow bridge rises.
It's the job for me!
Can you carry them by yourself?
It looks heavy.
Well, that's...
I'll help you.
I'll lend a hand at carrying them.
Let's go, Horn Geist!
Hey hey hey, who said I was going with you?
It's so refreshing after the rain!
And what a beautiful rainbow!
Such an unique view that tingles my artistic sense!
It's shaking!
I-It appeared!
Is that it?
Alright! So it's right next to that little house.
I-I must inform the newspaper company!
Hello, it's the Touto Newspaper.
Oh, if it isn't Takumi-kun!
What! A dinosaur robot appeared near us?
Alright, I'll send the perfect guy immediately!
Tokuda!
Yes!
I, Tokuda Osamu, shall do my best!
About what?
I'm going to cover an event.
Take care of the office!
Hey, mama...
What, Kouta?
Why must we join you to the place where you and papa first met every year?
Because it's our memorable place!
If I and papa wouldn't have met,
Fuuko and Kouta wouldn't exist in this world!
All because of that fateful incident...
I've had enough of that story.
I've heard it for the umpteenth time.
But it's really romantic, you know?
When I...
You slipped your foot and almost fell into the Rainbow Waterfall, right?
That's right!
Then papa tried to save you, but ended up falling first himself.
Oh, you know it very well.
Because you tell it every year!
Then you tried to save papa and fell into the waterfall too, right?
No matter how many times I hear it,
it's such a clumsy story.
Really! And that's the beginning of love.
Yeah, yeah...
It's an earthquake!
Isn't it the sewer construction work?
An earthquake!
What the hell is this?
Someone has dug here before me.
Where's the treasure?
It's not here! It's not here! It's not here!
Oh, you've dug quite a bit.
Did you find the treasure?
Well... Seems like someone dug here first and I can't find it.
What?
That can't be!
Ah! You're trying to get the treasure all by yourself!
Are you saying you can't trust me?
I bet it was you who came here first
and dug out the treasure!
What was that?
Don't mess with me!
What?
Damn you!
What a loud construction work.
I'm telling you it's an earthquake!
Could it be...!
You bastard!
What are you guys doing?
Ptera Geist!
There's no rainbow here!
I'm certain there was a rainbow earlier...
I see now!
No wonder it can't be found.
You went one step ahead of us and took the rainbow!
I can't hang around with idiots!
It's the Geisters!
I must inform Exkaiser!
What did you say? Geisters appeared in front of our house?
And like that, it was really huge!
So, where did this dinosaur robot go?
Now that you mention it...
There was a loud sound and earth dust near Kouta-kun's house...
What?
Takumi-kun, thank you for the information!
Well, I only did what's expected!
I hate it after the rain!
Exkaiser?
Ah, papa!
Papa, that dinosaur robot-...
Mama! Is mama alright?
Mama!
Kouta!
Exkaiser, I wasn't expecting at all that the Geisters would appear here!
Just what are they planning?
Maybe they found out that Exkaiser is at our home!
I don't think that's it...
Anyway, we must investigate what those Geisters are planning!
Alert to all Kaisers!
Geisters appeared near the Hoshikawa's house.
Everyone, start investigating what they're planning!
Roger!
Is it impossible no matter what, papa?
I'm sorry. I must hurry this article
to the evening paper.
But if I'm not with papa...
Is it really impossible?
I'd love to go too...
Wherever together with mama...
But we're running short of people.
Oh my! Well, this is horrible!
It's all gone!
Tokuda!
Ah, chief editor...
What happened to taking care of the office?
Well, my senior told me to go help you!
I don't need your help!
Hey, papa...
How about you give the job to Mr. Tokuda?
That's right! Leave it to me.
Chief editor doesn't have to do the covering all by himself...
Doing it myself or not, that's not the point!
I'm here because I can't leave it to someone who snores at the editorial department!
Chief editor... That's too much...
So that's the situation.
I'll leave you the car, so go to the Rainbow Waterfall with mama driving.
Papa, you really can't come?
Please give mama a fun time by yourselves.
Papa...
Idiot! Stupid! Dumbass! Goof! Silly!
Lord Dino Geist is saying this,
all of you will go this time!
Failures are unforgivable!
But where is that rainbow?
Go to the Rainbow Waterfall!
There's a rainbow there all the time!
Hey, mama!
Since papa can't come,
shouldn't we really cancel for today?
No, we will go.
It's our yearly event, after all...
N-No matter what?
Exkaiser, did you find out anything about Geisters?
I'm having them investigate right now.
Don't have worries, Kouta!
But...
Kouta, what are you doing?
We're going!
Yes! Bye then...
Sister, what's wrong?
Well, you know!
Mama is doing the driving, our mama!
That's right!
Well then, we're going!
Y-Yes...
Um, mama? Is there something wrong with the car?
There's no such thing...
Wow, it's beautiful!
It really is! Good that we came!
Really!
It would've been better if papa was with us...
We're here! We're here!
Let's hurry and go eat our lunch boxes!
Let's take a forest walk first.
Mama, let's go quickly!
Maybe I'll wait here...
What's wrong? Are you feeling bad?
I'm lonely, since papa isn't here...
That's so stupid! Is this something the rainbow mother would say?
Kouta, let's go!
That's no good, mama!
If mama doesn't have fun with us, papa will cry!
Papa will cry?
Papa feels like it's his responsibility that he couldn't make mama happy.
He said he's sorry!
That's right.
Papa has a strong sense of responsibility so I can't make him worry.
Let's go.
Yup!
It's the Rainbow Waterfall!
We've come to the Rainbow Waterfall again this year!
The rainbow is as beautiful as that time!
It's a shame that papa isn't here with us...
Mama! Let's eat our lunch boxes.
If you're dazing too much, Kouta will eat them all!
That's fine! My heart is already so filled.
What's the matter, Mario?
They're over here too!
Let's hide!
Oh no!
How horrible! What should we do?
So the treasure is buried in here?
What's this?
This will stop the water!
It stopped...
Alright, dig up the treasure!
Yeah, roger to that!
The Rainbow Waterfall is...!
Change, Exkaiser!
So you appeared!
Exkaiser!
You awful Geisters!
What do you intend to do with
the Rainbow Waterfall?
It's none of your business!
Kouta!
Go quickly to a safe place!
You should just play with this!
You damn Geisters!
This is awful! The dam is moving!
This is...!
Change, Blue Raker!
Change, Green Raker!
Raker Brothers!
Twin Fire!
What a great power!
Exkaiser!
Give it your all, little brother!
Hey! The treasure better be buried in here!
Since you've dug so much already and there's nothing, this might not be the place...
Max Team has arrived!
Geisters!
We, Kaisers, won't forgive any of your evil doings!
This is bad! Let's get outta here.
It's not like we lost!
I bet your comrades are already...
What did he say?
Take this!
Exkaiser, do it now!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
Kaiser Kick!
Go help Blue Raker and Green Raker!
Got it!
Kaiser Sword!
Oh no!
You did good, Raker Brothers!
Thunder Flash!
Forming Beam!
I'll return the dam back to normal!
Get the water!
Roger!
Raker Hurricane!
They did it!
The waterfall is back to normal!
It's papa!
Papa!
Heeey!
Touto Newspaper Company
Mama!
Mama, were you alright?
Dear, what about work?
Such thing!
It's more important that mama is safe!
The rainbow is back!
How beautiful it is!
It's like back then.
It really is a must to see it with papa!
It's my first time seeing such a beautiful rainbow!
Exkaiser, thank you!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Have you ever seen a wedding ceremony?
Soon, a foreign princess and prince are holding a wedding ceremony in Japan!
And sheesh, Kotomi-chan is like "I wonder if a prince charming would appear for me too!"
Eh? The princess got attacked?!
Exkaiser!
Don't let Geisters bother the wedding ceremony!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
The Targeted Bride
Is there an alien in your home, too?