Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Concert for the Braves
»Kaiser Sword!«
»Thunder Flash!«
He did it!
So cool!
Mysterious robots Exkaiser and friends protect us from the evil deeds of Geisters.
Music that praises them will be performed at a ceremony in Asahidai Civic Center.
What is that?
Such a bad taste!
Today I'll be talking to the designer of this Civic Center,
who also composed the symphony "Brave",
it's the master Tokoroda Jusaburou.
Master, good day!
Master, so you have a variety of talents like architecture and music?
And I'm the only son of the Kaneari family who donated to this Civic Center.
I'm Kaneari Takumi!
I just knew that was the taste of Takumi's family...
The truth is that there's a special execution planned for this evening's concert!
Please look at this!
At the same time when the performance and the piano solo ends,
the ceiling dome opens and laser beams color the sky!
The cost of this and decorating fees are truly-...
Um, thank you very much!
Well then, over here is the instrument for today's performance, that was specially ordered from Italy.
It's the piano by Mythos Farina.
Wow! It's amazing!
The genius piano artisan of the
19th century, Mythos Farina.
The tones that his piano creates can truly be called the treasure of mankind!
Camera! Over here!
Um, Takumi-kun, what is it?
Well, I just thought I'd let all the TV viewers hear the sound of this world's most fantastic piano.
But it's decided that this piano can only be touched by the performer!
What are you saying?
I'm the sponsor, you know!
Ah! Don't!
Hey! Let go! Who do you think I am?
What the heck is he doing...
Well then, over here is the one who will play the piano solo!
It's Tsukiyama Kotomi-chan!
Look! It's Kotomi-chan!
You were chosen out of the many elementary school students in Asahidai, so how are you feeling?
It's unbelievable that I can play the piano by Mythos Farina!
I'm going to play my best!
What nonsense that there's songs for Exkaiser!
Those humans do such stupid things...
What should we do, Lord Dino Geist?
I absolutely can't allow that there's a concert for those bastard.
Disturb them and steal that piano!
Yes, sir!
Alright, we're here.
Oh my, what a splendid hall!
I always dreamt of going to a concert!
Exkaiser, if you're here then can you hear the performance from inside?
No problem with that...
But it makes me somewhat
embarrassed that it's music for us...
Don't be embarassed!
Kouta!
What are you doing? Let's go!
Yes! See you later, Exkaiser.
Songs that praise me and my friends, huh...
Ah! Chief editor!
Oh, Tokuda! You're here too.
Don't sound like it's surprising.
The completion of the Civic Center is an important cultural event for Asahidai!
Oh? Kouta-kun...
Why are you holding a bouquet?
I promised to bring Kotomi-chan flowers.
I see!
Well then, let's go together since
I'd like to interview her!
Yeah!
Then we'll go in the auditorium before you.
Got it!
Hey, wait a moment!
You're rather cool, if I can say
so about my little brother!
Hall
It's not just the outside, but the
inside is all jumble too!
Um... To even begin with, where are we currently?
What's the matter, you two?
This Civic Center has been made with my family's help.
So you can ask me anything!
What's with that outfit?
Takumi-kun, I'll ask you then.
Do you know where Kotomi-chan's dressing room is?
Go straight from that corridor!
Mr. Tokuda, let's hurry!
Alright...
You'll reach it eventually.
Oh, Takumi-kun!
Kotomi-chan!
Kotomi-chan, congratulations for today! Here you go!
Wow, they're beautiful! Thank you!
Kouta-kun promised to bring me flowers too, but...
Another corner!
We can't go straight at all!
Anyway, let's go over here!
Kotomi-chan!
Huh? I heard Kouta-kun's voice...
Eh? Is that really so?
Ah! Look! He's over there!
Eh? Where?
Ah! They're over there!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Look! Look! Over here!
Kotomi-chan!
Please let me interview you!
Ah! Over here!
Where exactly?
Kotomi-chan!
Please let me ask things!
Takumi-kun!
Hey! Wait!
Here! This way!
Kotomi-chan!
Takumi-kun! Where is he?
Over here!
Wait!
Damn! Why did they build such
a maze-like building...
Ah! It's starting!
Kouta, you couldn't give them?
Yeah...
I wonder if Kotomi-chan is angry...
Everyone! Welcome to the Asahidai Civic Center Completion Ceremony Concert!
Well then, we'll start with a symphony by the piano and orchestra players.
It's called "Brave"!
The conductor is of course the composer, master Tokoroda Jusaburou.
The musical performance is by
Asahidai Philharmonic Orchestra.
And the piano solo is done by Asahidai elementary school's student from 3-B class,
the one and only who's called a piano genius!
It's Ms. Tsukiyama Kotomi!
This isn't good... Looks like she's really nervous.
He only gave her more pressure by doing that introduction!
Do your best, Kotomi-chan!
It's unbelievable...
I calmed down as soon as I sat in front of this piano!
Oh...
Yeah... Seems like she suddenly calmed down.
As expected from a piano that's
called a treasure.
Kotomi-chan!
This sure makes you excited of what sort of tones we'll be hearing!
They sure are at it!
Our hall is...!
Professor! Did you design it to transform like that?
Kotomi-chan is inside that!
Don't, Kouta-kun!
If only Exkaiser would come at a time like this...
That's right! We should all just call for him!
That's right!
One, two...
Exkaiser!
Change, Exkaiser!
You again?
Those who disrupt the concert of Earth's people who have put their whole hearts into it...
I won't forgive them!
Exkaiser!
Kouta-kun!
Kouta!
Don't get full of yourself just because they made songs of you, Exkaiser!
Don't go looking away!
Take this!
Idiots! Don't shoot over here!
Kouta! What are you trying to do?
Kotomi-chan is inside that!
What?
It's dangerous! Come back, Kouta!
What are you doing? Carry the treasure quickly!
Kouta!
I won't let you!
Ow ow ow...
Kotomi-chan!
No use!
Jet Boomerang!
Kouta!
Don't get in our way!
Die!
Raker Brothers!
Max Team!
So they've come!
Oh no! Kouta and his friend are inside!
What did you say?
I see!
Get on this quickly!
I see! They're not attacking us now!
Goddamn it!
They're playing dirty!
Raker Brothers, you should stop its feet.
Drill Max, you'll go save Kouta!
Roger!
Let's go!
Okay!
Chain Crusher!
Kouta!
Drill Max!
What great powers!
We have to hang on until Drill Max escapes!
Let go!
Ah! They'll get defeated!
Exkaiser!
Kotomi-chan!
Kouta-kun!
Thank god you're okay!
Kouta, step aside!
Kouta-kun!
Kotomi-chan...
I was scared...
Come on, let's hurry!
Drill Max!
Hurry!
Go on! At least you two must escape!
Even if you tell us to escape...
From where...?
This is it!
Kotomi-chan, it's the piano!
Eh? The piano?
This hall is made so that the ceiling dome will open when the piano is played.
But it's in such state now...
Kouta! Hurry!
Dash Max!
You tenacious bastards!
Drill Max! Hurry!
I can't do it! My fingers shake so much...
Kotomi-chan!
I can't do it! I can't play!
I did promise to bring you flowers before the performance...
Although it's only one of them...
Now it's time for Kotomi-chan to fulfill her promise and play the piano.
Kouta-kun...
Sky Max!
W-What is this?
This is the sound of Mythos Farina's piano...
It's the song I composed for Exkaiser!
Do your best, Kotomi-chan!
It's a song for us, huh?
It gives me more powers!
Yeah!
Hang on! Just a little more!
No matter how hard you try, this is your end!
Damn you!
What is this?
Thank you                            Exkaiser
King Loader!
Form Up!
Super Giant Fusion, Great Exkaiser!
Great Blaster!
This is nothing!
Form Up!
Left&Right Fusion, Ultra Raker!
Ultra Shoulder Crash!
Ultra Raker!
Max Team, Form Up!
Triple Fusion, God Max!
God Slicer!
Great Exkaiser, do it now!
Kaiser Sword!
Thunder Crash!
Damn... Let's retreat!
They did it!
We were able to hear such wonderful songs...
Thank you!
Exkaiser! You're so cool!
Thank you, Exkaiser!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Everyone, do you know Halloween?
It's a day when you dress as monsters and either do tricks or get sweets!
It's a very fun festival!
But I've heard that it's also the day when
demons have the most powers in the year!
Whoa! Our treats! A demon really appeared!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Halloween Monster
Is there an alien in your home, too?