Brave         Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Aim to Be a Space Pilot
I'm here at the Space Frontier that has just recently been opened.
I'm standing in front of one of its sections called Space Camp.
This is a facility that was built in order for children to experience the same training
and studies of real astronauts.
As you can see, even though it's a facility for children, full-scale training equipment has been prepared.
It's wonderful, right?
Buses full of children who've come to learn from this experience have just arrived.
It's a space shuttle!
Kouta-kun, can we board that?
We can!
After the learning experience, we
do departure training with that!
Everyone! We'll go inside now!
This multi-axis trainer is a training device to become familiar with zero gravity.
You can experience the zero gravity
state in that space ball!
Kouta-kun, you know so well!
Well, that's because my dream
is to become an astronaut...
But with your grades...
Takumi!
Astronauts fly space shuttles and rockets of latest technology, you know.
What about it?
I'm saying that you can't become one unless you're good at math and science!
That's not true!
The pilot Muraoka has said that he wasn't very good at math and science during elementary school!
Pilot Muraoka?
The person who became
the first space pilot in Japan!
I don't care if he's the first in Japan or not,
but he sure isn't a good pilot then.
Well, I'll just be buying a shuttle and hiring a
first-rate pilot, so it doesn't really matter...
Hey!
Don't touch the training devices without permission!
This isn't an amusement park!
I-I'm sorry!
No training touches!
Could he be...
This person is?
I'm Muraoka who'll be training you for the next 2 days.
Let me remind you that this is a place where you experience astronauts' training and learn from it.
This isn't a playground!
Got it? I'll be relentless so be prepared.
Everyone!
Do as teacher Muraoka says and learn many various things!
Yes!
Hey, don't be so slow!
This is more like a soccer or
rugby club's training camp...
I agree!
I didn't come here to do this...
Those who call it hard are fastener nails!
Can't anything be done about those lame jokes... Sheesh...
I-I can't do it!
Kotomi-chan!
Stop!
No need to help her!
But she's a girl...
There's no men or women!
In space, both men and women are in the same conditions!
Um! Can I tell you something?
We are on Earth now, so the conditions
are different from space!
Earth is also one of the planets in space.
If Earth would be a spaceship,
then all humans would be astronauts!
It's alright! I'll do my best!
That's it! That's the spirit!
Kotomi-chan...
Alright, just a little more!
Kotomi-chan! Do your best!
I did it...
She did it!
See? You can do it if you try.
The important thing of an astronaut
is challenge mentality!
Challenge mentality?
It's the mentality to challenge yourself to do anything! That's needed.
There's nothing that humans can't do.
If you try, you can do anything!
Do you understand?
Yes!
Even though it's challenge,
don't put a lozenge in tea.
Help me!
My eyes are spinning...
That's too pitiful!
At this rate, you can't get balance in zero gravity!
Ouch!
B-But...
No buts or ifs!
If Earth would be a spaceship,
then all humans would be...
Astronauts, right?
If you know that, then try harder!
Next!
Hoshikawa Kouta!
I'll try it!
Alright!
Let's go.
Yes!
How was this challenge?
I-It's tough...
Right? Challenges are tough.
Good work.
"If Earth would be a spaceship, then all humans would be astronauts"?
Don't act on your own!
What are you doing? Let go! I'm going home!
If you'll be docile, I'll let you go.
Will you be docile?
I'll be docile, so let me go...
I'll let you go the other way!
No way... That wasn't the deal!
It's best for humans to be docile!
Ah, good work.
H-Help me!
Young sir...
It's tough?
That's right...
But since it's training, it can't be helped, right?
But it's not like we can go to space immediately...
Teacher Muraoka said that if Earth would be a spaceship,
then all humans would be astronauts, right?
Yeah...
I think that teacher is right.
Earth is also a part of space.
Earth might only be a planet that
revolves around sun...
But Earth has a destination called future.
The people who live here can decide what happens in that future.
In other words, if Earth is a spaceship that's going
to the future, then mankind is its astronaut.
Do you understand?
Yeah!
It's all depending on mankind's future actions
whether Earth will become good or bad.
Especially since young Kouta and the others will create the future.
So that's what he meant!
It's the same with the challenge mentality.
The same challenge mentality is needed in order to cultivate both future and space.
I understand now, Exkaiser!
It's teacher Muraoka! Exkaiser, good night then!
Kids sleeping in the center of beds and
there's a sleeping empire in Central Asia...
Ah, is that the Empire of Paradise?
Re-entry to the atmosphere range requires an angle of inclination of 38 degrees.
That's in order to suppress the atmosphere's friction heat to the minimum.
Well then, do you have questions?
Here!
Is there anything else important for an astronaut
besides the challenge mentality?
Another thing is...
Teamwork!
Teamwork?
That's right!
You already know what you can do alone.
That's why you need cooperation!
Don't do spadework!
How about we'll shortly begin
the shuttle simulation?
We'll finally go to the cockpit!
Someone entered wrongly the re-entry angle's setting.
But it's not one person's
responsibility, it's everyone's!
It's a system where even if one makes a mistake, another person checks it.
But if everyone acts ignorant, this is what happens!
Teamwork is needed!
Well, failure does teach success...
Failure tastes bitter, after all.
Change to the next group now.
Yes!
First up is departure preparations.
Remember the guidelines I taught you and check things with discretion.
Not the Jack of spades!
Yes! Orbiter's output... Jack!
I mean... Check!
Huh? I didn't even do anything yet...
Did someone touch the switch?
I-It wasn't me!
It stopped!
What are those?
Calm down! You must calm down!
It's Geisters!
This is bad...
Let's get out of here!
Mr. Muraoka!
Mr. Muraoka...
W-We got shut in!
Someone save me!
Papa! Mama!
Calm down!
You must think.
The most important thing in emergencies
is to calm down and think!
Oh no, this is terrible!
I must think!
Alright! This time the treasure is ours for sure!
Spike Cutter!
Change!
Geisters!
How dare you try to steal the Space Frontier
that holds humans' future and
their dreams and hopes of space!
I won't forgive you!
What can you even do alone?
Wait!
Don't forget about us!
Change, Dash Max!
Change, Drill Max!
Change, Sky Max!
Max Team has arrived!
Geisters! Prepare yourselves!
Hey, it's your turn now!
What?
Let's combine!
Alright!
Max Team, Form Up!
Triple Fusion, God Max!
Dragon Jet!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, Dragon Kaiser!
Let's do consecutive attacks!
Alright!
Exkaiser!
Exkaiser, wait!
We're inside the shuttle robot!
What did you say?
I'm currently thinking of a way to escape,
so change this Space Frontier back to normal first!
Damn!
As if we'd let you bother us that easily!
Kill them!
Yeah!
Bind Crush!
What?
Form Up!
Left&Right Fusion, Ultra Raker!
God Max, I'll help you!
Oh, Ultra Raker! Please do!
Ultra Chain Crusher!
Now's the chance!
God Sonic-...
As if I'd let you!
God Max!
Don't panic!
Even if you say that, it's the end now!
There's a way if you try,
but if you don't then there's no way at all!
That's it!
Isn't there an escape pod?
So you finally noticed.
Mr. Muraoka, you knew?
Of course! I'm your instructor!
I was waiting for you to notice it.
You're way too laid-back!
This shuttle's whole cockpit is
made to be an escape pod.
Pilot!
Use the computer and release the escape pod's safety system.
Pilot is...
That's you!
Y-Yes!
No good!
The computer is broken!
There should be a spare computer.
Kotomi-chan! Connect the spare
system's circuit immediately!
Y-Yes!
That's the way to go! Teamwork, teamwork!
The spare system is connected!
Releasing the safety system!
Huh? It doesn't work!
It's really no good!
This shuttle has turned into a robot!
It doesn't take our orders!
You say "no good" too much!
If you say "no good" all the time,
you'll turn into a no good man!
But...
There's also too much "buts"!
Use those "buts" to rather become
a man who rebuts nothing!
Pilot, don't give up!
Remember the challenge mentality!
Yes!
Kouta!
If doing the same thing twice doesn't work, then try something else.
Something else?
If the automatic system doesn't work, then how about the manual system?
Correct! That's exactly right!
I see!
It worked!
Alright, let's escape!
Yes!
0!
Departing!
Alright! Now's the time!
Get away!
Stop right there!
We'll back you up!
God Max! Ultra Raker!
Ultra Cannon Beam!
God Sonic Buster!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Super Giant Fusion, Great Exkaiser!
Kouta-kun! Looks like we're safe now!
Kaiser Sword!
Thunder Crash!
This is bad! Let's escape!
He did it!
Thank you, Exkaiser!
Mr. Muraoka, how did you manage to be calm during that big emergency?
It's because I believed in you.
Those who believe are saved!
Really?
Yeah! You all can become great astronauts who operate the spaceship called Earth.
Of course!
But the "no good" and "but" boy
could train his spirit a little more!
Would you like to train here for another week?
No... Um... I won't say "no good" or "but" ever again,
so please forgive me!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Everyone, have you ever thought
that you wanted a robot friend?
I bet it would be so much fun to
study and play together!
But I have Exkaiser, of course!
Huh? Where am I?
Did I perhaps get brought to the Geisters' base?
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Destruction! Geisters' Base
Is there an alien in your home, too?