Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Mario and Juliet
C-Cold...
A-All because that Exkaiser bastard destroyed
our base, this is what we get...
I miss being inside a volcano...
Well then, at this week's My Pet...
We'll be introducing this doggy today!
It's so cute!
Thanks to her, my family has been saying
that I've become more gentler.
And what do you mean by that?
When tough or sad things happen,
it's a great comfort to be playing
and talking to this dog.
I see! So adoring a doggy enriches people's hearts.
Looks so warm...
And we're here shivering in cold...
Why is a mere dog having such a cozy life...
Damn...
At this rate, I won't be able to hold my anger!
All Japan
Bow-Wow Contest
All Japan Bow-Wow Contest, huh...
District Qualifiers
So cold...
Hey, let's go home quickly! We walked all
of Mario's jogging trails already, right?
Hand warmer
Very warm
Sheesh! As if I'd want to walk
the dog on a day like this!
Kouta-kun!
Kotomi-chan!
How come you have a puppy?
Papa got her from his friend!
She's called Juliet!
So cute!
Go on, Juliet... Greet them.
She's so wise!
I'm sure she would win if you'd
participate in the Bow-Wow Contest!
You people!
Could you say that once you've seen my dog?
Takumi!
Well then, let me introduce to you!
It's a purebred Great Dane.
And his name is Goldgo!
Did your family even have such a dog?
In order to participate in that contest, he was ordered from Europe.
You sure spend money needlessly as usual!
It's said that pets resemble their owners,
so Kotomi-chan's dog is what I'd expect!
She's so elegant!
She's a purebred Poodle.
I see!
And what dog breed is that
Mario-kun over there?
He's a Chow Chow mix..
Mix?
I'm sorry to hear that...
If that's so, then even if you'd participate in the
Bow-Wow Contest, it'd be impossible to win!
You don't know about that!
You're naive...
Take a look at this Goldgo.
Sharply shining eyes.
A smart figure!
And the overflowing nobleness!
On the other hand, Mario-kun is...
Small eyes.
A round figure.
And overflowing clumsiness!
Even thinking of competing should be
called a mistake, don't you agree?
It's true that our Mario is a fatty,
shorty and a human-faced dog!
But you don't have the right to say that!
Sister...
Seems like you know it well enough
even if I don't point it out loud and clearly.
Kouta! Can you stay silent after hearing all that?
Say something back!
I won't stand this after hearing
all those awful things!
But you're the one who called him an
useless and human-faced dog...
Mario!
If you're a man, then you gotta
put your spirit to the test!
It's such a nice and quiet Sunday.
Oh! Good morning, Mario!
What's the matter?
Mario!
We have to dry you properly!
Hey, Mario! It's no use running away!
Just what is going on?
We're going to participate Mario
in the Bow-Wow Contest!
Bow-Wow Contest?
What do you think?
He looks even worse now...
You think so too?
Alright! Change of plans!
Mario in a contest, huh...
I think it's a waste of effort...
Oh, why?
A wonderful dog like Mario will win for sure!
I feel sorry for Mario...
By the way...
Why did you come here?
Oh you! Isn't that obvious?
We already ate dinner.
Posture correction technology!
Now his posture will get much better!
I feel like this is animal cruelty though...
You go all out once you're at it!
Mario!
Sister, take it off quickly!
Why didn't it work...
Sheesh... Seems like it's a hard job to be a pet.
Are you alright, Mario?
Your figure isn't too good to begin with...
Mario! It must've been tough.
Here is your food!
Wait!
Listen up! From today on, Mario's food
will be changed to this diet food!
Dog Food
No way...
I just made this...
If you'd like, I can help with that!
This is all of today's calories!
Delicious! This is really delicious!
Let me taste one of those...
Isn't this pretty good too?
This crunchiness is rather...
Sister, what will you do this time?
I'm going to cut his fur like Juliet
from Kotomi-chan's family.
Wouldn't he look a bit cooler then?
Come on, Mario-kun!
It won't take long...
Sister! There's no need to go that far...
What are you saying!
Such a shameful and useless dog can't let
be seen by others unless I do all of this!
N-No way!
Wait! Mario!
Mario!
Where are you going?
Come back!
Mario!!
Maybe I said a bit too much?
It wasn't a bit!
Sheesh!
I wonder where Mario went...
Don't worry, he'll come back eventually.
I hope so...
Exkaiser! It's Dash Max here!
Did something happen?
Well, it's nothing important...
But I just saw Kouta's family dog
walking with a miserable expression...
Mario!
Such a shameful and useless dog can't let
be seen by others unless I do all of this!
Mario...
Don't do it!
M-Mario, look out!
Mario!
Mario, sister wasn't serious when
she said those things!
And no matter who says what,
I do believe that Mario is a wise,
tough, kind and admirable dog!
Mario!
Well then, everyone! The long-awaited day of the Bow-Wow Contest is finally here!
A variety of remarkable dogs!
Which doggy will be the one to
bask in the glory of victory?
I'm already very excited!
Bow-Wow Contest...
Is it that exciting?
A variety of remarkable dogs, they said...
Interesting!
I'll be snatching all of those cheeky dogs!
Up!
Jump!
She sure shows us!
But the victory goes to our Mario!
Well... We'll see about that...
The next one is entry no. 10.
Kaneari Takumi-kun's pet dog!
It's the entry of Goldgo!
Well, what kind of things can this doggy do?
Before that I'd like to tell you about this Goldgo's perfect lineage.
First of all, the famous Napoleon the 1st-...
Oh my... How terrible!
He valued the lineage, but you can't
judge a book by its cover...
After this incident, it's time for the pet dog of Hoshikawa Kouta-kun and Ms. Fuuko.
It's the entry of Mario-kun!
Come on, Mario... Show them the
epic stunt that we practiced...
If you don't do it, you'll be eating
diet food for the time being!
Mario! You're so wonderful!
They're all shocked...
Maybe this was a mistake, after all...
It appeared!
Well then, let's take all the dogs that are inside!
I got so many!
Mario!
Juliet!
There you go!
We'll be taking these!
Wait!
Change, Exkaiser!
So you appeared, Exkaiser!
I won't forgive you for tearing apart the
friendship of humans and dogs!
This is none of your business!
Dragon Jet!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, Dragon Kaiser!
You idiot!
It's not my fault if something
happens to the dogs inside this!
What?
Exkaiser!
Please save Mario and the others!
Take this!
Don't get full of yourself, Exkaiser!
Who's there?
Max Team has arrived!
Damn villains!
Prepare yourselves!
Wait!
We must first save the dogs that
Ptera Geist has captured!
What?
But how can we save them...?
What's the matter?
Aren't you going to attack?
Mario!
Here's the payback!
I do believe that Mario is a wise,
tough, kind and admirable dog!
Do your best!
I'll put you out of your misery now...
Mario!
What?
Damn dog! Don't get in our way!
Mario!!
Mario!
We've taken back the dogs!
Damn!
We failed, huh...
Ptera, you klutz!
What are you doing!
Mario!
Mario, hang in there!
Geisters! I won't forgive you!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Super Giant Fusion, Great Exkaiser!
Escape!
Wait!
Do it! Kill them!
Kaiser Sword!
Thunder Crash!
Mario, wake up!
Mario!
Look! Thanks to you, Juliet and
the other doggies are safe.
That's why...
That's why, Mario...
Please don't die!
If this is the outcome, we shouldn't
have participated in the contest!
Mario! I'll write a front page article
about your brave actions!
Mario!
Mario...
You are a true Brave!
You don't need to win...
You can be a bit clumsy and uncool...
Just come back to life!
Mario!
I'm so glad...
Hoshikawa Mario-kun!
I declare you the winner of
Asahidai's Bow-Wow Contest!
That's great! Congratulations!
The best in Japan!
This is just picture perfect!
That's why I said it!
That a wonderful dog like Mario will win for sure!
Mario! You're so cool!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Everyone, do you know that fires are scary?
Fires where black smoke comes out and
everything gets burnt are really scary!
The fire trucks and firefighters put
out those fires! They're so cool!
Ah! Smoke!
How terrible! Geisters have set the building on fire!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Fire Truck, Set Out!
Is there an alien in your home, too?