Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
The Origin of Cake Is Gone!
I did it! It's a great success!
Oh... Too bad...
Kouta, shouldn't you give up already?
It's a waste of flour.
What's with you!
Wasn't it you who said giving a handmade present is the best!
I did say that but...
I'll absolutely give a handmade cake as a present to Kotomi-chan for her birthday tomorrow!
Wouldn't it be better to go buy a different present already?
Shut up already!
I've decided to give Kotomi-chan a handmade cake as the present!
Mama, where's the flour?
Oh, there isn't any there?
Not at all.
Was this the last of the flour?
Sheesh, did you use it all up?
I was thinking of making tempura as a side dish today...
Oh yes, maybe I'll make buckwheat tempura!
Don't do it, mama!
Oh, why?
Emergency news flash!
Flour is gone!!
Today various flour manufactoring factories, preserving storehouses
and shops that sell flour are getting attacked one after another.
Flour has disappeared from Japan.
The criminal has invaded from both ceiling and underground.
An arbitrary giant hole with the diameter of several meters has been left behind.
The only ones who could've done this... are those guys!
N... No good! No good! No good!
I'm giving it as a present to Kotomi-chan!
It has to taste more gorgeous and elegant!
This and this and this too, redo them all!
Um... But there's no flour anymore.
If there's none, then go buy some!
Um... It's gone from all over Japan.
Gone from all over Japan?
Most of the stores are closed.
So flour is the origin to a lot of foods?
Yeah...
Kouta, cheer up!
Geisters are the only ones who could've done this.
I'll definitely catch those Geisters and get back the flour.
Thanks.
But it'll still be late for Kotomi-chan's birthday.
Stop!
Alright!
This store isn't closed!
I can buy flour!
Excuse me, can I have flour-...
Isn't there a little bit left?
No, it's truly all gone.
Kouta!
Ugh, T-Takumi...
If you're looking for flour, you'd better give up.
Since you don't have connections like me.
No way I can give up!
I absolutely need flour to make Kotomi-chan's present!
Kotomi-chan's present?
You're going to give Kotomi-chan a cake as the present, right?
S-So what...
Shop manager!
Y-Yes...
You mustn't sell flour to this guy!
Tell that to all stores!
Who would've thought Takumi was going to give a cake as the present too...
Such a bad luck...
What's wrong, Kouta?
Ah, I know!
Maybe there's some flour left in there!
Cooking Classroom
What a good idea from me!
Excuse me! If there's flour here, let me borrow some...
Kouta-kun!
Oh my...
Huh? Why's Kotomi-chan and our teacher here...?
I see, so teacher was searching for flour too?
I was thinking of making her favourite food, udon.
Because of old age, her teeth have weakened and her only eatable favourite food is udon...
Only udon?
I had no idea you had weakened so much...
Who said I was talking about myself?
My teeth are in good shape!
The one with weakened teeth is my mother.
It's unbelievable that I can't even fulfill the only enjoyment of a senior...
Oh right! It wasn't the time to be talking about this.
I must search for flour!
See you!
I feel so bad for our teacher...
If I wouldn't have wasted flour, I could've given some to teacher...
I'll definitely find flour for teacher's sake!
I'll search too!
Kouta-kun, let's make udon together tomorrow and give it as a present to our teacher, okay?
Eh?
But...
Tomorrow is Kotomi-chan's...
Okay? Please, Kouta-kun!
I got it, Kotomi-chan!
Give us flour!!     Where's the flour!!    Hand over the flour!
The front of National Diet is filled with people who want flour.
Idiot, gimme  Dissolve  Let us eat!
Give the flour  Give flour!!  Where's the flour!!
That's good! That's good!
Everyone's troubled!
Make a bigger noise! Rough things up!
When are you going to tidy up?
Huh? What about?
That!
Flour       Flour       Flour
It's in the way! Hurry up and tidy it up!
... Is what lord Dino Geist said.
Don't worry! In three days, a space merchant will come get them and it'll be all nice and clean.
That won't do! Clean it up right away!
There's no need to be in such hurry...
Shut up, Ptera Geist!
I can't hear the TV...
What was that?
Your voice is much noisier than mine!
What?!
Please feel at ease, everyone.
An emergency import of flour is on it's way.
W-What did he say?
It'll arrive via boat to the harbour sometime this afternoon.
Furthermore, this flour is...
And thus, Kotomi-chan's heart will belong to me!
That was an announcement from the Prime Minister about the emergency flour.
Alright!
Now I can get some flour!
Exkaiser, drive to the harbour!
It's dangerous, I'm sure those Geisters will appear!
Please, Exkaiser!
I absolutely need flour!
But...
Exkaiser!
Alright then, Kouta.
Thank you!
Blue Raker! Blue Raker!
Green Raker! Green Raker!
Respond! Respond!
What is it, Exkaiser?
It's highly possible that Geisters will appear at the harbour.
Please back me up!
Roger!
I'll come there as soon as I've let off the passengers.
Same thing here, Exkaiser.
Let's go, Kouta! Hang on tight.
What should I make for dinner?
The buckwheat tempura got rejected, after all...
What's wrong, Mario?
Hey, go away!
Oh, our car...!
No way it could've been, right?
Okay, just like that! Alright, alright, alright, alright!
Kaneari Shipping
Alright, alright! Alright, slowly just like that.
Okay, all's good!
Excuse me! Um, I absolutely need flour!
Could you give me a little?
No can do.
I really need it! Please!
No means no.
I feel pitiful for people with no connections.
T-Takumi!
Ah, guy over there, do you have a moment?
I think that should be "mister" to you...
O-Oh! If it isn't the young sir of Kaneari. What brings you here?
I'm actually in the need for a little flour.
Could you give me some?
I can't do that.
C-Can't do it?
Why?
People around the country are troubled because there's no flour.
I can't ignore those people and give young sir special treatment.
That's right.
Me and teacher aren't the only ones who are troubled.
I'm the company president's son!
I know that.
Then, I'll be taking some.
Young sir!
My father is the company president, you know!
Please listen, young sir!
I'll take that as "go ahead"!
You wouldn't mind me, Kouta?
G-Geisters!
Run!
We'll be taking this flour!
This is awful!
All of the flour will be taken!
Exkaiser, come quickly! All of the flour will be gone!
I can't transform in front of all these people...
What should I do...
That's it, I should go inside there...!
L-Let's hurry up and escape!
Get behind the wheel!
Yes!
Go take that flour for Kotomi-chan's sake!
No... No...
Hurry!
Sheesh!
It's not good manners to take other people's stuff behind their backs.
M-My father is a company president, you know!
Change, Exkaiser!
What's taking you so long, Exkaiser?
Come here quickly!
That's...
That's still untouched, I've got to save even if only that much!
All right!
Mister!
Hurry up and escape!
Are you trying to take it secretly again?
Won't it get going!
I'll destroy him with a missile!
Get going! Dammit!
I did it!
Give it back, you damned!
W-Who is it that disrupted me?
You villainous Geisters!
How dare you put your hands on the important food of humans!
I, Exkaiser, won't forgive you!
Exkaiser!
Ugh, you came to bother us again!
Change, Armor Geist!
Change, Ptera Geist!
Why you!
Exkaiser!
Now I gotcha!
Kouta, run away!
You idiot!
Let's go, brother!
Yeah!
Change, Blue Raker!
Change, Green Raker!
Raker Brothers!
Looks like we were just in time.
Let go!
You villainous Geisters,
where did you hide the flour you've stolen until now?
No way we'll tell you!
You'll be soon taken to the Cosmic Court.
If you're silent, your punishment will only get more severe!
As if we'd tell you with such a weak threatening!
What was that?
I-I'll tell you! We discarded the flour on a desert island!
How could you tell so easily! Don't you have the willpower of Geisters?
Never mind willpower, I'd rather get a lighter punishment!
Then take the punishment alone.
Do it!
It got cut!
Go!
Form Up!
Left&Right Fusion, Ultra Raker!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
Kaiser Blaster!
Ultra Canon Beam!
They did it! How amazing!
It got defeated already!
Things are only getting started!
What!
This is this guy's true form!
How terrible!
Kaiser Shot!
Oh no!
This is bad, they got caught!
Try talking back now!
Serves you right!
W-What should I do?
They'll get done in at this rate!
Alright!
Hey! Over here, over here!
There's flour over here!
Now's our chance!
Not good, let's escape!
Kaiser Sword!
Kaiser Flame!
Thunder Flash!
You did it!
As expected from you!
Thank you, Kouta.
You saved us back there.
Nah, don't mention it.
But I wonder where the Geisters hid the stolen flour?
Don't worry, Kouta.
The stolen flour will surely come back to the hands of you humans.
Heaps of the flour that got stolen from all over the country were found on a southern desert island yesterday.
Although it's unknown why heaps of them were found on a desert island,
authorities are transporting them urgently.
How strange...
Kotomi-chan!
I, Kaneari Takumi, have brought you the greatest birthday cake ever!
S-She's not home...?
Kotomi-chan!!
I wonder if teacher will be happy?
Yes, of course she will be!
Safe...
Be careful, Kouta-kun!
You're right, I've got to handle it with more care.
After all, we went through a lot of trouble to get it, right?
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
What's the highest mountain in Japan?
That's right, it's Mt. Fuji!
We're having a camp at it's foot today.
It feels good and it's so much fun!
Huh? What a huge snake!
It's Geisters' sidekick!
They're trying to erupt Mt. Fuji!
Exkaiser, make them stop!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Mt. Fuji Explodes!?
Is there an alien in your home, too?