Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Burning Movie Town
Drive Theater
What a huge screen!
Ice cream
Thank you very much!
It's such an excited feeling to
wait for the movie to start!
I'm excited with just watching a movie with mama.
Oh, papa!
Special News
The castle is...!
Castle Story
Oomaeda Tonari
Work of the Director
Super large scale historical play.
Castle Story.
Coming soon!
Notification of Looking for Actors
Castle Story is currently looking for actors.
They're looking for actors!
Should I join it too?
But they seem to be looking for child actors.
Oh...
Kouta, would you like to participate?
Come on! You'll be a movie star too!
A movie, huh...
Hey! Kouta-kun, Takumi-kun!
It's decided!
What is decided?
Do you know Castle Story? (Shiro Monogatari)
I know it. It's the story about a
dog called Shiro, right?
It's a samurai movie that's currently being filmed!
That's right! They were looking for child actors so I send an application!
Eh? Does that mean that Kotomi-chan is going to be in a movie?
It's not just me, but three altogether.
I send the application as a three person group.
Would Kouta-kun and Takumi-kun like to participate in it with me?
Eh, really?
Alright!
If that's the case, I've got to start
practicing immediately!
W-What are you doing?
I'm practicing my signature.
As I'm finally going to become a movie star!
I'm sure we're just extras among a crowd!
You might be one of the crowd,
but I'll become a celebrity instantly.
Here, you should take one too!
So Kouta is going to be in that movie, too?
Yeah, although just going to the filming location is exciting enough.
What is a filming location?
It's like a factory where movies are made.
That's why movie stars and celebrities gather there.
There's an old town and a future town that are being used in filming.
There's even models for monsters!
That sounds like fun.
Well, I've got to go now.
See you later, Exkaiser!
When I come back from the filming location, I'll tell you more!
Yeah, I'll look forward to it.
Actors' Waiting Room
Obtain your part's costume from here in turn and change into it.
Understood?
Yes!
Kouta-kun, Takumi-kun sure is late...
Now that you mention it...
Ah, he's here!
Everyone, good day!
Kotomi-chan, what do you think? Do I look cool?
That won't do, kid!
Come over here and change to the costume we've arranged for you!
W-Wait, I'll stumble!
Get out of the way!
Director, what an amazing castle this is!
It truly looks like the perfect choice for an epic movie!
I'm the movie!
The castle is only a supporting role in this movie!
That's why this castle will burn down!
Eh, what a waste...
When you think of director Oomaeda, you're known for monster films,
so it's rare for you to do a historical play.
I'm the historical play!
Oomaeda is aiming for the world!
Director! What do you mean with "world"?
Do you think you can get the
International Movie Prize?
I'm the world's Oomaeda!
Movies are the culture of mankind!
They're the treasure of mankind!
Treasure?
Lord Dino Geist, all of them have gathered.
It's your fault for screwing up that we failed.
It's because you do some useless planning...
That's right! It's all Ptera's fault!
What did you say?
Please forgive us!
How many times do you have to disgrace the name of Geisters?
Lord Dino Geist is mad at your incompetence!
Use your head a little more!
W-We're awfully sorry...
The next target is movies!
Movies?
Lord Dino Geist, please leave it to me!
Thunder Geist, you'll go too!
He's an idiot, but he's got strength.
What?
Idiot?
I'm not an idiot!
Do you wanna fight?!
Failures are unforgivable!
Yes, sir!
Why am I a merchant, when you two are a samurai and a princess?
The assistant director said that the merchants were more rich than samurais in this age!
Takumi-kun is rich, so that's why you became a child of a merchant family!
But still, this kimono sure is shabby...
I'm the great director Oomaeda!
Everyone! I'll explain the play to you!
This castle where all of you are in
is in the absolute pinch as it's been surrounded by enemies!
Together with the town children, the feudal lord is trying to help the prince out of the castle,
who is currently wearing kimono of a commoner.
The prince is one of you!
It might you!
Or it might be you!
I understand now! So I'm that prince!
Is that really so...
That'd be interesting if it's true!
Worker Who Holds the Guitar 4
»Ms. Yatsuko, please forget about me.«
»I'll wait... I'll wait forever!«
»Ms. Yatsuko...«
»Mr. Akio...«
Is it this?
Hey! The movie disappeared!
It ran away!
That bastard!
Alright, let's go to the next one!
Ready... Start!
Where are you going?
These are children from the town.
I'm sending them to their homes.
There better not be the prince among them!
I'm the prince!
Cut!
You over there!
Yes!
Don't say unnecessary things!
And besides, you're not the prince!
Oh... So it's not me...
I knew that was the case!
Director! Is there something...?
My vision of the gatekeeper is different...
Yes, so what is your vision?
You newspaper reporter over there!
D-Do you mean me?
Way to go, Mr. Tokuda!
Can I really do it...
The enemies! I want something unexpected...
Do you have a vision for them, director?
Test!
Alright, we're testing this!
Everyone, in your original positions!
Ready! Start!
That's good! Keep on going!
T-They appeared!
Gatekeeper! That's rather good!
D-Director!
They're Geisters!
This is it!
This is exactly what I was looking for!
Let it roll! Keep the camera rolling!
Kotomi-chan, over here!
Where is it? Where is the treasure called "movie"?
It's a big incident!
Dinosaur robots have appeared at the filming location of the Castle Story!
What could their object be?
My camera...
Um, do you know where my camera and bag are?
Search them by yourself!
Which of these is the movie?
It's that!
I have no clue, but if it's something that great
then Lord Dino Geist will be delighted for sure!
Alright!
Change, Armor Geist!
Change, Thunder Geist!
Don't let go of the camera even if you die!
Escape!
W-What are those?
Exkaiser! Geisters appeared at the filming location!
I got it! I'll come immediately!
Max Team, please come back me up!
Geisters are rampaging at the filming location!
Sky Max here, roger!
So it's the filming location, right?
I'll go there full speed!
Do it! Steal that building!
It's awful! The robots are going towards the castle!
They're coming over here!
Alright!
Lift the castle with anti-gravity beams!
What is this sound?
Director, the castle is...!
This is good, it's a great spectacle! Keep the camera rolling!
Camera, my camera...
My scoop...
Exkaiser, come quickly!
That's good! Just a bit more!
I won't let you!
K-Kaisers!
Change, Exkaiser!
Geisters!
We won't let you do as you wish!
It's Exkaiser!
All right!
Gimme that!
This is amazing!
This will be my greatest movie after filming monster movies for 35 years!
No way we'll get captured by you!
Do it!
Leave them to me!
Dash Max!
Spike Cutter!
Screw Cutter!
What!
Dash Max!
Are you alright, Dash Max?
Thanks!
We three are a team!
Let's fight together!
Yeah!
It's a beautiful theme about the friendship of robots!
Alright! Set the castle on fire!
We're going to film fighting robots with the burning castle in the background!
No way!
Director, once it's been burned,
it's the end for that castle!
What are you talking about ending!
Don't you understand that the masterpiece of the century is about to be born?
U-Understood...
The explosive is ready!
Alright, explode it!
What was that sound?
The castle... The castle is on fire!
Director! Everything doesn't seem to be okay...
The children are in the castle's tower!
Put out the fire immediately!
Kouta-kun!
Something awful has happened!
The children are still inside that castle!
Kouta!
How dare you set the treasure on fire without even asking me!
Let go!
Breezing Tornado!
Here's the final blow!
Damn you!
Are you alright?
Exkaiser!
All right!
Damn you...
Guess I'll just have to bring the Kaisers' heads as a souvenir!
Squish those Kaisers!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
Max Team, Form Up!
Triple Fusion, God Max!
We must save the children!
I got it!
God Slicer!
The God Slicer doesn't work!
Kaiser Sword!
That's good! Defeat them just like that!
Are you alright, King Exkaiser?
We must save the children or I won't be able to use Thunder Flash!
Alright! Leave it to me!
King Exkaiser, please distract it.
I leave it to you, God Max!
God Bird Attack!
Thunder Flash!
Kouta-kun, did those robots die?
Exkaiser!
They did it!
Good job, God Max!
Nah, it was nothing special...
Wonderful! It's a very emotional last scene!
Assistant director, we must hire those robots!
Contracts! Let's get contracts!
Director!
Hey, you guys!
Please be in my movie one more time!
No matter at what cost!
It'll definitely be a great hit if you guys are in it!
We're terribly sorry...
Those Kaisers appeared and got in our way.
Please take this for the time being...
Please forgive us!
Damn you, Exkaiser!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
It's time for the once in a year date for Orihime and Hikoboshi.
That's right, it's Tanabata!
I promised with Kotomi-chan that we would go see the Tanabata stars with the latest telescope!
Huh? Sister is going on a date, too?
Eh?! Your date is Dash Max?
What should I do? She'll find out about Exkaiser and the others!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Fuuko's Tanabata Story
Is there an alien in your home, too?