Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
It's Here! Super Giant Fusion
You guys should also do something!
... Is what Lord Dino Geist said!
Even if he tells us to do something...
Is there even a way of beating Exkaiser?
You idiot!
That's exactly why we should do something!
Although it seems like Exkaiser
has gotten a new sword.
Idiot?
Then do you have a good idea?
T-That's...
No thoughts can pop into your heads with those small brains of yours!
What was that?
Small?
Well, just leave it to me. I have a good idea.
The force of the Typhoon 13 that formed in the Pacific Ocean
hasn't weakened at all and the
center pressure is 950mbar...
I'm neither an idiot or small!
Hey, stop it! You bastard!
This year's largest Typhoon 13 becomes more powerful as it's coming from the southern sea.
It's advancing to the Kantou district at the speed of 30km/h.
They said that it's the largest typhoon...
What should we do?
Oh my, it seems scary! I'm getting excited.
Don't say such carefree things!
It's the largest typhoon, you know!
Humans might get flown away, too!
That reminds me that during last year's typhoon Mario's doghouse got blown away and it was terrible...
T-That's right... Something must be done.
However everyone, there's no need to worry.
This is a typhoon removal device Typhoon Buster,
that's recently been developed.
Typhoon Buster?
Typhoons are natural phenomenons that form when the difference in pressure of the surroundings are immense,
but a device that adjusts and weakens that pressure is installed inside this Typhoon Buster.
Against this Typhoon 13...
What does it mean exactly?
It can neutralize the typhoon.
That's why there's no need to worry!
Oh, is that so...
Altitude 15,000m!
We're currently above the typhoon's center.
Activating the propulsion thruster.
Dropping the Typhoon Buster!
It's a success.
Typhoon 13 has been altered to
temperate zone pressure.
It's disappearing gradually.
Alright, experiment is over.
Let's go retrieve Typhoon Buster.
Roger!
How strange...
What's wrong?
Typhoon Buster's response has disappeared from the radar!
What?
It might have fallen in the sea.
That can't be!
Search better!
The connection between what happened in Nazca and me?
That's right! That time you showered in light...
What was that light?
That was...
This is...!
It's certain that someone gave me new powers.
But I don't know who it was...
Someone gave you new powers?
That's right.
Wasn't it one of your comrades?
No, I'm certain that it wasn't one of my comrades.
Then who could it be?
Exkaiser! Exkaiser, please respond!
What's wrong, Sky Max?
I'm currently above the southern sea.
And I just caught a response of Geisters!
What?
Kouta, what happened to the incident of Typhoon Buster disappearing?
They said that it crashed in the sea!
How suspicious...
Mama, look! The sky is so beautiful!
It really is!
Originally a typhoon would've landed here somewhere around this time...
This is all thanks to Typhoon Buster!
Oh no! My hair will get messed up!
What's that sound?
What could it be?
Huh? Could that be the Typhoon Buster that went missing?
Oh my, thunder! It's kind of exciting!
I-It's raining!
Hurricane Bazaar - Now ongoing
Mama, I'm scared!
This is a typhoon!
No way! Why would a typhoon come so suddenly?
It's terrible! A typhoon suddenly appeared in the middle of Tokyo!
That can't be!
I've never heard of a typhoon appearing suddenly!
With its size, Kantou region will
receive great destruction.
What a major incident has happened!
I must return to Tokyo to cover the event!
Just what's going on?
Those are Geisters!
How terrible! I must inform Exkaiser!
So it really was Geisters' doing!
I got it! I'll come there immediately!
Let's take all the treasures in this city
before those Kaisers appear!
That's a good idea!
Alright! Let's get to it!
They're coming this way!
They're so big...
What are you doing, mama?
We must escape quickly!
Oh, that's right.
Those are mine!
How pretty!
Go!
Safety First
Take all of those humans' treasures!
Oh?
I'll go take a look!
Kouta, it's dangerous!
Ah! That really is the Typhoon Buster!
I'll make you real flat!
Here goes!
Change!
Damn you!
Dash Max!
Run, Kouta!
So you appeared, Dash Max!
You villainous Geisters!
Today's the day you won't get away!
Prepare yourselves!
What can you even do alone?
What happened to your friends?
We're right here!
Kaisers have arrived!
Out of the way!
I'll make you drop dead!
Step back!
Exkaiser! Exkaiser!
What?
That's the device that can neutralize typhoons?
But for some reason it's now creating a typhoon!
Damn Geisters!
So you've connected the circuits in reverse.
I got it, Kouta.
I'll get back the Typhoon Buster!
Come, Typhoon Buster!
The typhoon is settling down...
Ah! Typhoon Buster got attached to it!
Max Team, Form Up!
Triple Fusion, God Max!
Left&Right Fusion, Ultra Raker!
First strategy! Do it!
God Sonic Buster!
Oh no!
Spike Cutter!
So the one that's in the face is the Typhoon Buster! Alright!
I did it!
Oh no!
Second strategy!
Aren't they going to escape if we dawdle?
How irritating! Let's go!
W-What?
The buildings are moving!
Oh no!
What is this?
Looks like they can't move at all.
What do you think?
Did you see my perfect strategy?
What are you intending?
This is my intention!
Four General Fusion, Mad Geister!
Seems like we got bigger.
It doesn't seem so! We actually got bigger!
Does it mean that we're 4 times stronger now?
This is great! Let's go, you guys!
W-Why don't we move?
Ugh, we're attached to the shoulders!
Hey, Ptera! What's the meaning of this?
I'm in command of the strategy!
It's obvious that I'm the head!
What?
W-Wait, Thunder! Move according to my strategy!
At this point there's no need for strategies!
Go! Go, Thunder!
Alright, I'll do it too!
Ah, we'll crash!
Alright, now's the chance!
Dragon Jet!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, Dragon Kaiser!
Use your hand to get up, Armor!
Thunder, move your leg out of the way!
Hurry up!
H-He has transformed!
I won't forgive you Geisters!
T-This is bad!
Do something, Ptera!
Dragon Archery!
Thunder Arrow!
Let's escape!
God Max! Please repair Typhoon Buster to its original state.
Looks like it really is impossible for those guys to defeat you.
D-Dino Geist!
Thunder Arrow!
It's useless! I know your techniques
completely already!
Dino Shooter!
Ah! He got captured again!
This is the end of you!
Give up!
I... I can't be defeated here!
Please! Please hang in there, Dragon Kaiser!
Heavens! Please give me powers once more!
Prepare yourself!
Die!
Thunder Storm!
What?
It's useless!
W-What's this power?
I see! I understand now!
The new powers and techniques
I received in that land...
Take a good look at them!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Super Giant Fusion, Great Exkaiser!
W-What's this guy?
He became bigger!
Are you alright?
Sorry to make you worried!
Leave the rest to me!
Dino Shield!
Did you see my powers!
What?
How about this then?
Great Flame!
What great powers!
Kaiser Sword!
Thunder Crash!
Damn!
You better remember this!
Exkaiser!
That was amazing!
Even Dino Geist got so surprised that he ran away!
I finally understand now.
Yeah, the new powers meant this!
Yeah, that's right!
With those powers, you can surely defeat Dino Geist, right?
Yeah, I'll definitely defeat him.
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Are there any mischievous kids around you?
The most mischievous kid in
my class is Ichimura Kosuke.
He's even worse than Geisters!
That kid took my Kaiser bracelet!
What should I do?
Whoa! There's Geisters at a time like this!
Kosuke! Call for Exkaiser!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Friend Is a Young Kabuki Actor
Is there an alien in your home, too?