Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Panda Cub Competition
Bayside Zoo
Look! Look! There's a baby!
It's so cute...
My pocket money will go up 20% just by watching after these guys today!
If I save up this extra money...
Many a little makes a mickle!
Let's go then!
Huh?
Kouta? Kotomi-chan?
Giant Panda
Xiaolong
Xiaolong! Xiaolong!
Xiaolong!
I wonder what's wrong with Xiaolong?
Yeah... Maybe she's feeling bad...
Hi, Kotomi-chan!
Takumi-kun!
What a coincidence!
Oh... Kouta-kun is here too?
Did Takumi-kun come to see Xiaolong, too?
I came here to study the living of this animal that's on the verge of extinction,
this international heritage that's been left behind for humanity.
In other words, you came to see her.
It's studying! Not sightseeing!
Kouta! We're going to the next one!
But sister, Xiaolong is still...
Look here!
The zoo is vast so if you're slow at moving ahead, the day will end!
But we want to see Xiaolong playing happily.
It can't be helped...
Xiaolong! Hey, just for a little bit... Could you face this way please?
Oh my, what a good girl!
Hey!! You panda cub!
What are you acting superior for,
when I'm being nice!
How dare you give that attitude to me!
Can't you even turn around!
My driver! Where's the car? The car!!
Kouta, Kotomi-chan! We must escape!
But what about Xiaolong?
Don't worry! The zoo employees will save her for sure!
But sister...
Just hurry!
Hurry!
Ah! Xiaolong!
There's no time for that! Let's go!
No way...
Exkaiser, Geisters appeared!
What's the place?
The Bayside Zoo!
And what are they targeting?
It's the panda cub!
Geisters are taking away the panda cub!
Chief editor!
Those dinosaur robots have appeared again!
What?
Lo and behold, they appeared at the Bayside Zoo!
There's certainly animals from all around the world there...
But I'm sure they hadn't prepared
a nest for dinosaurs!
You idiot!
Would you just-...
The zoo?
Yes, I'll go to the zoo!
That's not it!
Call for the police and ambulance first!
Kouta and Fuuko are visiting there!
Hey, you guys! Hurry up!
Shut up! Can't you see that we're at it?
That Ptera bastard...
He took the best job just because he can fly...
Well, we gotta beat him with quantity over quality!
I took so many!
Change, Blue Raker!
Change, Green Raker!
Raker Brothers!
Blue Raker! Green Raker!
Villains! Let the animals go!
In your dreams!
"Oh, okay then..." No way we'd say that!
You bastards!
Twin Beam!
Do it! Kill them!
Ah! Xiaolong is...!
Kouta! What are you doing? Come here quickly!
But Xiaolong will be taken away...
Hey! Over here!
Change!
Exkaiser!
This is bad!
Twin Bind Crush!
Exkaiser!
I leave him to you!
Look out!
Kouta! You must escape quickly!
Yeah...
H-Huh? Xiaolong?
Kouta! Over here!
It's not my fault if anything happens, when you're so slow!
Xiaolong! We must escape quickly or you'll get captured again!
See? There's nothing to be scared of anymore!
Xiaolong!
Sheesh! Hurry up!
No! We must take Xiaolong with us!
Come on, let's go!
It doesn't work if you pamper him!
Hey!! Won't you start running?!
Ah! Don't go that way!
As expected from my sister!
Well, obviously!
And it's the best for animals to be running freely!
Let's get going then!
Run! Run!
You attacked the zoo that children enjoy,
and even tried to steal an animal that's on the verge of extinction...
It's absolutely unforgivable!
Ptera, what happened to the treasure?
You guys are so useless that
they snatched it from me!
Give up willingly!
Let's retreat!
Hey! Please don't leave me behind!
Tsk, what a troublesome guy!
That's better!
Wait!
You slow idiot!
We haven't given up yet!
Chief editor!
Big news! This is an international problem!
The monster ruckus is over already.
Kouta and Fuuko were safe.
So we can leave the rest to the police. Go search for a better story!
But this is related to that monster ruckus!
Did the panda turn into a monster this time?
The truth is... It disappeared!
Disappeared?
During that ruckus, the panda cub disappeared!
What did you say?
So cute! Looks like she has become
a bit more energetic!
I'm sure she's happy to be out of that small cage.
Well, obviously!
It's the best for animals to be as nature meant them!
But still...
What?
What should we do?
I'm sure the zoo is having a big commotion because she has disappeared!
It's mama!
Hide her!
I'm coming in!
It sure was a hard day for you!
Especially to you Fuuko, so thank you!
Oh, no such thing! I only did what's expected!
Oh? You've bought a new stuffed toy again?
T-That's right...
It's so cute!
Mama, don't! She's actually very shy!
Oh my, it's very well done!
That's right! The latest ones even eat food!
I'll introduce you to her properly later! Okay?
Should I get her some bamboo grass leaves?
No, it's okay! Because she'll eat anything!
Bye then!
Everyone in this neighborhood!
Have you seen a panda cub?
If you see a panda cub, please tell the police.
A panda cub Xiaolong has gone missing from the Bayside Zoo...
What should we do?
It's such a huge commotion already!
Papa, welcome back home!
Yeah...
Mama! What are the kids doing?
Who knows?
Maybe they're feeding their new stuffed toy?
Feeding a stuffed toy?
Yes! It's very well done.
I heard it's very shy, too.
That's why they're keeping it in the garage.
Very shy?
Earlier it licked my cheek!
Mama! Could it possibly be a stuffed panda toy?
Oh, you know it already?
Fuuko!
Papa, would you like to eat a bamboo shoot?
Kouta, come out!
I know the panda is in there!
Kouta!
No, we can't give her away...
Geisters haven't given up yet!
If we return her to the zoo now,
she'll get targeted again!
Kouta! I won't do anything bad, so open this!
I absolutely can't give her!
Kouta!
A panda is a really important animal on Earth, right?
Exkaiser...
That's why everyone was taking good care of her, right?
Is shutting her in such a small glass room really taking care of her?
That's true...
Their way might've been a little wrong,
but I'm sure those people also wanted to take good care of Xiaolong,
so they're the same as Kouta.
But she'll get targeted by the Geisters again!
We will definitely protect her!
Really?
Yeah, I promise you!
That's too bad...
I would've loved to hug her even just once...
Xiaolong...
Don't worry.
I'll write a main article about how Xiaolong should be let grow up in a vast place.
It's a promise, papa!
Of course!
Kouta...
Kouta!
I'm going to the zoo!
I forgot to say goodbye to Xiaolong!
Kouta...
Come back before dinner, okay!
You're an important product! You won't be killed!
Wait!
What?
Dino Geist!
Now that we Max Team are here,
things won't go your way!
What can the three of you even do?
Change, Dino Geist!
Let's do a three way attack!
Yeah!
Hyper Phonon!
Gatling Smasher!
Turbo Tornado!
You small fry... This is how it's done!
Are you done already? Then it's my turn next!
Even if one's powers wouldn't be enough,
we, Kaisers, combine our strength and won't lose to the likes of you!
I wonder about that...
King Loader!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
Just keep on playing with that!
I won't let you go!
So annoying...
Sky Max!
Exkaiser!
Give it your all!
Please save Xiaolong, Exkaiser!
Kouta!
We will protect Xiaolong!
Really?
I promise you!
I can't lose here...
Exkaiser!
Dragon Jet!
Is that also one of Exkaiser's comrades?
Amazing! Exkaiser is flying in the sky!
Kaiser Wing Break!
Sky Max, are you alright?
Leave the rest to us!
Max Team, Form Up!
Triple Fusion, God Max!
Dino Geist, I'll be taking back Xiaolong!
What's that?
Dammit!
Damn you! We'll finish this battle some other time!
God Sonic Buster!
Thunder Flash!
They did it!
Xiaolong!
So you were safe!
Thank you, Exkaiser!
I'm so glad that Xiaolong is cheerful now.
Papa was telling me, that whether it's about pandas or humans,
they shoudn't be shut in confined places when they're little.
Oh yeah, Ms. Fuuko isn't coming today?
Since she didn't tell about Xiaolong, seems like her pocket money got reduced.
Jeez, it was my chance to get 20% up!
I'm never going to have anything
to do with pandas again!
Mario, no! You can't!
Good for you, Xiaolong.
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Shooting stars are coming in a shower!
I heard that if they'd fell to Earth, the whole world would explode!
But it's alright! Artificial satellites called Sweepers will protect us.
Dino Geist is targeting the Sweepers!
How horrible! The meteorites will be coming soon!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Defeat the Meteor Shower!
Is there an alien in your home, too?