Brave         Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Find the Idols!
In your town and in my town
lies hidden the raw stones that we'll find and turn them into shining jewels!
The ultimate idol producing program!
You Are the Golden Egg!
And here's the idol our program has produced...
It's our very own Morita Kumiko-chan!
Hello! I'm Morita Kumiko!
This Kumirin is really popular at school!
Is that so? I like the good old Hanafusa.
I did it!
I'm going to participate in You Are the Golden Egg!
Look, here's the notice!
Really? On this program?
Yup!
Let's have a great week again and aim to be idols!
Fuuko, if you don't hurry it'll be over! What clothes will you wear?
If you get a taxi, you'll just make it.
Mama, I'm participating next week...
Oh, is that so?
All the idols nowadays have come
from this program.
To think that my sister would be an idol...
Kids like Kouta don't understand
the greatness about me!
Fuuko-chan, give me your signature!
It's not easy to get an idol's signature, right?
That's why I'll get it now...
Mama, my sister isn't an idol yet!
You'll definitely become an idol!
You're my child, after all!
That's what I'm worried about...
You idiots keep on failing time after time!
It's unforgivable to keep on rubbing mud on the name of Geisters!
... Is what Lord Dino Geist said.
When we're getting to the good part,
that Exkaiser and his friends always get in our way...
Please forgive us!
This is the next treasure we're targeting!
Hello! I'm Morita Kumiko!
According to the information, the TV station behind this screen
is a place where they put out idols called golden eggs one after another!
Go steal the whole thing!
You guys, don't fail!
Yes, sir!
How strange... There's no golden eggs here.
Not here!
Not here! Not here! Not here!
Idiot! The treasure is not inside the TVs!
It's at the source where TV is made!
Source?
Isn't it amazing?
My sister is going to be on TV today!
Is it that amazing to be on TV?
That's right!
Most people that appear on TV are celebrities or people who've done bad things!
Has Fuuko-kun done something bad?
Sheesh, Exkaiser! You don't understand anything!
TV informs us about the incidents and news around the world,
creates drama shows, televises sports and wonderful songs.
It's a box of dreams!
I see! A box of dreams, huh...
Anyway, when you appear on TV you can become very popular!
Kouta, Kotomi-chan is here!
I'm coming!
I'm going to the TV station too to cheer on my sister! See you!
What do you think?
Oh, it's great!
Good enough I guess.
Let's go then!
Takumi-kun?
What's up with that outfit?
I just have a little business at the TV station.
Kotomi-chan, if you're going to the TV station too, then please join me.
But Kouta-kun and Ms. Fuuko are...
Isn't it fine that he'll give us a ride!
Come on now, let's hurry...
Um, I meant only Kotomi-chan...
Driver, please hurry!
There's no time to waste!
U-Understood...
Kouta, you have such a good friend!
Y-Yeah...
Why must I give you two a ride, too...
Men don't complain about such small details!
It's not here! Where is the treasure?
Hey! Doesn't this factory produce idols that are called golden eggs?
Idols? T-They are at the TV station!
So please don't eat me!
TV station?
Ah, I've seen that face on TV!
By the way, why did you come here?
Can't you tell by looking?
Please give me your signature!
That person that I got the signature from has the best record of being killed in detective dramas!
Amazing...
Since you're at it, you should get a better TV talent's signature...
Ah, it's the Justice Police Mekaman!
I watch it every week!
I'd love to get the signature of Mr. Okada Takeshi!
Sheesh!
Ms. Fuuko, shouldn't we head to the open-air stage now before it starts?
There's still time.
I thought there'd be more stars inside the TV station, but there sure isn't many...
Ah, look! It's Shibata Kouhei!
It really is! Hey, please give me one!
Um, please give me your signature!
Signature? Sorry, but I have some
urgent business to do!
Sorry!
Wait! Please!
We'll get scolded if we enter here!
It's fine! My father is a sponsor of this TV station!
Huh? There's only veneer in this room...
They're filming the Justice Police Mekaman!
That sea monster Lagas is an unfair guy.
Take this!
That's unfair!
Damn you, let go!
Stop it, sea monster Lagas!
Don't!
Cut! Cut!
Who are you? We're filming for real here!
I'm sorry!
Huh?
Ah, Mr. Tokuda!
What are you doing here?
I came here to interview the currently
very popular idol, Morita Kumiko-chan!
Really?
Well, when one becomes a huge star like her, they won't do interviews unless it's from a talented reporter.
Mr. Tokuda! Please take us with you!
Pretty please!
Okay, you can come.
All right!
Changing room
I've had enough!
A manager like you is fired! Fired, I say!
Please don't be so selfish...
I hate this job!
I can only sleep 2 hours every day
and today I haven't even eaten!
Seems rough.
That's Kumirin who's always smiling on TV?
No! I'm telling you no!
Who are you people?
Um, I'm Tokuda from Touto Newspaper.
I came here to get an interview...
And a signature too!
We're busy at the moment! Leave this for later!
Just leave me alone!
Hey! Where are they making those idols that are called golden eggs?
U-Um... T-This is a relay station...
We don't make anything here,
you need to go to a bigger TV station...
A bigger TV station, huh?
That's Geister!
Exkaiser, Geister has appeared!
Where?
He was in a TV relay station in the mountains, but he got away already...
What? Kouta and the others have gone to a TV station today.
I hope nothing happens...
In your town and in my town
lies hidden the raw stones that we'll find and turn them into shining jewels!
The ultimate idol producing program!
You Are the Golden Egg!
Sister! Do your best!
And here's the idol our program has produced...
It's our very own Morita Kumiko-chan!
Hello! I'm Morita Kumiko!
Kumirin!
Perhaps because we saw Kumirin earlier...
It kinda puts you off...
Yeah...
Amazing!
So cool!
Is this an ad for a movie?
There's no such guest written in the scenario...
It's a scoop!
It came over here!
Exkaiser! Geisters have appeared at the TV station!
Please come quickly!
I got it! I'll come immediately!
I-It's coming this way! Help me!
Are you the idol that's called a golden egg?
Please stop this! Don't come here!
I'll be taking you.
Stop it!
Don't touch Kumirin!
You bastard!
Kumirin, we must escape!
Kouta, over here! Quickly!
Kumirin...
Kumiko-chan, are you alright?
You sure have guts to say that
as you ran away first!
Idol! I won't let you escape!
Change, Horn Geist!
Help us!
We must escape inside the TV station!
What are you doing? Keep the camera rolling!
Kouta! Please be safe...
This is an emergency news flash!
Look at this! That ruffian robot has just now appeared at the TV station!
You'll get stepped on if you stay there!
Escape quickly!
No! I have the duty to do this news flash!
Is she a golden egg too?
Idiot! Idols are much younger!
I know that!
I'm so bitter! So bitter!
Let's escape now!
How can this be!
The steel tower turned into a robot!
Where's the TV camera? Cameraman, over here!
The treasure is inside that building! Go!
It's coming this way!
What did I do to deserve this? Help me!
Change, Exkaiser!
You villainous Geisters!
How dare you destroy the broadcasting station that creates dreams for humans, and attack the weak ones!
I, Exkaiser, won't forgive you!
Exkaiser!
So it's you again, Exkaiser...
Today's the day we won't let you bother us!
Change, Ptera Geist!
Yeah, attack however you like!
Look at this!
In order to protect us from those ruthless and nasty evil robots,
the robot of justice has arrived!
Alright! It's a scoop!
Huh? My camera... My camera's not here!
Spike Cutter!
Change, Thunder Geist!
What's the matter? Try saying something!
Alright! Go steal the treasure by
taking the whole building!
Why must I go through all this?!
Things have taken an awful turn!
It's trying to steal mankind's remarkable
broadcasting station along with the building!
And the reliable ally of justice has been captured!
Let go!
Don't rampage!
I want to stop being an idol already!
Kumirin, don't say that!
Please get a grip!
Look!
That robot is doing his best in order to protect you!
If Kumirin stops being an idol,
we won't know anymore for what reason that robot is fighting for!
Well? Are you giving up?
This'll be like carrying a playing child on our back!
Lord Dino Geist, I have captured Exkaiser!
I'm the one who captured him!
Give that back, you bastard!
I'm the one who made this plan!
What are you doing? The glory is mine!
Are you trying to take the glory all by yourself?
I'm the one!
Me!
It's me!
Jet Boomerang!
Lord Dino Geist!
You idiots!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
Let go of that building!
Kaiser Shot!
Kaiser Blaster!
Oh no! That was a dirty trick!
Kaiser Missile!
Anti-Gravity Beam!
He did it!
He got the broadcasting station
back from the bad guys!
Kaiser Wing Break!
Kaiser Sword!
Kaiser Flame!
It's over now!
Let's scatter!
Thunder Flash!
He did it! He did it!
He did it!
So that robot saved me...
I'll become an idol that won't lose to that robot!
What will you do, sister?
I'm calling it quits! I don't want
to sleep for only 2 hours.
It's much easier to just watch TV.
I agree!
Dino Geist!
I know that you're watching this TV!
Geisters' crimes that torment the people on Earth...
I, Exkaiser, won't forgive them!
We, Kaisers, will defeat your evil doings!
And Dino Geist!
We will definitely capture you!
Damn you, Exkaiser!
I will go next time!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Blue sky and blue sea as far as you can see...
It's only for one day, but we got on a super luxury liner for a relaxing cruise.
Isn't it nice?
But the whole ship got captured by Geisters!
Eh? That black robot is Dino Geist?
It's much bigger than King Exkaiser!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Go! Go! Luxury Liner
Is there an alien in your home, too?