Brave         Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Monster Library
"It's our final showdown at last."
"I'll definitely defeat your magic ball!"
"Bring it on!"
It always says "To be continued" when it gets to the good stuff!
To think that you're infatuated
with such a stupid book...
It makes me wonder about your mental age...
What did you say?
Takumi-kun, what do you read?
The Cool Ways to Spend Money
I read this!
It's full of kanji!
It tells about how the richest millionaire of all ages in our country used his fortune.
This book is much more stupid!
I think it's far more meaningful
to read it than these comics!
It's the teacher!
Kouta-kun, do you know what day is tomorrow?
Um... It's the Culture Day!
That's right.
It's a day when we think about our culture and strive to do something cultural.
And thus!
Book report homework?
Each of you should read a new book and bring a report of it the day after tomorrow. Understood?
We sure got an awful homework...
Is that so? I love both reading books and writing reports.
Kouta-kun! How about we go to the bookstore now?
Takumi-kun, would you come too?
Takumi-kun!
Please don't bother me...
I'm at an important part now...
Takumi! Look in front!
I see... When you pay, you should act like you don't care about the amount of money.
So that's how you'll look cool-...
Takumi...
T-This sure is useful...
Book Center
Kotomi-chan, did you decide?
Look! This book is cute, right?
Thumbelina
It really is!
I've loved it since I was little!
Biography Series
Biography series, huh...
Edison! Lincoln! And then...
Kaneari Takumi
It's obvious that my book will also be here eventually!
Autobiography
Kaneari Takumi's Story
What are you smirking about by yourself?
Y-You wouldn't understand what a person like me with great ambitions would think about!
I bet you were thinking that your name could be in the biography series, right?
Instead of bothering others, how about
you go decide a book for yourself!
I know that...
I wonder what book would be interesting...
Book report homework, huh...
Do you have any interesting books?
Alright, alright! Just leave it to your big sister!
This is "The Idol of Love and Sadness."
Idol boy and girl get torn apart even though they love each other...
This is "The Stewardess of Love and Sadness."
It's a story where a stewardess and pilot
break up even though they love each other.
And then this is...
"The Nurse of Love and Sadness."
It's a story where a nurse and a young doctor can't be together even though they love each other.
They were all so romantic and great!
You!
School Uniform of
Love and Sadness
If you aren't moved by this,
you aren't my little brother, okay!
"On the day of the high school exam, Rika arrived with a pale face."
"Teacher, I'm done for. I can't pass it..."
I can't do it!
What's so interesting about this book...
If only this was a comic, I could read it many times without getting bored...
Comics are interesting in their own way,
and books are interesting in their own way, right?
Don't you think that it'd be a wonderful thing to enjoy both of them, instead of only one?
I understand that, but...
Thanks to letters and books, people on Earth can share their own thoughts and experiences
to many people regardless of era.
For some time now, I've been thinking that
such a wonderful invention can rarely be found even if searched through the vast space.
But I get sleepy by just seeing a paper
that's full of letters...
Isn't that because you're reading it unwillingly?
You wouldn't get sleepy by reading
a book that you like, right?
Yeah... Both Kotomi-chan and Takumi have their favorite books...
I'm the only who doesn't know what books I want to read...
If you search with all your might, I'm sure there will be a book that you'll love.
Do you really think that?
Yeah! I'm sure of it!
Alright!
I'll go to the bookstore again tomorrow...
And I'll try to find an interesting book!
Kid, you still haven't decided?
Wait a bit more!
It's Geister!
Oh! This is a mountain of treasures!
My shop is...!
Publication Delivery Center
Kino Publisher (Ltd.)
Geisters have quickly disappeared after attacking various bookstores, printing factories and publishers in the city.
How troublesome...
I wanted a new cookbook...
What should I do?
This is Exkaiser!
Geisters are targeting books.
Please keep an eye on mainly bookstores, publishers and printing factories!
Roger!
"And then a huge thing came flowing from the river like whoosh whoosh..."
What's so interesting about this?
I don't know!
But since they're important for humans, I'm sure they are of some use.
Delicious!
Lord Dino Geist!
You idiots!
Looks like you forgot to attack the most crucial place!
... Says Lord Dino Geist who's angry at you!
The most crucial place?
If you attack that place, you can get different kinds of books!
... Is what Lord Dino Geist is saying!
That place?
But it seems like humans really
like these things called books...
Yeah... There's shops that sell books everywhere, after all.
That's so true! They never let go of books.
Are books really that interesting?
I-I didn't know that there exists such an interesting thing in the world!
Get the car ready!
We're going to the library to read comics!
Understood!
There sure is a lot of people, chief editor...
Well, this library is currently the only place in the city
where you can read any kinds of books.
Dear! I found a nice cookbook!
Oh, that's good.
Sparks are always flying from you two, chief editor! Oh you!
"This will be my final punch!"
"What?!"
"Super Delicious Final Punch!"
C-Comics are way too interesting!
Are you perhaps... Takumi?
You're mistaken.
Young sir! It's soon time to head home.
I-I only read it a little on the way to borrow the biography of Napoleon!
You sure were reading it eagerly
even though it was just on the way...
It's a misunderstanding! I wouldn't read comics...!
Kouta! Fuuko!
Mama!
T-The library...!
It turned into a robot!
Alright! Carry it away like that!
Exkaiser!
Geisters appeared at the library!
Got it! Just wait, Kouta!
Change, Exkaiser!
All the books will be taken!
Wait, Geisters!
He's here again!
You bastard!
Those who try to steal the culture that people on Earth have established and cherished...
I won't forgive them!
We've been waiting for you!
Mr. Exkaiser, do your best!
You're repeating yourself!
Take this!
Flaming Nova!
Oh no!
The books will burn!
What?
I'll end up burning the books inside
if I attack thoughtlessly...
That bastard stopped attacking!
Kill him now!
Exkaiser!
Sorry for the wait, Exkaiser!
Change, Blue Raker!
Change, Green Raker!
Twin Bind Crush!
Exkaiser! Now's the chance!
Dragon Jet!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, Dragon Kaiser!
Dragon Kaiser!
Do your best!
I can't use missiles and beams...
Dragon Anchor!
Dragon Boomerang!
Dragon Kaiser!
This isn't good! He'll get defeated!
What's the matter, Dragon Kaiser?
If I continue fighting like this, I'll end up burning the books that are inside!
Kouta!
I want you to tell me the temperature when books start burning!
Temperature when books burn?
If I know that, I can control the temperature so the books won't burn and attack this guy!
I don't know the temperature!
Kouta, you humans have books!
The answer can surely be found from a book!
That's right! Just wait, Dragon Kaiser!
Kouta! Where are you going?
I'm sure that Dragon Kaiser can't attack because he's worried about the books!
So I just need to tell him the temperature when books start burning!
I see!
Good job for realizing that!
As expected from Kouta-kun!
I'll go too!
Me too!
I'm counting on you, Kouta!
Don't let them run around!
Oh no!
Hurry, hurry...
It's not this! Or this... or this...
We must hurry or things will be bad!
I found it!
Found it?
Is that true, mama?
Now I can make today's supper!
Now's a good time to take the rest of the treasures.
My eyes start hurting from all these small letters...
Papa!
Kouta-kun, it's no use! Let's escape!
Dammit!
I won't let you!
Look out!
I know it!
What a persistent guy!
What are you doing? Kill him already!
Dragon Kaiser!
Kouta!
The temperature when books start burning is...
Fahrenheit 451!
Fahrenheit 451
Thank you, Kouta!
Green Raker! Blue Raker!
Are you alright?
You must escape quickly!
Changing Dragon Thunder's
temperature to Fahrenheit 451!
Dragon Thunder!
Twin Beam!
They did it!
The library broke free!
Dammit!
The treasure is...!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Super Giant Fusion, Great Exkaiser!
You guys should combine too!
Alright! Kill him!
Twin Kick!
Escape!
Great Cannon!
Kaiser Sword!
Raker Hurricane!
Thunder Crash!
Good job, Exkaiser!
You're the best!
Thanks to your help, I managed to protect your important books.
Your culture was protected by the power of books that you yourselves have created!
It's so great that the books are safe!
So great that the comics are safe!
No... Uh...
Around the World in Eighty Days
Fabre's Book of Insects
A Trip to the Moon
20,000 Leagues Under the Sea
You borrowed so much at once...
What should I do?
I haven't read a single one yet!
It's not my problem, okay...
Seems like it'll take some more time till Kouta understands the appeal of books.
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Everyone, do you like horses?
I got to ride on a horse with the
help of rider Mr. Takara!
The horse was bigger than I thought and its eyes were very gentle!
I bet it's a nice feeling when you win in a race while riding that horse!
Whoa! It's Geisters! They're targeting the horse!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Become the Wind, White Horse
Is there an alien in your home, too?