Brave         Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He's the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
I'm a Jet Pilot
This is the 400:1 model of the supersonic jet Condor
we're going to see on our field trip tomorrow.
I especially ordered this and had it made.
Awesome! So cool!
How wonderful.
The hero of the sky is soon to be the Condor.
That's why my family intends to buy
two or three of them in different colors.
We're thinking of placing the order some time soon...
Kouta-kun!
You made this, Kouta-kun?
This is my original paper airplane.
It looks a bit like the Condor, right?
Can you teach me how to fold it?
Yup, sure.
That's nothing! My Condor can fly that much, too!
Here it goes!
Takumi, you idiot.
The supersonic jet Condor is supposed to be in Japan for a demonstration
so it left America's airport this morning, followed by many cheers.
The Condor can even get close to the stratosphere
and it can fly from New York to Tokyo in only two hours.
Look at that! It's faster than you.
That lousy airplane can't even fight. It's no match for me.
But in terms of speed, you can't beat it.
Shut up already, you want to fight?
No, I didn't mean it like that.
You only told the truth.
Stop it!
I'll tell you lord Dino Geist's next command.
What's our next target?
Since the flying of that is shown off to many people, it has to be a very important treasure.
Go snatch that supersonic airplane!
... Is what he said.
Interesting, that cheeky plane won't even know what hit it when I get to it.
Come on everybody, we're going there to study. Don't be too wild!
Paper airplanes are only primeval toys after all.
As we live in the future, we should pay attention to the latest technology.
Hey, Kouta-kun!
Huh, Mr. Tokuda?
Are you going to see the Condor, too?
Yup, Mr. Tokuda's doing an interview for it?
Yes, I predicted a traffic jam, so I came with my scooter.
Sorry, but I'll be going ahead!
Mr. Tokuda, look out!
How nice, young people are so full of energy.
There's the Condor!
Here it comes.
Wait a minute!
I made it in time.
Good for you.
If I'd miss the moment of the landing,
the chief editor would scold me again.
Such a loud noise!
Listen here, the landing is called the final approach.
I've heard that it's the most difficult thing to pilot.
You sure know a lot, tell me more.
Alright, ask me anything.
Final approach, huh?
So cool...
I wonder which one would be faster compared to Exkaiser and the others.
So that's it? Looking all expensive and stuff.
Alright.
Seems like it's on standby on this airport.
Hello, feel free to explore.
So this will be the hero for day trips between United States and Japan, huh?
But what does it matter to be in such a hurry?
It feels good to fly fast!
Cool...
An earthquake!
Oh no!
What on earth?
It's alright, please don't leave from the seats!
Everyone, please calm down!
Calm down and sit in the seats!
God, please protect the children...
What on earth is this?
I don't really understand, but anyway, it's a scoop! I'll have the top story!
Starting the engine.
But there's almost no fuel!
Our only chance is to fly.
Mom...
Kouta-kun...
It's alright! Everything's alright, Kotomi-chan. It's okay...
This is bad, don't let the Condor get away!
Something unexpected happened to the airport, so we had to emergency takeoff.
But please be calm, everyone!
It's the Geisters!
I must inform Exkaiser.
Exkaiser, it's terrible! The Geisters appeared!
What?
Exkaiser, come quickly.
Kouta, where's the place?
Airborne over the airport.
Alright, I'll come immediately.
Mario, you mustn't misbehave!
Dash Max, Sky Max, Drill Max!
Please hurry to the airport!
Alright, I got it.
Roger, airport it is then.
The sky is my speciality.
Everyone, please feel at ease. We're now flying steady.
Now all's that left is to fly to some other aiport, huh?
Such a a good luck to be able to board the flying Condor, right?
I can't just sit around, I have to get an exclusive interview from the pilot.
Excuse me, guest, do you need something?
As a newspaper reporter, I'd like get an interview from the captain.
I can't allow that! Only the personnel can go in.
Well, don't be so formal.
I definitely won't be bothering their work.
Guest!
I'd like to interview you...
We don't have time for that.
Is there a problem?
This plane hasn't been refueled since it left America.
Even if we fly slowly, it'll only last for about ten minutes!
Ten minutes is it?
No way!
Only ten minutes?
This is bad!
Exkaiser, things have taken a serious turn!
What's wrong, Kouta?
Although we took off, there's no fuel and it can only fly for ten minutes!
You must stay calm, I will definitely save you.
Although they made a scene about the speed, it sure is lagging.
Seems like a rescue aircraft came!
It's a bird.
It's a Pteranodon!
Stay at your seats, you must stay calm!
Mr. Tokuda!
Did you find out anything?
Why's it flying so slowly?
Well...
This airplane is the fastest in the world, right?
Well, there's a lot of reasons...
Could it be that there's no fuel?
You're wrong, there's no such thing.
It must be that it can only fly for five minutes.
No, it's not that!
It can fly double that, so rest assured-...
My intuition is truly magnificent.
Ten minutes?
Damn it!
So if they want to, they can go faster.
Captain, it can't hold any longer!
It can't be helped.
It became slow again...
You're not escaping!
Captain!
We're done for, there's no pilot anymore!
The pilot's gone?
Goddamn, someone take responsibility for this!
Isn't there parachutes? Parachutes-...
Now I gotcha.
I won't let you!
Sky Max!
Drill Max!
Change, Exkaiser!
You villain's sidekick, come on!
Captain, please get a grip.
Exkaiser, the pilot lost his consciousness.
Calm down, Kouta.
Even if you say that...!
At times like this, the true hero is the one who brings out his courage!
I'll definitely save you, so calm down other people in the meantime.
Exka-...
I must have courage.
What're you going to do?
Calm down and don't leave your seats.
Everyone, please look over here!
Even a paper airplane like this can fly.
So there's no way this plane, that's controlled by people, will crash down.
H-How stupid...
The kid is more level-headed than us.
How embarassing for us.
Kouta-kun!
I don't want to die together with that idiot!
Impact Flash!
Drill Max, Dash Max!
We'll help you!
Crush them all!
King Loader!
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
Captain, captain!
It's no use, he's completely unconscious.
It's the end for us!
Exkaiser, it's about to crash down!
Kouta, attach the Kaiser Bracelet to the cockpit's computer.
I'll take the lead after that.
But how can I attach it...
Press the right button in the Kaiser Bracelet.
Right button?
Awesome!
Follow me, Kouta-kun.
Sky Max!
Dash, Drill!
Change, Sky Max!
Let's combine!
Max Team, form up!
Triple Fusion, God Max!
Are you okay, King Exkaiser?
God Max, the Condor will soon come down. Let's hurry up!
Alright, let's do a simultaneous attack!
God Sonic Buster!
Kaiser Sword!
Thunder Flash!
Dammit, you better remember this!
Kouta, grab the control stick.
The airport is in bad shape, landing is impossible if it's not done manually!
No way!
Bring out your courage.
Alright...
Kouta-kun!
Everyone, it's dangerous if you're not in your seats.
That's right.
Everyone, please fasten your seat belts!
What happened to the pilot?
It's the final approach!
Kaiser Blast!
Let's go.
Kouta-kun, you did it!
That was wonderful, Kouta-kun.
I did it, Exkaiser...
You did great, Kouta.
Are you okay, Kouta-kun?
Y-Yeah...
That sure was thrilling, I'd love to ride it one more time!
Please, Kouta-kun! Let me ride it once more.
I've had enough of fast stuff! Right?
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Has everyone ever gone cherry-blossom viewing?
Mr. Tokuda and others drink sake, sing karaoke and have a great time there.
They don't even look at the cherry-blossoms, how weird.
But it's really beautiful when the cherry-blossoms fall like snowflakes.
Exkaiser! Don't let the Geisters bother the cherry-blossom viewing!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Buddha Rampage at the Hanamiyama
Is there an alien in your home, too?