Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Time Is a Mess
Great Treasure Exhibition 13F         Summer Fair
Kotomi-chan is so late...
Today is the Anniversary of Time!
Unbelievable that she's late on the Anniversary of Sky Time!
At 2:30 we'll watch a movie,
at 4 we'll have tea,
and at 5 it's study time!
My perfect schedule is falling apart!
That's because you made a too
detailed time schedule.
You should be like me and just be like "At afternoon it's playing time!"
I'm going to become a man who carries Japan on his shoulders!
No way I could make a loose schedule like you!
Kouta-kun!
I'm sorry!
I was thinking of what to wear so I came a little late!
Don't worry about it! About 30 minutes don't even feel like we waited!
You sure are one to talk!
You were angry just a minute ago...
So cute!
This is an atomic clock that shows the standard time.
Around the world, people match their country's time to this atomic clock
and so they can show the exact time.
T-The world's time...!
P-President!
It's so awful!
The Kyuuku department store's mechanism clock disappeared!
No! It was the flower clock that
disappeared, right?
No, the mechanism clock!
The flower clock!
Why are you fighting?
You can find that out by reading papa's newspaper.
There's no need to wait for the evening paper!
Today afternoon, starting from the atomic clock of world's standard time,
incidents where rare clocks were stolen from all over the world happened.
Sapporo's clock tower and London's Big Ben are both now lost.
So it wasn't only the mechanic clock that disappeared!
According to witnesses,
they've said that a dinosaur took them, but there's no positive proof.
It's Geisters!
What? Rare clocks are being targeted?
That's right.
Please be on alert.
OK, since there's a rare clock here too.
Alright! I'll dash through a second round!
Change, Thunder Geist!
That's it.
What's wrong, Dash Max?
Did something happen?
I just slipped a little.
Those damn Geisters ruined our race again!
What? I'll come immediately!
Don't try to do the impossible!
Nah, don't be worried.
I'll beat them up easily!
Change, Dash Max!
As long as I, Dash Max, exist
your evil doings are absolutely unforgivable!
Shut up!
Help me!
Look out!
There we go...
I won't let you escape!
Dash Max, answer! Dash Max!
This is bad...!
This is a payback from the other time!
This is for the time before that!
If you don't stop soon,
he won't be much of a hostage!
This is more important now.
I'm sure we can sell this much rare
clocks at a high price!
Hey! I stole most of them,
so my share must be the biggest!
What was that?
I'll obviously get the best share,
since I'm the one who thought of this!
I'll get the best!
You haven't even worked that much!
Why you...!
Don't forget about me-...
Shut up!
Be quiet! Be quiet!
I'm the best!
Leave the fighting among yourselves for later and look at this!
Installation of the spare atomic clock has been finished successfully.
With this, all the clocks around the world have regained the standard time.
Now who was it that said that there's only one atomic clock?
No way I could know there's a spare one!
Damn, they're playing dirty...
The clocks would be a treasure,
if there's only one of them in the world!
It's no treasure if two of them exist!
... Is what Lord Dino Geist said.
Hey, what'll we do?
We'll just have to make the other clocks out of order, right?
This place was safe, huh?
But they're only stealing clocks... Could it be because today's the Anniversary of Time?
This is the mechanic clock of the Kyuuku department store!
But that couldn't be... Since it got stolen.
Huh, if it isn't the atomic clock!
As expected of the clock museum,
it's got everything!
Bastards! Don't think you'll get off easy for doing this!
Seems like you still want us to pay attention to you! There you go!
Change, Ptera Geist!
Alright, let's start!
Yeah!
What's going to start?
Well, just watch!
Sapporo's clock tower and other
various tourist places-...
We're sorry for that. We'll continue the news.
This piece of news seems to tell something about that recent shock wave...
Currently...
Seems like clocks have broken all about.
What's going on?
Exkaiser!
I flew in a 5 km radius around the race area, but I didn't get any response.
This is Blue Raker.
I went as far as 20 km from the race area, but I couldn't catch a response from Dash Max.
I see.
Exkaiser!
What's the matter, Kouta?
All the clocks in the world broke at the same time!
Could this be the work of Geisters?
What did you say?
Hello!
Our spare atomic clock is broken too.
I don't know the exact time!
By the way, what time is it?
When is the 18:00 train arriving?
Well, the 17:00 train hasn't arrived yet...
So what's going on with that 17:00 train?!
I do not know!
Even I don't know which trains are running at the moment!
Good evening, everyone.
It's time for the 3 o'clock news.
Don't lie! What do you mean "3 o'clock news"?
It's already dark outside! It's nighttime!
You'd better show our drama!
Wait!
The 3 o'clock...
Mr. Takeshi...
news...
Ms. Aiko...
are starting.
Chief editor, this is all of them.
Yeah.
I wonder why we became so busy when there's no clocks...
Chief editor!
The sun is rising!
What?! Get the manuscripts printed quickly!
Yes!
Chief editor, I am getting paid for overtime, right?
If you have time to think about useless things...
Hurry up!!
Y-Yes!
I'm home...
It's papa!
Papa!
Are you alright?
We're home...
Oh my...
I'm tired!
Same here... The classes were longer than usual.
What are you saying?
They were actually shorter than usual.
Because that tree's shadow
is currently in that position...
So it's 3 o'clock!
I got it!
It's the theory of the sun watch!
I learned it in grade school!
As expected from Mr. Tokuda, you are so educated!
Oh come on now, madam! Don't tease me!
I'm sleepy too...
Let's expand the scope of our search.
Blue Raker should head west as till now.
Green Raker should head north.
Roger!
Have you found out something?
No...
But you sure look tired.
It's such a mess now that the clocks are broken.
Aren't clocks only machines that punctuate time?
So why all this just because such things broke...?
Now that clocks are gone, I realized for the first time,
that punctuating time is really important!
If you don't know the punctuation,
you just keep on studying or working
and that's what makes you tired!
So clocks are very important, huh?
And those Geisters dare mess with such important things!
This is Blue Raker!
Exkaiser, I've caught an unidentified energy wave!
What?
Hey, let's get rid of those rare clocks already and make Lord Dino Geist delighted!
Yeah... It's about the time I'll get contacted by the space merchant.
I bet those humans have now learned the dread of us Geisters!
That's true!
This guy is still alive.
You villains!
Now's the only time you'll be able to laugh!
You're one to talk!
I'll laugh as much as I want to!
Change, Sky Max!
Change, Drill Max!
Dash Max!
Are you alright?
Yeah...
We won't let you take our capture so easily!
I'll pay you back!
Please stop it!
My captures!
Change!
Exkaiser!
Dash Max! Thank god you're okay!
I-I'm sorry, everyone!
You couldn't stop with just stealing clocks from around the world,
so you dared to steal time from humans
and disrupt the peace!
It's unforgivable!
Damn you!
Those are the stolen clocks!
Kill him!
That was close...
Sky Max, Drill Max! You two should protect Dash Max!
Yeah!
Don't get in our way!
Jet Boomerang!
What a horrifying power!
Oh no!
Prepare yourself!
Change, Blue Raker!
Change, Green Raker!
Raker Brothers!
Twin Kick!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
Left&Right Fusion, Ultra Raker!
Kaiser Shot!
Ultra Chain Crusher!
Kaiser Blaster!
We did it!
It's still moving!
Ultra Raker!
Have you learned your lesson?
Sky Max, Drill Max!
Let's combine and I'll aid too!
But it's impossible in your condition!
It's not the time to be saying that!
Let's combine!
Max Team, Form Up!
Triple Fusion, God Max!
God Max!
God Cosmic Bomber!
This is bad, let's retreat for now!
Damn!
Do it now, King Exkaiser!
Kaiser Sword!
Thunder Flash!
All right! The clocks are fixed!
I'm sure it was Exkaiser and the others.
Kouta, feel at ease.
The time has returned to you humans!
Thank you, Exkaiser!
Time has come back.
This afternoon at 15:05, the various clocks around the country
have returned to normal
simultaneously for some reason.
Now the next news,
the clocks that were stolen around the world were found in faraway mountains.
Papa, the morning paper came only now.
And it's this thick! What happened?
Well... It's just that... How should I put it...
Anyway, it's good that everything solved!
Huh? You were fine even without a clock, mama?
I'm fine even if there's no clock,
but if there's no clock then papa gets busy, right?
It's the best when there's a clock and papa is right next to me. Right, papa?
Oh well...
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Red, blue, yellow, purple and... Um...
Even if I can't say all 7 colors,
rainbows are really pretty, right?
We're going on a hiking to the
Rainbow Waterfall today!
But even Geisters came along with us!
How horrible! The dam's water is overflowing!
The town will be filled with water!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Great Flood at the Rainbow Waterfall
Is there an alien in your home, too?