Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Retrieve Summer!
What's wrong, Mario?
Did the heat get the best of you?
I did it...
I did it! That's it for today's homework!
I'm going to the pool!
Oh... Kouta, what about homework?
I did all of today's share!
How strange...
Today's share came only now.
See?
I bet you were just playing and didn't do yesterday's share.
If you want to go to the pool,
do today's homework first.
That's right!
It says here that it's "every day's study", right?
If you don't do it every day, it's meaningless!
Damn...
Did you do your today's share then, sister?
Of course! Well then, I'm going to the pool!
I had already promised Kotomi-chan
that we'd go to the pool...
Hey, can I do this homework in the night?
That's fine by me.
But the fireworks festival is this night, right?
Ah! That's right!
Didn't you make promises for the fireworks festival too, Kouta?
I think it's better to do your homework early.
Why do I have to do homework every day
when it's the long-awaited summer vacation...
Oh, Kotomi-chan!
Ms. Fuuko, where's Kouta-kun?
You're waiting for Kouta?
Yes!
That kid is still doing his homework.
Forget about him and let's go swimming together!
I've bought a new swimsuit!
Okay? Let's go!
But...
It's fine! You'll just get hot by
standing here, right?
Sheesh, Kouta-kun... I guess it can't be helped.
Ms. Fuuko, are you ready yet?
Here I come...
What do you think?
Wow, it's so stylish!
Right? This was quite expensive.
Come on! The poolside is waiting for the queen of swimsuits!
It's an earthquake!
I-It appeared!
W-What?
Alright, here I go!
I'll definitely learn how to swim and invite Kotomi-chan to this pool!
H-How was it? I swam at least 3 meters, right?
Well... It was more like 30 centimeters...
W-What?
I'm falling!
I'll be taking this!
Hey! Give it back! My pool!
Eh? The pool got stolen?
That's right!
I had just bought a swimsuit and now there's no place to swim!
There's a pool at school too, right?
I'm saying that the school's pool got stolen also!
The pool robberies have spread out to nearby regions, leaving everyone involved in confusion.
What could be the intention of this crime?
According to this piece of news I just received,
the Homework Forwarding Center, that sends summer vacation's homework to many households via fax
seems to have been attacked by dinosaur robots called Geisters.
After this, we'll show you the scene...
Homework Forwarding Center?
I'm here at the Homework Forwarding Center.
Look at this!
The dinosaur robots have stolen all of the summer vacation's homework that were in this center.
Manager, do you have any comment?
All compulsory school students in the country!
Everyone's important summer vacation's homework was stolen!
I'm really sorry!
Sorry?
Even though homework is gone?
That's way too silly, right?
Homework is gone! Yay!
Those Geisters do good things once in a while!
Is it alright for homework to be gone?
Of course!
It was all homework's fault that
I couldn't go to the pool!
But the pool got stolen too, right?
That's a problem...
It's boring that there's no pool even though it's summer vacation!
Summer vacation's homework and pool, huh...
Kouta, it could be that Geisters are targeting things that are related to summer.
Things related to summer?
Chief editor!
What? Don't shout right next to my ear!
Chief editor, there's been trouble!
Then say what's the trouble already!
Things have been stolen again!
Ice making factory, ice cream factory
and the juice factory!
The factories of ice, ice cream and juice?
It's summer and those three important things are gone... Just what should I do?
That's not my problem!
And there's even more!
Listen carefully... Something important to chief editor got stolen.
Something important to me?
What's that?
It's beer!
What?!
Did the beer factory get attacked, too?
Yes!
I can't stay here!
Ah! Where are you going?
Isn't it obvious? I'm going to go hoard beer!
Please wait! I'll go hoard ice cream too!
Food Center Imaga
Daily Necessities        Alcohol         Cigarettes
Hey! Sell beer to me, too!
Sold out, sold out! Beer and juice are all sold out!
No way...
Oh? Chief editor!
It sure is hot! Chief editor, you couldn't buy beer?
Yeah...
I got this much. Would you like one?
With this much, I'll survive through this summer.
Let me remind you that once ice cream melts, it's the end for it.
Oh no!
I can't fit this much in the freezer.
What should I do...
So it really was as I thought.
Yeah... Ice, ice cream, juice and beer... They're all things related to summer!
Exkaiser, please do something! At this rate, this summer will be nothing but hot!
Is there anything else that might get targeted?
Anything else?
Oh yeah, there's a fireworks festival this night.
Fireworks festival?
It's a summer's event that many people look forward to!
Fireworks are really beautiful!
They're lights like paintings that fill up the whole night sky.
In order to forget the heat of summer,
everyone watches them while cooling off.
Paintings that light up the night sky, huh...
There's a high possibility that they'll target them.
Exkaiser...
I know, Kouta!
I won't let them do as they wish!
I'm counting on you, Exkaiser!
What's it say here...
"Ms. Hanako bought 6 apples that cost 100 yen each.
She paid them with a 1000 bill.
Well then, how much money did she get back?"
Um... How much, uh...
Ouch!
What's that?
That's what they call ice!
Ice?
There's no flavor at all... What's the use of these?
I don't know! But it's still one of
summer's treasures for humans.
Delicious!
This thing called ice cream is pretty delicious!
Well, let me taste it too.
This is pretty good actually.
What'd you do that for, you bastard!
Beer... Beer is delicious!
This guy... He drank all of the beer from the tank!
I'm strong!
What are you doing?
Stop him!
It couldn't be that you ruined the summer's treasures that we just stole?
N-No! No such thing...
Well, whatever.
The real aim of this plan is to completely crush that Exkaiser bastard.
All of our actions so far were only
bait to lure him out!
And what does that mean?
He's saying that Exkaiser will surely appear at the next place that we'll attack!
And that's the time when we'll finish them off!
Kouta, that's too dangerous!
It'd be best to stop everyone now!
It's impossible! Most of them have already left...
Kouta, what are you doing?
Oh no!
Aren't you coming?
We'll leave you behind if you're so slow!
Sister, Geisters might appear.
Are you really going?
It's alright!
What would summer be if we didn't go to the fireworks festival?
Mama too?
Papa also said that he'll go there to do work.
If things really get dangerous, that Mr. Exkaiser will come for sure!
If you aren't coming, then suit yourself.
Mama, let's go!
I'm worried about everyone, so I'm going!
Such an amazing crowd!
I wonder where papa is?
Ah, it's Kotomi-chan!
Kotomi-chan!
Oh, Kouta-kun!
We want to drink various juices!
We want to eat flavored ice, too!
Everyone seems irritated...
That's right...
Give back beer!
We've lost one of summer's pleasures, dammit!
Papa!
Oh, Kouta!
I'm glad that we found you!
Mama, you look wonderful in a yukata!
Oh you, papa!
Huh? Mr. Tokuda, what's the matter?
K-Kouta-kun... Think of this as saving me and please eat these...
T-Toilet!
He ate so much ice cream,
that he got sick in the stomach.
Oh... I feel bad for him.
What's this? It has melted!
Takumi!
Kotomi-chan, would you like to come over here?
It's air-conditioned, so it's cool!
Look, there's even home-made ice cream here!
Oh?
What are you saying!
The right way to watch fireworks is to cool ourselves with fans at the same time!
What a bad idea that is...
And think about the possibility that Geisters might appear.
You'll escape much faster in a car, right?
That might be true.
Well then, everyone! Let's get in it.
I-I meant only Kotomi-chan...
Give back beer!
Give back my pool!
Let's rough things up!
Wait!
It's dangerous here! Please evacuate!
Change!
We've been waiting for you!
You're like the summer bugs that fly into the flame.
You villains have stolen people's pleasures of summer and disrupted the peace!
Your selfish actions are unforgivable!
Keep on shouting!
Lord Dino Geist!
Change, Dino Geist!
Exkaiser!
Today's the last day you'll be able to talk so mighty!
I'll have you die here!
What?
Let's combine!
Max Team, Form Up!
Triple Fusion, God Max!
Form Up!
Left&Right Fusion, Ultra Raker!
King Loader!
King Loader will get destroyed!
If you can't combine, you'll be no opponent for me!
You'd better not forget about me!
I'm here too!
Just mere two...
I'll defeat you like this!
God Max! Ultra Raker!
Here goes!
You're not even worth mentioning.
T-This is bad!
Exkaiser is getting defeated!
It's dangerous to stay here! Run!
Toilet
Make it move!
This is so amusing!
Damn you! Let go of Exkaiser!
All right! Do your best, Exkaiser!
How dare you bother us!
Oh no!
Kouta, it's dangerous here!
Sorry, Exkaiser...
You villainous Geisters!
If you think that things will go your way now that you've stopped my combining...
You're gravely mistaken!
Dragon Jet!
Tsk, there's another pesky guy...
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, Dragon Kaiser!
What?
Ah! Exkaiser turned into a different robot again!
Dragon Anchor!
Impossible!
This is bad!
Escape!
Hurry!
God Sonic Buster!
Ultra Cannon Beam!
Damn!
Damn you Kaisers! Things won't always go this way!
Remember that!
He's escaping?
Dragon Archery!
Thunder Arrow!
He did it! He did it!
So cool!
Are you alright, God Max, Ultra Raker?
Yeah, these injuries are nothing.
Seems like they didn't know that Exkaiser has a trump card.
But still, what reckless people they are!
Don't say that.
We should resume the fireworks festival that many people were looking forward to.
Yeah.
Yahoo!
Good morning!
Good morning.
Papa, let's go to the beach already!
All compulsory school students around the country!
Please rejoice!
From today on, everyone will receive their
homework to their households via fax again!
That's good for you!
What? You didn't know?
Really! Good for you that you can study again!
No way!
Sheesh!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Have you ever sighed when you
opened your piggy bank?
It's so easy to spend money,
but saving it up is much harder!
I wonder if I'll save enough in time for my sister's birthday present...
But all my sister does is aim for my piggy bank!
She doesn't even care how I feel!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Piggy Bank That Scattered in the Sky
Is there an alien in your home, too?