Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
Destruction! Geisters' Base
Ow ow ow...
You guys sure were careless!
I heard that the back-alley doctor
refuses to check them...
Shut up!
Could you do something about this
instead of complaining-...!
How could I let this happen...
Damn those Kaisers!
Even if he tells us to do something...
If we just roll them somewhere,
won't they heal by themselves?
What did you say?
W-Wait!
Heal this! Heal this!
You've got a lot of guts to make
Thunder Geist angry...
A-Alright! I'll do something about it!
Robot Fair
Portrait Corner
Please eat plenty of takoyaki!
Checkmate!
It just won't leave me...
This sure is amazing!
The next era might be one where there's
one robot in every household.
That could be!
I don't have siblings, so I'd love to have a robot that's like a little brother, but...
I guess it's still impossible?
Well, it seems like it isn't that impossible!
In fact, I came to get information especially about that today.
A robot that understands everything that humans
say and also thinks and acts how it wants...
It seems like professor Tokoroda
has finally completed it.
Really?
Then it's like Exkaiser?
No! It might be even greater!
That's right...
The mankind has finally created the greatest robot!
Kouta-kun...
Don't you believe in the powers of the
Earth's scientist of the century?
T-That's not it...
Hey! Let's hurry and go see that
invention of the century!
Today at the first Robot Fair,
we'll be introducing various robots that might become our neighbours in the future.
Ah, sorry...
Good! It hasn't started yet!
Well then, the greatest robot in the world will be announced here at last.
It's the RPT-001...
Ah, I'm sorry...
Professor Tokoroda has named him Future the 1st.
And he's entrusted with the future of robot culture.
Without further delay, we'll introduce Future the 1st
that's made with mankind's intelligence!
U-Um... This is...?
That shorty is it?
It doesn't look very reliable...
But it's cute!
I'd love to have one!
Um, is this the greatest robot that
mankind has created?
Ah, I see...
It can keep company to elderly and
maybe take the dog for a walk...
Professor, welcome back home!
Would you like coffee?
Please give me your hand...
Blood pressure is slightly high.
Let's leave the sugar out.
Amazing!
Professor!
Can we talk with Future the 1st, too?
Let's try it!
Me too!
Everyone! Sorry for the wait!
Questions regarding the publicity of Future the 1st
can all be asked from me, the eldest son of the Kaneari Group that sponsored this research.
I, Kaneari Takumi, will be in charge of them.
Sponsor?
Well, the investment money was about a billlion...
Well then, our Kaneari Group has created
this together with professor Tokoroda.
It's the super robot of the century, Future the 1st.
Well then, Future the 1st.
What shall I make you do...
That's it!
Future the 1st, could you turn off that TV?
Yes!
Um... Just what is this?
What's going on?
Future the 1st can't yet be programmed with a distinction
of turning off the TV and turning off the power?
Is something wrong?
It's Geisters!
Where is that doctor?
It's not a doctor, it's a professor.
There's trouble!
Kouta!
Wait for me!
Rescue! Rescue!
It's the rescue robots! Let's ride them quickly!
Wait!
Takumi!
Kouta-kun!
Lean on me!
Danger! Danger!
Must depart immediately!
Kouta-kun, hurry!
Kouta-kun!
Damn you!
Wait!
Your opponent is me!
What did you say, you brat?
T-This is a big scoop!
Professor Tokoroda! What are you doing?
You must escape quickly!
I found you! Are you the doctor
that's called a professor?
You won't be getting away!
Where did he go?
Ah, professor! Let's go in that!
Thanks for that.
Is this guy the doctor that's called a professor?
That's right!
Then let's take this whole thing.
Wait!
Change, Exkaiser!
So you appeared, damn Exkaiser!
Geisters who disrupt the peace on Earth!
I, Exkaiser, won't forgive any of your evil doings!
Exkaiser!
Uh-uh! Don't even dare getting closer than that.
Don't you care what happens to these guys?
Help us!
That's it! It's good to be obedient!
Armor, hold this for a moment!
Kouta!
You unfair villains!
I'm fine with being unfair!
Horn, let's get going already.
Yeah!
K-Kouta!
Can they really fix us?
This guy too?
What about this?
Throw it away! It can't even be used as any parts.
You're right.
Kouta!
Someone...
Dragon Jet!
Alert to all Kaisers!
Geisters have taken away Kouta,
professor Tokoroda and Mr. Tokuda!
You should all spread out and search!
Roger!
Someone save us...
That should be enough parts.
Come on, fix this quickly!
Fix this!
Um... Do you have ointment or something...?
What did you say?
I'm sorry!
Bandages then...
Kouta! Kouta!
What's wrong, Kouta?
Kouta, are you alright?
Somehow...
Where are you currently?
Um... This is...
That hurt!
I'm sorry!
Are you really an assistant?
I-It's really true...
Welcome back home! Would you like coffee?
Can't this guy do anything else?
It's a children's toy!
Hot!
Hot! So hot!
Thunder! Can't you be quiet?
This is terrible!
We have been brought to Geisters' base!
What did you say?
There's some strange radio waves...
Geisters' base, you said?
Yeah! Professor Tokoroda has been brought
here in order to repair their hurt comrades.
Mr. Tokuda is here also.
Listen carefully, Kouta!
Keep on transmitting to me.
Okay!
I'll definitely come save you by
relying on this radio wave!
Kouta! Kouta!
It's jammed, huh?
Exkaiser?
If I could take a full picture of this Geisters' Base...
It'd be a big scoop... No, I'd get an exclusive award!
What?
Don't disturb us!
Something emits radio waves that are
different from what humans use!
We're under treatment!
Do you really think that these
guys could do such a feat?
Or don't you just want us to get fixed?
Idiot!
What if this place is found by Kaisers?
Search for the source of the radio waves!
... Is what Lord Dino Geist said!
Alright then!
Fix our injuries quickly!
Y-Yes!
I need to stop the jamming somehow...
This is Max Team!
We haven't found Kouta and the others yet.
Raker Brothers, how's it going there?
No luck!
We haven't seen even a glimpse.
The jamming is strong, but keep on searching!
Kouta, where are you?
This might be the control room...
Um... The switch is...
Brat! Where did you come in from?
Wait!
It's a dead end over there.
Please help us!
Thanks to you we're able to move better now.
Mr. Tokuda!
Are you alright?
Kouta-kun! Why are you here?
I was hiding inside that truck!
Welcome back home!
We don't need you anymore!
You can all go to the afterlife together!
Help us!
What's the use in putting the TVs on?
TVs?
I see!
Future the 1st!
Turn off those TVs!
Roger!
Don't mind that thing.
Prepare yourselves!
What?
Now's our chance!
It's dark!
What did they do?
Kouta!
I got it! They're in the underground of that volcano!
King Loader!
Ah! It's the exit!
Alright!
I thought that we were done for! We're saved!
Maybe we're done for, after all...
You sure looked down on us...
Die!
Help!
We've finally found your location, Dino Geist!
You can't escape nor hide anymore!
Exkaiser... You dare come to our base!
Exkaiser!
Thank you! This time we're saved for sure!
What?
Unforgivable!
Change, Dino Geist!
Dino Shield!
Dino Blade!
What?
Now!
Dragon Jet!
Super Giant Fusion, Great Exkaiser!
Great Kick!
Kaiser Sword!
Double Fusion, Pteder!
Double Fusion, Hormor!
God Sonic Buster!
It's an earthquake...
Oh no! An eruption will happen!
Bring it on, Exkaiser.
Thunder Flash!
It's an eruption!
Escape!
We'll get engulfed!
Exkaiser!
Exkaiser...
Seems like we made it okay...
Where's Lord Dino Geist?
He's over there!
Our essential base...
Remember this, damn Exkaiser!
Thank you for saving us!
We should be the ones to thank you.
Thanks to you we were able to
destroy the Geisters' base.
It was all Future the 1st's achievement!
Eh? Was that so?
Thank you once more then, Future the 1st-kun!
Thank you very much!
Thank goodness...
Well then, let's have afternoon tea.
Yeah!
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
Mario ran away from home!
It's all because sister called him a fatty
human-faced dog! That's too much!
I do believe that Mario is a tough,
gentle and wise dog...
Geisters appeared at the Bow-Wow Contest!
Mario! Do your best! You must save everyone!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Mario and Juliet
Is there an alien in your home, too?