Brave Exkaiser
Over a million of them shine with a blue light
The shards of love have scattered
It's brewing in this world
A storm that you'll confront
And because I believe in you
I'm not afraid of anything
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
Courage and friendship
That moment when we join our strength GATHER WAY
GO WITH ME Exkaiser
I'd almost forgotten it
The fiery burning and important PASSIONATE feeling in my heart
The mysterious and vast universe.
In this universe exists the evil life forms,
the space pirates Geisters
who've invaded Earth in order to obtain the treasures of mankind.
However, in front of the Geisters who use destruction and plunder as they wish
a hero appeared, who completely stood in their way.
He is the cosmic police, Exkaiser.
This is the story of Brave Exkaiser and his friends, who fight against evil all around the universe.
It's Terrible! Mama Is...!
Just what is going to begin?
I'm going to surprise my mama!
Why?
Well, obviously because today's Mother's Day!
But...
Mama, over here!
Over here, I'm telling you!
What? What's going on?
It's okay, okay!
It'll be the moment of joy!
I really think it's not nice to surprise her.
There you go!
Oh Kouta, what are you doing?
It's Mother's Day!
Oh my, they're beautiful. Thank you!
Oh yes, you two should come too!
To the World Fair of Flowers 2001!
Eh, really?
Lucky!
Mr. Tokuda's mother is coming to Tokyo today.
And so, papa asked that I'd keep them company.
Mr. Tokuda's mother?
Papa asked you? Then who is going to drive...?
Just get ready right away, you two!
It's been a while since I last drove!
Eh, our mama is going to drive?
Sister, it's okay! Don't be worried!
Is it really gonna be okay?
Yup!
Uh, mama?
What is it, Fuuko?
Could you do something about the speed...
You're right!
There we go!
Exkaiser! Weren't you going to steer us nicely?
Today is mama's day, right?
I'm moving exactly in the way she wants to.
No way!
Mother! Please wait a little!
I'm really sorry!
Instead of sending you a carnation on Mother's Day,
I invited you to the World Fair of Flowers 2001 as chief editor was so nice to give me a day off!
So let's have a nice time with just us close-knit family!
What do you mean "close-knit"?
I've never got a carnation from you!
Well, that's why... This includes all the earlier times...
If you'd have such an admirable heart,
you wouldn't have been late on picking me up!
I said there was a traffic jam...
Shut up!
You obviously drank too much
last night and slept in late!
How did you know...
How many years do you think I've been your mother?
Just because we don't see often,
I can still see through one or two lies!
Well, it is true that last night I drank a little in preparation for mother...
What do you mean "preparation"?
Am I a ghost?
Sheesh, what do you take your parent for?
Well, isn't it obvious!
My mother is my treasure!
No, the country's treasure!
Mother! The entrance is in the opposite direction...
Treasure?
All right, go ahead.
What the...?
Oh, there's no free space...
M-Mama! Look in front! In front!
Oh, there's a free space!
Alright, we're here.
Lord Dino Geist! Lord Dino Geist!
What do you mean "preparation"?
Am I a ghost?
Sheesh, what do you take your parent for?
Well, isn't it obvious!
My mother is my treasure!
No, the country's treasure!
I'll be going ahead to steal that...
It's not good to get all the glory by yourself, now is it, Armor?
Let's go over there!
Delicious!
What on earth is this? Such a bad taste...
Hi, so you came here too?
Takumi!
What do you think?
It's a restaurant my mama started as a part of her business.
Would you like to come inside?
It only serves french cuisine though...
We're good.
Come on now!
I'll at least introduce you to my mother.
Mother!
Huh?
Mother! Where did... you go?
Mother!
Let's go.
How strange...
I was sure they were going to wait here...
Osamu, could you hurry up?
Come on, mother! Don't hurry so much!
It's such a disgrace to make the
chief editor's wife wait!
Don't be such a slowpoke!
Are you alright?
What a beauty...
Mother, are you alright?
Osamu, she is the one!
Mr. Tokuda!
Oh, I'm sorry for all this!
You know each other? Well, that makes things easy.
Um... What could you mean...
Mr. Tokuda!
What's the matter?
Young lady, would you like to marry our Osamu?
Oh, you called me a young lady...
Well, now I'm troubled. What should I do?
What's the matter, Blue Raker?
Exkaiser, what's going on today?
The tip of my nose is so itchy, I can't stand it!
Today is called "Mother's Day".
It's a day when they put up flowers and treat mothers with great care.
This planet sure is strange...
If that's the case, they should just do it everyday.
You're right, Green Raker!
What on earth is this?
Could something have happened to Kouta-kun and the others...?
Why didn't you say earlier that she is the chief editor's wife?
You...!
You made me embarrass myself!
Oh? "Mother Contest"?
Could I be able to enter?
It looks interesting!
Would Mr. Tokuda's mother also like to enter this?
That's a nice idea, you should enter it!
My mother will surely win!
You idiot!
At times like this, you should cheer on the madam!
Let's go then, madam!
Y-Yes...
Come on now!
Mr. Tokuda has it tough too, huh?
Not really. I'm always so irresolute, that my mother can't help but nag out of worry!
Is that what it is?
Alright, let's go too.
Um, I need to go to the toilet, so go on ahead!
Is that so?
I've been a cosmic police for a long time,
but it's my first time seeing a malicious space creature parasitizing on a human.
You're wrong!
That's a baby inside her stomach!
Eh? A baby?
I also grew up in my mother's stomach and was born from there.
It's the same for all humans and animals!
So they protect the children inside the mother's body?
You're exaggerating things, Exkaiser!
So there's a treasure there, Armor?
I'm sure about it!
I heard that the best one is being picked out in there.
Okay, got it!
And now, next up on the Mother Contest is the contest of changing diapers!
Who is the no. 1 mother!?
Start!
Done!
That's the way to go!
No, that's all wrong! Borrow me that.
I'm sorry!
Sheesh, young people these days...
W-What's that?
Alright, let's search for the treasure!
Which one is the treasure?
Lost Child Center
Mother!
Where is the treasure?
Here it is!
Over here!
Madam! It's alright since I'm here!
Don't you dare come close to the madam!
What a great intensity!
It's the same as in a monster movie!
No good, I can't reach!
Let's use this then.
Alright, do it!
Mama!
Mother!
Change, Exkaiser!
For all the living things in this world,
a mother is the most important existence!
You dare to put your hands on these mothers...
It's unforgivable!
Stop saying similar things every time!
Kill him!
Mother!
Osamu!
I'll save you immediately!
You idiot! Aren't you a newspaper reporter?
It's a scoop! Make this scoop your own!
What are you saying!
My mother is more important than any scoop!
Osamu!
Mr. Tokuda, do your best!
Mother!
I've got the treasure!
Mama!!
Oh no, mama is...!
You damn monster, give back my mother!
We gotta save them somehow!
But how?
If we don't do something, starting from tomorrow there won't be anyone to make us breakfast
and there won't be anyone to change the sheets when you wet your bed!
I don't wet my bed!
Do it! Do it more!
Change, Blue Raker!
Change, Green Raker!
Raker Brothers!
Leave this to us!
Go save the mothers quickly!
Got it!
Save us! Oh no, we're done for!
It's alright!
The ally of justice won't abandon us!
I won't let you go, Armor Geist!
We're here!
See?
Ugh, you're still alive...
As long as there's evil in this world,
justice will never die!
Now! Give the mothers back!
Uh-oh, I can't let that happen.
Such cowardice!
Now, pull!
Blue Raker!
What's the matter, Exkaiser?
Are you completely hopeless?
Damn!
Armor Geist! How long are you playing around?
Give the treasure to me quickly!
Mama!
Mother!
Mother, I'll save you now!
Osamu!
Mother!
This is the treasure all right!
You bastard!
Shut up already!
Mr. Tokuda, hold on!
Kouta-kun, never mind me...
Please... save my mother...
Mr. Tokuda...
What the heck!
If your mother is important to you, such wounds shouldn't hurt one bit!
Mama, wait for me.
Kouta!
Mama!
What a noisy fly!
You monster!
What are you doing to my son?!
Oh crap!
Kouta!
Mama!
Big brother...!
Little brother...!
Big brother!
Twin Power!
Form Up!
Left&Right Fusion, Ultra Raker!
Ultra Raker!
Now, go quickly to a safe place.
Mama!
King Loader!
Form Up!
Giant Fusion, King Exkaiser!
Come on, attack however you like!
Kaiser Shot!
Kaiser Sword!
Oh no, it's all over now!
Let's escape!
Thunder Flash!
Mother!
Osamu!
Osamu, thank goodness you're okay!
I'm so glad... As long as mother is alright, I'm...!
What?!
You didn't take a single photograph of this amazing scoop?
S-Sorry... But...
You no good!
How many years have you been a newspaper reporter? Sheesh!
It's awful! My mother is gone!
She got taken away by those guys...
Announcement!
To the visitor Kaneari Takumi,
your mother has left you a message:
"I'm going home early."
That is all.
Mother!
Thank you, Exkaiser!
A mother, huh?
Seems like a rather troublesome treasure.
Faraway wind carries your dream
What could you discover from this excited feeling
Dreams get bigger strongly and fast
Don't forget to be who you are
Embrace your enthusiastic heart
And try walking that path
NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW
What was the dream I saw last night?
It was a really cool dream...
When you see a good dream,
you're happy all day, right?
But what's up with this noice? My head will burst!
I can't sleep like this!
I know! It's those Geisters!
They're trying to steal dreams from us!
On the next episode of Brave Exkaiser,
Be Careful of Dream Thieves
Is there an alien in your home, too?